{
  "Class III" : {
    "English" : {
      "-MFnmrYuLPkwasSYbEpn" : {
        "Answer" : "Eat with small bites ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:40:6",
        "Option1" : "Eat with large bites ",
        "Option2" : "Eat with small bites ",
        "Option3" : "Eat with tiny bites ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "1-The meaning of \"Nibble\" is _____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnTTIDyOYLyWJigvV" : {
        "Answer" : "Unwanted small plants ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:42:46",
        "Option1" : "Unwanted small plants ",
        "Option2" : "Unwanted big plants ",
        "Option3" : "Unwanted plants ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both ",
        "Question" : "2-The meaning of \"Weeds\" is ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnxjXWkxJKlbWRvqh" : {
        "Answer" : "To jump",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:44:54",
        "Option1" : "To fly",
        "Option2" : "To jump",
        "Option3" : "To move",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "3-\"Climb\" meaning is____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnoVIEiklE3NXxSuh6" : {
        "Answer" : "Personal",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:47:15",
        "Option1" : "Personal",
        "Option2" : "Private ",
        "Option3" : "Particular",
        "Option4" : "Individual ",
        "Question" : "4-\"Own\" means.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnplUSYRkWiOOZdX4Q" : {
        "Answer" : "Life cycle of Frog ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:52:48",
        "Option1" : "Life cycle of Frog ",
        "Option2" : "Life cycle of Lizard ",
        "Option3" : "Life cycle of Honey Bee",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "5-The story \"Growing\" is about____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnqCLBfHdebOqSICx-" : {
        "Answer" : "A large hole in the side of a hill ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:54:42",
        "Option1" : "A small hole in the side of a hill ",
        "Option2" : "A large hole in the side of a hill ",
        "Option3" : "A damaged hole in the side of a hill ",
        "Option4" : "A,C both",
        "Question" : "6-\"Cave\" means",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnqc_aQTcaSd_m3jnx" : {
        "Answer" : "Gold",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:56:34",
        "Option1" : "Silver",
        "Option2" : "Gold",
        "Option3" : "Mud",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "7-The story \"Three Girls\" is about to get the ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnqxtOehc7i3AOtmyu" : {
        "Answer" : "The spirit of a dead",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:58:1",
        "Option1" : "The spirit of evil",
        "Option2" : "The spirit of  dead animal ",
        "Option3" : "The spirit of a dead",
        "Option4" : "A,C both",
        "Question" : "8-\"Ghost\" means",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnrRR3AeYcVgLiNnPa" : {
        "Answer" : "Strong ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:0:6",
        "Option1" : "Strong ",
        "Option2" : "Weak",
        "Option3" : "Confident ",
        "Option4" : "Innocent ",
        "Question" : "9- In the story \"Three Girls\" the third girl is ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFns3IKGtfzJwgkZRbv" : {
        "Answer" : "Tadpole",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:2:49",
        "Option1" : "Larva",
        "Option2" : "Tadpole",
        "Option3" : "Pupa",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "10-The second stage of growing of \"Frog\" is ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnsQmfY__IBtCKXWRg" : {
        "Answer" : "Cave",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:4:25",
        "Option1" : "Room",
        "Option2" : "Class",
        "Option3" : "Cave",
        "Option4" : "A,C both",
        "Question" : "11-In the story \"Three Girls\" the third girl goes into the ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnsuX1dKhz4iWjb1NS" : {
        "Answer" : "An area of sand near a sea",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:6:31",
        "Option1" : "An area of sand near a sea",
        "Option2" : "An area of mud near a lake",
        "Option3" : "An area of sand near a river ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "12-The meaning of \"Beach\" is ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFntZq0rA2biY65wmVg" : {
        "Answer" : "Sun, Kitten, Park",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:9:25",
        "Option1" : "Sun, Kitten, Park",
        "Option2" : "Sour, Green, Tall",
        "Option3" : "Wasp, Scooter, Rude",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "13- Identify the set of \"Noun\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnu7zpYKKRIzqmDg9w" : {
        "Answer" : "Quaid e Azam",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:11:53",
        "Option1" : "Allama Iqbal ",
        "Option2" : "Quaid e Azam",
        "Option3" : "Liaqat Ali khan ",
        "Option4" : "Nawaz Sharif ",
        "Question" : "14- Select the name of person as the founder of Pakistan from the given \"Proper Noun\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnuRbHRhn6joaZrYlb" : {
        "Answer" : "Adnan",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:13:13",
        "Option1" : "Lady",
        "Option2" : "Boy",
        "Option3" : "Man",
        "Option4" : "Adnan",
        "Question" : "15-Identify \"Proper Noun\" ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnus20IT4n9ytFBnYE" : {
        "Answer" : "Animal",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:15:5",
        "Option1" : "Peacock",
        "Option2" : "Aunt",
        "Option3" : "Animal",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "16-Which one is the \"Common Noun\" in given words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnvWVS0_-_C9rC3qUS" : {
        "Answer" : "Doctor",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:17:55",
        "Option1" : "Engineer",
        "Option2" : "Doctor",
        "Option3" : "Farmer",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "17- Complete the sentence with \"Noun\".\nI work in a hospital. I look after those who are sick.\nI am a _____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnw-aGyQ0OclODfjjR" : {
        "Answer" : "Celebrating ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:20:3",
        "Option1" : "Playing ",
        "Option2" : "Celebrating ",
        "Option3" : "Washing",
        "Option4" : "Listening ",
        "Question" : "18- Choose the correct \"Verb\". \nWe are ____ Grandma's eightieth birthday today.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnwF4K8NqGtUQFV3O0" : {
        "Answer" : "Caught ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:21:6",
        "Option1" : "Cards",
        "Option2" : "Caught ",
        "Option3" : "Trees",
        "Option4" : "Blue",
        "Question" : "19- Pick the \"Verb\" in given words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnwTyVusiAtgYUSDNO" : {
        "Answer" : "Great",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:22:7",
        "Option1" : "Whisper ",
        "Option2" : "Kitten ",
        "Option3" : "Great",
        "Option4" : "Window",
        "Question" : "20- Choose the \"Adjective\" in given words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnwoa0pwkQ9qcr55-G" : {
        "Answer" : "Great",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:23:36",
        "Option1" : "Great",
        "Option2" : "Red",
        "Option3" : "Whisper",
        "Option4" : "Caught ",
        "Question" : "21- Give the \"Adjective\" to given sentence.\nKing Aurangzeb was a ____ ruler.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnxTZLZcY9zSdFr-0r" : {
        "Answer" : "Is",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:26:28",
        "Option1" : "Are",
        "Option2" : "Am",
        "Option3" : "Is",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "22- Choose the correct \"Verb\" (being word) for given sentence.\nSalma ____ watching T.V",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnxm-bZTfStSueZc2u" : {
        "Answer" : "Brown",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:27:47",
        "Option1" : "Brown",
        "Option2" : "Stitch ",
        "Option3" : "Card",
        "Option4" : "Cattle",
        "Question" : "23- Identify \"Adjective\"\nAli has ____ belt.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnyQWUYF_GsKt7oB28" : {
        "Answer" : "Caught, Stitch, Celebrate",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:30:37",
        "Option1" : "Sun, Park, Tall",
        "Option2" : "Rude, Innocent, Sharp",
        "Option3" : "Caught, Stitch, Celebrate",
        "Option4" : "Board, Pencil, Eraser ",
        "Question" : "24- Choose the set of \"Verb\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnyuvaR9_aJC64PElW" : {
        "Answer" : "Tall, Brown, Sharp",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:32:46",
        "Option1" : "Tall, Brown, Sharp",
        "Option2" : "Stitch, Cattle, Card",
        "Option3" : "Camel, Horse, Aunt",
        "Option4" : "Caught, Swim, Watch",
        "Question" : "25- Choose the set of \"Adjectives\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "ICT" : {
      "-MFlUrbduUMFn2EhhPwh" : {
        "Answer" : "instructions ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:57:51",
        "Option1" : "instructions ",
        "Option2" : "results ",
        "Option3" : "pictures ",
        "Option4" : "files ",
        "Question" : "Hardware needs______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlWg9amx3vSL2_gTn4" : {
        "Answer" : "tasks ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:5:49",
        "Option1" : "tasks ",
        "Option2" : "programs ",
        "Option3" : "drive ",
        "Option4" : "title case",
        "Question" : "Computer performs many______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlXd1WZERunllvMaZh" : {
        "Answer" : "Hard disk",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:9:58",
        "Option1" : "Hard disk",
        "Option2" : "Floppy  disk",
        "Option3" : "Ram",
        "Option4" : "CD",
        "Question" : "_____ drives are used rarely now a days.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlY9C695fGk6ALXUkz" : {
        "Answer" : "Motherboard ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:12:14",
        "Option1" : "Modem",
        "Option2" : "Ram ",
        "Option3" : "Motherboard ",
        "Option4" : "Power supply",
        "Question" : "______ is the main circuit board of a computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlYj3sAa4l-GBC5J-X" : {
        "Answer" : "Data",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:14:45",
        "Option1" : "Data",
        "Option2" : "Input",
        "Option3" : "Output",
        "Option4" : "Storage device",
        "Question" : "It is collection of facts and figures. ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlZt9IxmMr8n2odwEl" : {
        "Answer" : "CD/DVDs",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:19:48",
        "Option1" : "CD/DVDs",
        "Option2" : "Monitor ",
        "Option3" : "Mouse",
        "Option4" : "Web cam",
        "Question" : "Games, movies and songs are stored in the______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl_e6IYlWXpkEMnKy9" : {
        "Answer" : "Usb",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:23:9",
        "Option1" : "Usb",
        "Option2" : "system unit",
        "Option3" : "Software",
        "Option4" : "Hardware",
        "Question" : "We can use______ to transfer data from one computer to another computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlc9-RcizrlebXDtuC" : {
        "Answer" : "Flash drive",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:34:3",
        "Option1" : "Hard disk",
        "Option2" : "Cd",
        "Option3" : "Flash drive",
        "Option4" : "Google drive",
        "Question" : "______ is used to store very small amount of information. ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlcdGCP3YKyvUB1O5s" : {
        "Answer" : "Hard disk",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:36:12",
        "Option1" : "Hard disk",
        "Option2" : "Scanner",
        "Option3" : "Files",
        "Option4" : "Pages",
        "Question" : "_______ is the main storage device of computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlekswcEJJCFYYGK9Q" : {
        "Answer" : "System unit",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:45:27",
        "Option1" : "System unit",
        "Option2" : "Flash drive ",
        "Option3" : "Input",
        "Option4" : "Soft copy",
        "Question" : "It protects the parts of a computer from dust and damage.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlfFwsYrWxXgJLZxyC" : {
        "Answer" : "Storage device",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 1:47:39",
        "Option1" : "Power supply",
        "Option2" : "Input ",
        "Option3" : "Out put",
        "Option4" : "Storage device",
        "Question" : "The device which are used to store data and information are known as: ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnlyZNoRmIYKsRCmjT" : {
        "Answer" : "Physical",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:36:12",
        "Option1" : "Storage",
        "Option2" : "Physical",
        "Option3" : "Digital",
        "Option4" : "Input",
        "Question" : "Hardware refers to the ______ parts of a compute.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmTplnCeov_0cGUpN" : {
        "Answer" : "Input device",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:38:25",
        "Option1" : "Input device",
        "Option2" : "Out put device",
        "Option3" : "System unit",
        "Option4" : "Hardware",
        "Question" : "The devices which are used to put data into the computer are called______ devices.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmnloljsmpm5gEQF2" : {
        "Answer" : "Keyboard",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:39:50",
        "Option1" : "Cpu",
        "Option2" : "Keyboard",
        "Option3" : "Microphone",
        "Option4" : "CD",
        "Question" : "It is used to input letters, numbers and other symbols in a computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnA-QTbG4G_dYoy0P" : {
        "Answer" : "Mouse",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:41:26",
        "Option1" : "Printer",
        "Option2" : "Scanner",
        "Option3" : "Mouse",
        "Option4" : "Software",
        "Question" : "It is used to open programs and applications.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnVzStYrAaEyVjkve" : {
        "Answer" : "Speakers",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:42:56",
        "Option1" : "Speakers",
        "Option2" : "Mike",
        "Option3" : "Monitor",
        "Option4" : "Webcam",
        "Question" : "We can listen music and other sounds with the help of______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnzC0RULOCD8K_Esn" : {
        "Answer" : "Digital camera",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:44:59",
        "Option1" : "Mouse",
        "Option2" : "Digital camera",
        "Option3" : "Keyboard",
        "Option4" : "Microphone",
        "Question" : "A _____ is also used to input pictures and videos in a computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnoUTm51FPQ0_mv6hK" : {
        "Answer" : "Audio",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:47:12",
        "Option1" : "Audio",
        "Option2" : "Video",
        "Option3" : "Radio",
        "Option4" : "Tv",
        "Question" : "Speakers are used to produce _______ output.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnq_40kTxyIAQIdPas" : {
        "Answer" : "Small",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:56:19",
        "Option1" : "Large",
        "Option2" : "Small",
        "Option3" : "Ram",
        "Option4" : "Millions",
        "Question" : "A floppy disk is used to store very _______ amount of information.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnqmIm9GWddIUv3Vwg" : {
        "Answer" : "Scanner",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:57:13",
        "Option1" : "Scanner",
        "Option2" : "Input",
        "Option3" : "Webcam",
        "Option4" : "Output",
        "Question" : "A ______ is used to scan images and documents in a computer.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnrAKs-0HIcFF02056" : {
        "Answer" : "Storage",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:58:55",
        "Option1" : "Output",
        "Option2" : "Storage",
        "Option3" : "Process",
        "Option4" : "Informative",
        "Question" : "A flash drive is _______ device.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnrSl-x690z2uFBG8G" : {
        "Answer" : "System unit",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:0:11",
        "Option1" : "Mother board",
        "Option2" : "RAM",
        "Option3" : "System unit",
        "Option4" : "Floppy disk",
        "Question" : "A _______ contains different parts of a compute.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnsEFiteTYKhBVIH-O" : {
        "Answer" : "Scanner",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:3:34",
        "Option1" : "Digital camera",
        "Option2" : "Scanner",
        "Option3" : "Speakers",
        "Option4" : "Headphones",
        "Question" : "It works like a photocopy.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnthLuAViikBOF44UY" : {
        "Answer" : "Headphones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:9:59",
        "Option1" : "Headphones",
        "Option2" : "Printer",
        "Option3" : "Scanner ",
        "Option4" : "Mike",
        "Question" : "______ are used to hear sounds from a computers.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnuM6S3V7PV0cvtdb4" : {
        "Answer" : "Electronic",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:12:50",
        "Option1" : "Electronic",
        "Option2" : "Manual ",
        "Option3" : "Baking",
        "Option4" : "Shaking",
        "Question" : "A computer is an ________ machine.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Islamiyat" : {
      "-MFnRAg-sbpN-l5CRnfk" : {
        "Answer" : "Oneness of Allah",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:0:59",
        "Option1" : "Oneness of Allah",
        "Option2" : "Belief in prophets",
        "Option3" : "Belief in Holy books",
        "Option4" : "Belief in judgement",
        "Question" : "The first principal of Islam is belief in the______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnRh_FzUT_2uMNr8Ve" : {
        "Answer" : "One supreme being",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:3:18",
        "Option1" : "Many gods",
        "Option2" : "One supreme being",
        "Option3" : "A robot",
        "Option4" : "Machine",
        "Question" : "The balance and arrangements of the universe proves that there is _______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSQzp0wh0TiWXlBRc" : {
        "Answer" : "Kalima Tayyab",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:6:28",
        "Option1" : "Kalima Shahadat",
        "Option2" : "Kalima Tayyab",
        "Option3" : "Kalima Tamjeed",
        "Option4" : "Kalima Touheed",
        "Question" : "The first kalima is________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTWFcyXN9vb3TXb55" : {
        "Answer" : "For Muslims",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:11:12",
        "Option1" : "For Muslims",
        "Option2" : "For Christians ",
        "Option3" : "For hindus",
        "Option4" : "For Chinese",
        "Question" : "Touhid is the most important belief________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnU3Nj7eE2SbQxgPL3" : {
        "Answer" : "Pak and pure",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:13:36",
        "Option1" : "First",
        "Option2" : "Pak and pure",
        "Option3" : "Only one",
        "Option4" : "Supreme being",
        "Question" : "Tayyab means ______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnV5S0s9MZsAuyDunW" : {
        "Answer" : "First kalima",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:18:7",
        "Option1" : "First kalima",
        "Option2" : "Third kalima",
        "Option3" : "Fourth kalima",
        "Option4" : "Second kalima",
        "Question" : "Muslims declare Touheed by reciting ______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnVQGQPfWFMCobzVb2" : {
        "Answer" : "Touheed",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:19:32",
        "Option1" : "Prayer",
        "Option2" : "Quran",
        "Option3" : "Touheed",
        "Option4" : "Truth",
        "Question" : "To believe in one Allah is called________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnVoA5fC_whm-I9aJj" : {
        "Answer" : "Unity of Allah",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:21:14",
        "Option1" : "Universe",
        "Option2" : "World",
        "Option3" : "Unity of Allah",
        "Option4" : "Truth",
        "Question" : "All the prophets and messengers preached about the ________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnWIRfpJo3DwbNyoQ2" : {
        "Answer" : "Single and unique",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:23:22",
        "Option1" : "Partner",
        "Option2" : "Supportive",
        "Option3" : "Single and unique",
        "Option4" : "Master",
        "Question" : "Touheed means that Allah is _________. ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnWdyAtttO3DgdaQPj" : {
        "Answer" : "Faith",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:24:54",
        "Option1" : "Trust ",
        "Option2" : "Friendship",
        "Option3" : "Faith",
        "Option4" : "Loard",
        "Question" : "We should have firm ______ in Allah.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnX4uMZEHDtf5kpKQE" : {
        "Answer" : "Shark and dolphin",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:26:48",
        "Option1" : "Shark and dolphin",
        "Option2" : "Rabbit and hen",
        "Option3" : "Birds",
        "Option4" : "Camel",
        "Question" : "What creation of Allah will you find under the oceans?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnXjA0BDwAbxuy8tCN" : {
        "Answer" : "Lion and tiger",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:29:37",
        "Option1" : "Lion and tiger",
        "Option2" : "Star fish and octopus",
        "Option3" : "Humans",
        "Option4" : "Sea horse",
        "Question" : "What creation of Allah will you find in the jungle?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYUpbbh3kOdSOjRoT" : {
        "Answer" : "Human and animals ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:32:57",
        "Option1" : "Human and animals ",
        "Option2" : "Rainbow",
        "Option3" : "Star and moon",
        "Option4" : "Clouds",
        "Question" : "What creation of Allah will you find in the earth?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYq4ORVHNyfd0r364" : {
        "Answer" : "Camel and sand",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:34:28",
        "Option1" : "Sea",
        "Option2" : "River ",
        "Option3" : "Camel and sand",
        "Option4" : "Flowers",
        "Question" : "What creation will you find in the desert?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZIlNKFIzSlMXMXJZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Allah's creation",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:36:29",
        "Option1" : "Made by man",
        "Option2" : "Allah's creation",
        "Option3" : "Made by angels",
        "Option4" : "Created by itself",
        "Question" : "Muslims must believe that the world we live in__________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZnZuwRsdgv8sSIfw" : {
        "Answer" : "Messenger",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:38:40",
        "Option1" : "Commander",
        "Option2" : "Unique",
        "Option3" : "Messenger",
        "Option4" : "Subordinate",
        "Question" : "Hazrat Muhammad (S.A.W) is his ________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnaEs7pIT5FnHRwi8n" : {
        "Answer" : "Surah Al- Ikhlas",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:44:58",
        "Option1" : "Surah Al- Nas",
        "Option2" : "Surah Al- Alaq",
        "Option3" : "Surah Al- Ikhlas",
        "Option4" : "Surah Al- Fatihah",
        "Question" : "In which verse the Quran highlight concept of Touheed?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnaZ4QN83eZbLb7ZfV" : {
        "Answer" : "Touheed",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:46:21",
        "Option1" : "Touheed",
        "Option2" : "Worship",
        "Option3" : "Leader",
        "Option4" : "Messenger",
        "Question" : "The main emphasis of the Quran is upon the principal of _____.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnb2Zp5ndIMT7RUqxY" : {
        "Answer" : "Creator ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:48:30",
        "Option1" : "Messenger",
        "Option2" : "Greatest",
        "Option3" : "Creator ",
        "Option4" : "Kind",
        "Question" : "If you believe in the oneness of Allah then you believe that he is _______ of all things.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbNeunsCi34r8QU33" : {
        "Answer" : "Prophets",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:49:56",
        "Option1" : "Books",
        "Option2" : "Prophets",
        "Option3" : "Angels",
        "Option4" : "Light",
        "Question" : "He sent ______ to show them right path.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnc7kRD8R5t6V96dvS" : {
        "Answer" : "There is none like unto him",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:53:13",
        "Option1" : "There is none like unto him",
        "Option2" : "Holy Prophets ",
        "Option3" : "Belief in holy books",
        "Option4" : "Day of judgment",
        "Question" : "What is the meaning of \" There is no god but Allah \"",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncNNqCcV9SyKjvcDx" : {
        "Answer" : "Five ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:54:17",
        "Option1" : "Two",
        "Option2" : "Three",
        "Option3" : "Five ",
        "Option4" : "Six",
        "Question" : "How many pillars of Islam?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnlQAExH7qYBKvPOeU" : {
        "Answer" : "Allah is everywhere",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:33:47",
        "Option1" : "In mosque",
        "Option2" : "On the sky",
        "Option3" : "Allah is everywhere",
        "Option4" : "In Holy Kabaah",
        "Question" : "Where is Allah?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCKdPpqp18MQRyF8SJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Kind people",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:42:33",
        "Option1" : "Cruel people ",
        "Option2" : "Kind people",
        "Option3" : "Bad people ",
        "Option4" : "Honest people ",
        "Question" : "Who are the friends of Allah?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCL-cNhUZe34BXR3Ep" : {
        "Answer" : "To belive in heart ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:44:8",
        "Option1" : "To belive in heart ",
        "Option2" : "To belive in seeing",
        "Option3" : "To belive in knowledge ",
        "Option4" : "To belive in light ",
        "Question" : "What is the meaning of faith?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Math" : {
      "-MFnbWyoCrgcXGkOq9bx" : {
        "Answer" : "139",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:50:34",
        "Option1" : "193",
        "Option2" : "138",
        "Option3" : "139",
        "Option4" : "319",
        "Question" : "Write the number having 1 hundred 3 tens 9 ones",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbf6FR2lVFs4B9BQ8" : {
        "Answer" : "tens",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:51:12",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "What is place of 8 in 987?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbmJowa1vvDBCRv0D" : {
        "Answer" : "612",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:51:41",
        "Option1" : "621",
        "Option2" : "216",
        "Option3" : "612",
        "Option4" : "162",
        "Question" : "Write in number, six hundred and twelve.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbwWBMzjo5Fv-IGul" : {
        "Answer" : "1 000",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:52:23",
        "Option1" : "1 000",
        "Option2" : "10",
        "Option3" : "100",
        "Option4" : "101",
        "Question" : "What comes, 900 + 100 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnc3sVcM2uadgxOMLV" : {
        "Answer" : "909",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:52:57",
        "Option1" : "990",
        "Option2" : "090",
        "Option3" : "900",
        "Option4" : "909",
        "Question" : "Nine hundred and nine. Write in number.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncKF1Qx_n6KXgHim0" : {
        "Answer" : "731",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:54:4",
        "Option1" : "731",
        "Option2" : "711",
        "Option3" : "730",
        "Option4" : "7 301",
        "Question" : "Seven hundred and thirty-one in number. ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncTbAisaMOG2PGIm5" : {
        "Answer" : "ones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:54:43",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "thousands",
        "Option4" : "hundreds",
        "Question" : "Place of 2 in 682.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncc37aIcSYDL5km6e" : {
        "Answer" : "hundreds",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:55:22",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "In 450, the place of 4 is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnct4lRg6xYSmESLaG" : {
        "Answer" : "2 tens",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:56:31",
        "Option1" : "1 tens",
        "Option2" : "2 tens",
        "Option3" : "3 tens",
        "Option4" : "20 tens",
        "Question" : "20 ones make:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnd-WO5tAO_eNkNHx9" : {
        "Answer" : "300",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:57:2",
        "Option1" : "30",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "3 000",
        "Option4" : "300",
        "Question" : "If one large block = 100, then three large blocks make:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFndNTMAphFClip4IMa" : {
        "Answer" : "19 ones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:58:40",
        "Option1" : "9 ones",
        "Option2" : "19 ones",
        "Option3" : "91 ones",
        "Option4" : "90 ones",
        "Question" : "10 ones + 9 ones are equal to:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFndaosRYoiDzLgSHtg" : {
        "Answer" : "hundreds",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:59:39",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "thosands",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "tens",
        "Question" : "Place of 6 in 688:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFndlMu1RDo__OYCHaA" : {
        "Answer" : "7",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:0:22",
        "Option1" : "70",
        "Option2" : "700",
        "Option3" : "7",
        "Option4" : "7 000",
        "Question" : "If one tiny block = 1 , then 7 tiny blocks are equal to:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFndtyU68ExjiLWnZz5" : {
        "Answer" : "111",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:0:57",
        "Option1" : "10011",
        "Option2" : "111",
        "Option3" : "11",
        "Option4" : "101",
        "Question" : "One hundred and eleven in number:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFne9ORhhsLgan81v2O" : {
        "Answer" : "one thousand",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:2:4",
        "Option1" : "one hundred",
        "Option2" : "ten thousand",
        "Option3" : "one thousand",
        "Option4" : "ten ones",
        "Question" : "Write 1000 in words.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFneQJi-wy222sPlIqC" : {
        "Answer" : "tens",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:3:14",
        "Option1" : "tens",
        "Option2" : "housands",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "ones",
        "Question" : "Place of 4 in 142:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFneZt3e071TwTQlhri" : {
        "Answer" : "685",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:3:53",
        "Option1" : "658",
        "Option2" : "586",
        "Option3" : "685",
        "Option4" : "568",
        "Question" : "Write 6 hundreds 8 tens 5 ones in number.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnemGGGtBv4PR6K8Uw" : {
        "Answer" : "twenty ones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:4:48",
        "Option1" : "twelve ones",
        "Option2" : "twenty ones",
        "Option3" : "thirteen ones",
        "Option4" : "ten ones",
        "Question" : "Nine ones + eleven ones are equal to:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnetGPCP4kE6T2hub-" : {
        "Answer" : "505",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:5:16",
        "Option1" : "550",
        "Option2" : "50",
        "Option3" : "050",
        "Option4" : "505",
        "Question" : "Write five hundred and five in numbers",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnf-2RaTkbulIm0YgZ" : {
        "Answer" : "1 000",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:5:44",
        "Option1" : "010",
        "Option2" : "1 000",
        "Option3" : "10",
        "Option4" : "100",
        "Question" : "100 + 200 + 300 + 400 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnfAyJH4Aoo65P5c1J" : {
        "Answer" : "520",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:6:33",
        "Option1" : "520",
        "Option2" : "250",
        "Option3" : "502",
        "Option4" : "205",
        "Question" : "Write the number having 5 hundreds 2 tens 0 ones",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnfLLgmmvZS67l8lhI" : {
        "Answer" : "hundreds",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:7:15",
        "Option1" : "tens",
        "Option2" : "hundreds",
        "Option3" : "ones",
        "Option4" : "none of tese",
        "Question" : "What is place of 5 in 587?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnfVnuQX0_3PbbYiuo" : {
        "Answer" : "423",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:7:58",
        "Option1" : "423",
        "Option2" : "432",
        "Option3" : "342",
        "Option4" : "324",
        "Question" : "Write in number, four hundred and twenty-three.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnfdOEzJlHxGVyneV0" : {
        "Answer" : "700",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:8:33",
        "Option1" : "600",
        "Option2" : "700",
        "Option3" : "300",
        "Option4" : "100",
        "Question" : "What comes, 200 + 500 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnflzow7Onc_CFCWWz" : {
        "Answer" : "106",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:9:9",
        "Option1" : "160",
        "Option2" : "106",
        "Option3" : "601",
        "Option4" : "610",
        "Question" : "One hundred and six. Write in number.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Science" : {
      "-MFzwyywb87Rik1aCZeG" : {
        "Answer" : "Microscope",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:19:45",
        "Option1" : "Microscope",
        "Option2" : "Light",
        "Option3" : "Moon",
        "Option4" : "Candle",
        "Question" : ".......is used to study things that cannot be seen by the human eye.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzxA_vcl_mm9uqEjJI" : {
        "Answer" : "Brain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:20:37",
        "Option1" : "Eye",
        "Option2" : "Brain",
        "Option3" : "Eye lid",
        "Option4" : "Eye lashes",
        "Question" : "....... turn the image the right way around.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzxOk0wS69GSpvBu3d" : {
        "Answer" : "Eye lashes",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:21:35",
        "Option1" : "Eye lashes",
        "Option2" : "Eye lid ",
        "Option3" : "Eye ball",
        "Option4" : "Retina",
        "Question" : "......... trap dust and other tiny particles.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzxdhxhY2VpAVJblPd" : {
        "Answer" : "Living things",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:22:40",
        "Option1" : "Animals",
        "Option2" : "Plants",
        "Option3" : "Living things",
        "Option4" : "Non living things",
        "Question" : "All....... has a life cycle.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzxr3pFFFx3wjEEBTp" : {
        "Answer" : "Queen",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:23:35",
        "Option1" : "Queen",
        "Option2" : "Worker",
        "Option3" : "Drone",
        "Option4" : "Larva",
        "Question" : "......bee lays eggs.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzy-vl7C9nyIg0kYZs" : {
        "Answer" : "Sweet",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:24:16",
        "Option1" : "Sour",
        "Option2" : "Bitter",
        "Option3" : "Sweet",
        "Option4" : "Salty",
        "Question" : "The tip of the tongue tastes......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzyBubZg32Bf8BLztj" : {
        "Answer" : "Worker",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:25:5",
        "Option1" : "Queen ",
        "Option2" : "Worker",
        "Option3" : "Drone",
        "Option4" : "Pupa",
        "Question" : ".........bee feed hatched larva.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzyXVg5AE2iySiYmcs" : {
        "Answer" : "Eyes",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:26:33",
        "Option1" : "Eyes",
        "Option2" : "Ear",
        "Option3" : "Skin",
        "Option4" : "Nose",
        "Question" : "...... are the part of your body that enable you to see the world around you.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzykLS-0ybgeId5r9Q" : {
        "Answer" : "Ear",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:27:30",
        "Option1" : "Nose ",
        "Option2" : "Ear",
        "Option3" : "Tongue",
        "Option4" : "Eyes",
        "Question" : "The three smallest bonesin the human body are in.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzysXXI2cJtprPJVPq" : {
        "Answer" : "Three",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:28:3",
        "Option1" : "Three",
        "Option2" : "Five",
        "Option3" : "Ten",
        "Option4" : "Four",
        "Question" : "Human ear has..... sections",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzz1Y87GmPSzs5sYz_" : {
        "Answer" : "Three",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:28:44",
        "Option1" : "Three",
        "Option2" : "Nine",
        "Option3" : "One ",
        "Option4" : "Two",
        "Question" : "The nose performs ........ functions.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzzJhd8JdKqdPzaHjF" : {
        "Answer" : "Upsidedown",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:29:59",
        "Option1" : "Straight",
        "Option2" : "Upsidedown",
        "Option3" : "Tilt",
        "Option4" : "Blurry ",
        "Question" : "An image look like.......when your eyes first see it.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzza0BufQoWqgl0pAi" : {
        "Answer" : "Life cycle ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:31:10",
        "Option1" : "Life cycle ",
        "Option2" : "Zoology",
        "Option3" : "Botany ",
        "Option4" : "Nutrients",
        "Question" : "........ is all the changes that an animal goes through from birth to death.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG--EJlKw3uBOB7NYZH" : {
        "Answer" : "Colour",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:33:59",
        "Option1" : "Colour",
        "Option2" : "Name",
        "Option3" : "Family ",
        "Option4" : "Food",
        "Question" : "Some animal change their..... as they grow older.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG--YyznBtHlAFkP8V6" : {
        "Answer" : "Colour",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:35:23",
        "Option1" : "Food",
        "Option2" : "Brain",
        "Option3" : "Name",
        "Option4" : "Colour",
        "Question" : "A butterfly changes....... as it grows.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG--kQKBSsmuvXiaeZO" : {
        "Answer" : "Worker bee",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:36:15",
        "Option1" : "Lion ",
        "Option2" : "Worker bee",
        "Option3" : "Butterfly",
        "Option4" : "Ants",
        "Question" : "....... seals the top of honey bee cells.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG--yHrfbFNacWk2GNL" : {
        "Answer" : "Four",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:37:11",
        "Option1" : "Three ",
        "Option2" : "Four",
        "Option3" : "Ten",
        "Option4" : "Five",
        "Question" : "In the life cycle of a honey bee there are........ stages.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG-0DyngaZYV3m_y6J9" : {
        "Answer" : "Three",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:38:19",
        "Option1" : "Three",
        "Option2" : "Four",
        "Option3" : "Five",
        "Option4" : "Seven",
        "Question" : "There are...... types of honey bee.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG-0OTGEZWLF3pB50De" : {
        "Answer" : "Male",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:39:2",
        "Option1" : "Female",
        "Option2" : "Male",
        "Option3" : "Fish",
        "Option4" : "Baby",
        "Question" : "Drones are........ bee.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG-0Z-zjHzaNn3pq0Ry" : {
        "Answer" : "Honey comb",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:39:46",
        "Option1" : "Honey comb",
        "Option2" : "Tree",
        "Option3" : "Flower",
        "Option4" : "House ",
        "Question" : "They eggs are laid in.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC7Am8XpJ76PwbA6di" : {
        "Answer" : "Lion",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 9:43:45",
        "Option1" : "Lion",
        "Option2" : "Tiger",
        "Option3" : "Hen",
        "Option4" : "Dog",
        "Question" : "The cub has grown into a......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC7bXyUTgbsA8_CyVP" : {
        "Answer" : "Ear",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 9:45:39",
        "Option1" : "Nose ",
        "Option2" : "Ear",
        "Option3" : "Eyes",
        "Option4" : "Brain",
        "Question" : "Hammer is present in.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC7vY_drD4efVr55a_" : {
        "Answer" : "Back",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 9:47:1",
        "Option1" : "Back",
        "Option2" : "Tip",
        "Option3" : "Edges",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "You taste bitter by the ......of your tongue.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC8QKyxRuFPFJi99hV" : {
        "Answer" : "Chick ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 9:49:11",
        "Option1" : "Chick ",
        "Option2" : "Cub ",
        "Option3" : "Rabbit ",
        "Option4" : "Puppy",
        "Question" : "A....... changes colour as it grows into a hen",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC93ErvFNnK8E1uZ_n" : {
        "Answer" : "Skin ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 9:51:58",
        "Option1" : "Skin ",
        "Option2" : "Hands",
        "Option3" : "Nose",
        "Option4" : "Ear",
        "Question" : ".......holds everything else inside your body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Social Studies" : {
      "-MFjYylOjOyEOLfeT343" : {
        "Answer" : "Education ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 15:56:35",
        "Option1" : "Education ",
        "Option2" : "Things",
        "Option3" : "Facilities ",
        "Option4" : "Rest",
        "Question" : "5- Every child has the right to ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjZdxAw3jb8riyxGbR" : {
        "Answer" : "Justly",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 15:59:32",
        "Option1" : "Unjustly ",
        "Option2" : "Badly",
        "Option3" : "Justly",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "6- Every child has the right to be treated ____ in a court of law.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFj_CZFNcCr78H7Phj_" : {
        "Answer" : "Food, Clothes, Shelter ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:1:58",
        "Option1" : "Food, Clothes, Shelter ",
        "Option2" : "Bag, Perfume, Jackets",
        "Option3" : "Games, Cartoons, Movies",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "7- Basic human rights are ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFj_dG56NsIynC-SN9j" : {
        "Answer" : "Education ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:3:51",
        "Option1" : "Degree",
        "Option2" : "Result",
        "Option3" : "Education ",
        "Option4" : "Class",
        "Question" : "8- ___ is also the basic human right.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjbHVpkO9igLLNz6qc" : {
        "Answer" : "Clean water and fresh food",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:11:2",
        "Option1" : "Dirty water and stale food",
        "Option2" : "Clean water and fresh food",
        "Option3" : "Clean water and rotten food",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "11- Have access to____ .",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjbd7U26GyGHX32DNk" : {
        "Answer" : "Have special health care ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:12:35",
        "Option1" : "Have less health care",
        "Option2" : "Have much health care ",
        "Option3" : "Have special health care ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "12-In old age____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjcSoBeAgAWjC--eUf" : {
        "Answer" : "Branded clothes ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:16:11",
        "Option1" : "Branded clothes ",
        "Option2" : "Cheap clothes ",
        "Option3" : "Good clothes ",
        "Option4" : "Neat clothes ",
        "Question" : "13- Don't waste money on___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjcs92fW4CjxeUiE2e" : {
        "Answer" : "Who can't afford to learn ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:17:59",
        "Option1" : "Who can afford to learn ",
        "Option2" : "Who can't afford to learn ",
        "Option3" : "A, B both",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "14- Spend your knowledge to___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjeYlfLbnzIJ1O_Sqz" : {
        "Answer" : "Stay updated about poverty ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:25:19",
        "Option1" : "Stay updated about crime",
        "Option2" : "Stay updated about poverty ",
        "Option3" : "Stay updated about science ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "16- Through newspaper and T.V___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjf9D74DBD0mwc3k6B" : {
        "Answer" : "3rd",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:27:57",
        "Option1" : "3rd",
        "Option2" : "4th",
        "Option3" : "5th",
        "Option4" : "2nd",
        "Question" : "17- From the Sun,Earth is the ____ most distant planet.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjfawNaoWekaca7-s4" : {
        "Answer" : "365",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:29:54",
        "Option1" : "363",
        "Option2" : "364",
        "Option3" : "365",
        "Option4" : "360",
        "Question" : "18- The Earth complete a cycle around the Sun in ____ days.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjfsPrPogFD8EzNR7B" : {
        "Answer" : "Land ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:31:6",
        "Option1" : "Land ",
        "Option2" : "Ocean ",
        "Option3" : "Earth",
        "Option4" : "Sun",
        "Question" : "19- ____ is made of continental crust.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjgEY5oGIWuBEJ6mco" : {
        "Answer" : "Crust",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:32:41",
        "Option1" : "Core",
        "Option2" : "Mantle",
        "Option3" : "Crust",
        "Option4" : "Water",
        "Question" : "20- ___ is the thinnest layer of Earth.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjgqz8Q-wHEW8sbr85" : {
        "Answer" : "8km, 70km",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:35:22",
        "Option1" : "7km, 70km",
        "Option2" : "8km, 70km",
        "Option3" : "6km, 70km",
        "Option4" : "5km,70km",
        "Question" : "21- Continental crust is ___ to ___ thick.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjh9sDqT7QLY2z6wo_" : {
        "Answer" : "Oceanic ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:36:44",
        "Option1" : "Oceanic ",
        "Option2" : "Earth ",
        "Option3" : "Sun",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "22- ___ crust is about 8km thick.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjhYp1jwecsmacc4EW" : {
        "Answer" : "Magma",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:38:26",
        "Option1" : "Molten ",
        "Option2" : "Lava",
        "Option3" : "Magma",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "23- Mantle is made up of hot molten rock called____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFjhwfL7J6wGoLc3NmF" : {
        "Answer" : "Core",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:40:8",
        "Option1" : "Core",
        "Option2" : "Crust",
        "Option3" : "Mantle ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "24- ___ is the inner most layer of Earth.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFji9ry252bAO9MD2vJ" : {
        "Answer" : "3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 16:41:6",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "5",
        "Option4" : "2",
        "Question" : "25- Our Earth has ___ layers.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbHDomxOWpdG0q6KFI" : {
        "Answer" : "Country ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:37:45",
        "Option1" : "City",
        "Option2" : "Country ",
        "Option3" : "Nation",
        "Option4" : "1,2 both ",
        "Question" : "Every child has the right to be a member of a ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgA_ulZ4Ad4vUOelDI" : {
        "Answer" : "Healthy way, Love",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:26:51",
        "Option1" : "Healthy way, Love",
        "Option2" : "Poor way, Hate",
        "Option3" : "Healthy way, Poor",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Every child has the right to grow in a ___ with dignity and ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgAq-jyZAQt71HHsGr" : {
        "Answer" : "Help",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:27:57",
        "Option1" : "Security ",
        "Option2" : "Shelter",
        "Option3" : "Help",
        "Option4" : "Power",
        "Question" : "Every child has the right to get ___ if needed. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgB8qcWPiWbIWwXg0a" : {
        "Answer" : "Parents ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:29:18",
        "Option1" : "Siblings ",
        "Option2" : "Relatives ",
        "Option3" : "Parents ",
        "Option4" : "Neighbour",
        "Question" : "Every child has the right to live with ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgBVEWQhp54RBSUAYz" : {
        "Answer" : "Get treated by a doctor ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:30:50",
        "Option1" : "Get treated by a doctor ",
        "Option2" : "Get treated by a farmer ",
        "Option3" : "Get treated by a engineer ",
        "Option4" : "Get treated by a plumber ",
        "Question" : "During illness.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgBia8BekjzhsmYakm" : {
        "Answer" : "A pollution free environment ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:31:49",
        "Option1" : "A polluted environment ",
        "Option2" : "A pollution free environment ",
        "Option3" : "A bad environment ",
        "Option4" : "An unclean environment ",
        "Question" : "Breath in.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgC0st4MpFyxz0ZjbJ" : {
        "Answer" : "In need of help",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:33:8",
        "Option1" : "In need of branded clothes ",
        "Option2" : "In need of help",
        "Option3" : "In need of luxury cars ",
        "Option4" : "In need of money ",
        "Question" : "Reach out to those.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Urdu" : {
      "-MGCPBAixhK9fu3QUAfB" : {
        "Answer" : "خضرت محمدﷺ ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:2:24",
        "Option1" : "خضرت محمدﷺ ",
        "Option2" : "خضرت ابراہیمؑ",
        "Option3" : "خضرت موسیٰ",
        "Option4" : "خضرت یوسفؑ",
        "Question" : "    پھٹے کپڑوں کو خود ہی پیوند  لگاتے۔",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCQ9WrqGzHjY3LWdLO" : {
        "Answer" : "محنت کرنے والوں کو",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:6:40",
        "Option1" : "صبر کرنے والوں کو",
        "Option2" : "محنت کرنے والوں کو",
        "Option3" : "دوسروں کی مدد کرنے والوں کو",
        "Option4" : "معاف کرنے والوں کو",
        "Question" : " خضرت محمدﷺ نے کس انسان کو اللہ کا \n                   دوست کہا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCR0Apmjtyn2kpK6sg" : {
        "Answer" : "کہانی سننے کی ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:10:23",
        "Option1" : "کہانی سننے کی ",
        "Option2" : "باہر جانے کی",
        "Option3" : "سکول جانے کی",
        "Option4" : "کھانا کھانے کی",
        "Question" : "  بچے دادی جان سے کس بات کی ضد کر \n                        رہے تھے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCSOzXpZ8jxb5OFEKG" : {
        "Answer" : "تا کہ دل لگا کے پڑھ سکیں ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:16:27",
        "Option1" : "بھوک جلدی نہ لگے",
        "Option2" : "بیمار نہ ہو جائیں",
        "Option3" : "تا کہ دل لگا کے پڑھ سکیں ",
        "Option4" : "تا کہ کھیل سکیں",
        "Question" : "  اچھی طرح ناشتہ کرنا کیوں ضروری ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCjRJ4S9kvIYxfuhMM" : {
        "Answer" : "کیونکہ وہ کام میں مدد کرتی ہے ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:35:15",
        "Option1" : "کیونکہ وہ کام میں مدد کرتی ہے ",
        "Option2" : "کیونکہ وہ جلدی اٹھتی ہے ",
        "Option3" : "کیونکہ وہ سچ بولتی ہے ",
        "Option4" : "کیونکہ وہ جھوٹ بولتی ہے",
        "Question" : " فاطمہ کی کس بات سے اندازہ ہوتا ہے کے \n   وہ اپنی امی کا بہت خیال رکھتی ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCk2XAlJGCxMLpbiKm" : {
        "Answer" : "وہ فاقے کا مارا تھا",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:37:56",
        "Option1" : "وہ فاقے کا مارا تھا",
        "Option2" : "وہ گوشت کلیجی کھاتا تھا ",
        "Option3" : "اسے سردی لگ گئی تھی",
        "Option4" : "اسے گرمی لگ گئی تھی",
        "Question" : "            گڈو کا کتا کیوں مر گیا؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCkqAEw6E1-cDqJG7q" : {
        "Answer" : "اس کے سر کو گرم مسالہ چڑھ گیا تھا",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:41:24",
        "Option1" : "اس کے سر کو گرم مسالہ چڑھ گیا تھا",
        "Option2" : "اس نے دال کھا لی تھی",
        "Option3" : "اس نے دودھ کا پیالا پی لیا تھا ",
        "Option4" : "اسے تاپ ہو گیا تھا",
        "Question" : " رانی کی بلی کی مرنے کی وجہ کیا تھی؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCl_c4pfA9MIAngb-X" : {
        "Answer" : "جنوبی ایشیا اور افریقہ میں ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:44:38",
        "Option1" : "جنوب پنجاب میں",
        "Option2" : "پہاڑوں میں",
        "Option3" : "جنوبی ایشیا اور افریقہ میں ",
        "Option4" : "ریگستان میں",
        "Question" : "  ہاتھی عام طور پر کن علاقوں میں پاۓ \n                      جاتے ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCm8pEHHvLyhZwkNh7" : {
        "Answer" : "13 فٹ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:47:6",
        "Option1" : "13 فٹ",
        "Option2" : "5 فٹ",
        "Option3" : "7فٹ",
        "Option4" : "9 فٹ",
        "Question" : "        ہاتھی کا قد کتنا اونچا ہوتا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCn-psFagnK4ul1MBu" : {
        "Answer" : "انکے لمبے دانتوں کی وجہ سے",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:50:51",
        "Option1" : "وہ دوسرے جانوروں کا شکار کرتے ہیں",
        "Option2" : "انکے لمبے دانتوں کی وجہ سے",
        "Option3" : "وہ درحتوں کو نقصان پہنچاتے ہیں",
        "Option4" : "وہ اب سواری کے کام نہیں آتے",
        "Question" : "  شکاری ہاتھیوں کا شکار کیوں کرتے ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCnXAhDb2ZuONINsmw" : {
        "Answer" : "لگڑبھگے اور چیتے",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:53:8",
        "Option1" : "لگڑبھگے اور چیتے",
        "Option2" : "مگرمچھ ",
        "Option3" : "ہرن ",
        "Option4" : "سمندری گھوڑے",
        "Question" : " کونسے جانور ہاتھی کے بچوں کو کھا جاتے \n                          ہیں؟ ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCnutmTETduIDZ9l3D" : {
        "Answer" : "7 ہزار",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:54:49",
        "Option1" : "7 ہزار",
        "Option2" : "15 ہزار",
        "Option3" : "9 ہزار",
        "Option4" : "6 ہزار",
        "Question" : "     ہاتھی کا وزن کتنے کلوگرام ہوتا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCoN7uk9kn3G5rzncL" : {
        "Answer" : "کان ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:56:49",
        "Option1" : "کان ",
        "Option2" : "دانت",
        "Option3" : "آنکھیں",
        "Option4" : "ٹانگیں",
        "Question" : "     ہاتھی کے _______ بڑے ہوتے ہیں۔",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCosWFs82suIgWYSbC" : {
        "Answer" : "سننے کی",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:59:2",
        "Option1" : "دیکھنے کی",
        "Option2" : "سننے کی",
        "Option3" : "دوڑنے کی",
        "Option4" : "شکار کرنے کی",
        "Question" : " ہاتھی میں کس چیز کی صلاحیت بہت تیز \n                       ہوتی ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCpaww6GTnnH5cXmvJ" : {
        "Answer" : "پانی کی",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:2:12",
        "Option1" : "کھانے کی",
        "Option2" : "شکار کی",
        "Option3" : "پانی کی",
        "Option4" : "گھڑے کی",
        "Question" : "     کہانی میں کوا کس تلاش میں تھا؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCqBJfE6OcCkKuoJO7" : {
        "Answer" : "کوشش سے کامیابی ملتی ہے",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:4:45",
        "Option1" : "لالچ بری بلا ہے",
        "Option2" : "کوشش سے کامیابی ملتی ہے",
        "Option3" : "اتفاق میں برقت ہے",
        "Option4" : "نیکی کر دریا میں ڈال",
        "Question" : "       کہانی پیاسا کوا کا نتیجہ کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCqd3JnqwZqF4rae5n" : {
        "Answer" : "انگور",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:6:43",
        "Option1" : "انگور",
        "Option2" : "سیب",
        "Option3" : "آم",
        "Option4" : "انار",
        "Question" : " کہانی میں لومڑی کیا توڑنے کی کوشش کر \n                       رہی تھی؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCr9P__OSTFWQdUwTh" : {
        "Answer" : "انگور کھٹے ہیں",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:8:59",
        "Option1" : "انگور میٹھے ہیں",
        "Option2" : "انگور کھٹے ہیں",
        "Option3" : "انگور کڑوے ہیں",
        "Option4" : "انگور اونچے ہیں",
        "Question" : "        لومڑی جاتے ہوۓ کیا کہنے لگی؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCrYbeTl4qezAUhs_9" : {
        "Answer" : "واحد",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:10:44",
        "Option1" : "مزکر",
        "Option2" : "مونث",
        "Option3" : "متضاد ",
        "Option4" : "واحد",
        "Question" : "    ایک شخص یا چیز کو کیا کہتے ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCrypLOXRjnpwzO5L_" : {
        "Answer" : "زبانیں",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:12:34",
        "Option1" : "زبانیں",
        "Option2" : "زبانی",
        "Option3" : "زبانے",
        "Option4" : "کوئی نہیں ",
        "Question" : "              زبان کی جمع  کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCsPlsfWSxIG6TLhP2" : {
        "Answer" : "مرغیاں",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:14:35",
        "Option1" : "مرغے ",
        "Option2" : "مرغیاں",
        "Option3" : "مرغا",
        "Option4" : "کوئی نہیں ",
        "Question" : "                 مرغی کی جمع ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCsiIOeDZzvroOXSoR" : {
        "Answer" : "کاموں",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:15:48",
        "Option1" : "کامی ",
        "Option2" : "کاموں",
        "Option3" : "کامے",
        "Option4" : "قوم",
        "Question" : "               کام کی جمع کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCt7uL2fWIX4KWKVCX" : {
        "Answer" : "گھونسلے ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 13:17:37",
        "Option1" : "گھو نسلیاں ",
        "Option2" : "گھونسلے ",
        "Option3" : "گھونسلی",
        "Option4" : "گھاس",
        "Question" : "            گھونسلہ کی جمع کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaqn7zuncfGZjEN9mf" : {
        "Answer" : "پھول",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:37:54",
        "Option1" : "باغ",
        "Option2" : "چراغ",
        "Option3" : "پھول",
        "Option4" : "نور",
        "Question" : " فرمان ہے کہ بچے گلستان کے______ ہیں۔",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGarvs5NqHlc68L8aDD" : {
        "Answer" : "ماضی کا ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:42:52",
        "Option1" : "مستقبل کا ",
        "Option2" : "حال کا ",
        "Option3" : "ماضی کا ",
        "Option4" : "یا ان سب کا",
        "Question" : "               کہانی حصہ ہوتی ہے۔ ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      }
    }
  },
  "Class IV" : {
    "English" : {
      "-MFi5jOgqCYEksYpXDqd" : {
        "Answer" : "Pip",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:9:13",
        "Option1" : "Joe",
        "Option2" : "Miss Havisham ",
        "Option3" : "Pip",
        "Option4" : "Mrs. Joe",
        "Question" : "1-The central character of the novel \n(Great Expectations )is____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi6mJRoYYgcwI7iK39" : {
        "Answer" : "Husband ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:13:47",
        "Option1" : "Uncle ",
        "Option2" : "Brother ",
        "Option3" : "Husband ",
        "Option4" : "Nephew ",
        "Question" : "2-In novel \"Great Expectations\",Mr.Joe was the ____ of Pip's sister. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi8Wz6_Nhz1OgXr5rE" : {
        "Answer" : "Twenty ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:21:24",
        "Option1" : "Twenty ",
        "Option2" : "Thirty",
        "Option3" : "Ten",
        "Option4" : "Fifteen ",
        "Question" : "3-Pip's sister was ____ years senior to Pip.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi9AelnUb-KLLSd_iB" : {
        "Answer" : "Uncle Pumblechook ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:24:15",
        "Option1" : "Mr. Joe",
        "Option2" : "Pip",
        "Option3" : "Mr. Hubble",
        "Option4" : "Uncle Pumblechook ",
        "Question" : "4-____ brought two bottles of wine and a pie for the Pip's family. (Great Expectations )",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiA8Y8N4iIWzNX5KbS" : {
        "Answer" : "Prisoner",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:28:28",
        "Option1" : "Mrs. Hubble ",
        "Option2" : "Prisoner",
        "Option3" : "Mr. Joe",
        "Option4" : "Uncle Pumblechook  ",
        "Question" : "5-Pip gave the wine to the ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiAgMKGDSNpWajFaK5" : {
        "Answer" : "Coughing ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:30:51",
        "Option1" : "Laughing ",
        "Option2" : "Coughing ",
        "Option3" : "Sneezing ",
        "Option4" : "Smiling ",
        "Question" : "6-Uncle Pumblechook was ____ while taking brandy. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiBGtEAnq3bgV9GTZr" : {
        "Answer" : "Two hours",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:33:24",
        "Option1" : "A minute ",
        "Option2" : "Two hours",
        "Option3" : "10 minutes ",
        "Option4" : "Three hours",
        "Question" : "7-Mr. Joe completed his job in ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiCBiPacWsThbIVcTO" : {
        "Answer" : "Noisily ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:37:25",
        "Option1" : "Gently ",
        "Option2" : "Noisily ",
        "Option3" : "Calmly ",
        "Option4" : "Slowly ",
        "Question" : "8-Pip,prisoner and the young man were talking____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiCsDE5jpba-m3XKJ3" : {
        "Answer" : "Thankful",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:40:24",
        "Option1" : "Helpful",
        "Option2" : "Thank less ",
        "Option3" : "Thankful",
        "Option4" : "Powerful ",
        "Question" : "9-The meaning of \"Grateful\" is ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiDEU_Ifzzsr06vXaq" : {
        "Answer" : "Not good",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:41:59",
        "Option1" : "Not good",
        "Option2" : "Good",
        "Option3" : "Better",
        "Option4" : "Excellent ",
        "Question" : "10-The meaning of \"Unpleasant\" is___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiE8pDofX3DI7H7J0E" : {
        "Answer" : "Chris",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:45:58",
        "Option1" : "Duggan",
        "Option2" : "Tim",
        "Option3" : "Chris",
        "Option4" : "A, C both",
        "Question" : "11- Who was Danebridg's goal keeper?(Big Match)",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiEWxqK0OLCy9ERdUY" : {
        "Answer" : "Tim ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:47:37",
        "Option1" : "Tim ",
        "Option2" : "Chris",
        "Option3" : "Duggan",
        "Option4" : "Shenby",
        "Question" : "12- Who was Danebridg's captain?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiFMYxpxLu2g5sLfpf" : {
        "Answer" : "Shenby captain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:51:16",
        "Option1" : "Goal keeper",
        "Option2" : "Shenby captain",
        "Option3" : "Danebridg's captain",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "13- The penalty was taken by the ___.(Big Match)",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiFxd-gSKY99WeQiTq" : {
        "Answer" : "\"Big Match\"",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:53:52",
        "Option1" : "\"Cricket team\"",
        "Option2" : "\"Big Match\"",
        "Option3" : "\"Hockey Match\"",
        "Option4" : "A, C both",
        "Question" : "14- Choose the name of story in which two teams were playing match. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiH1rvNvYlN3xo25ug" : {
        "Answer" : "To happen suddenly",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:58:36",
        "Option1" : "To happen slowly ",
        "Option2" : "To happen rapidly ",
        "Option3" : "To happen suddenly",
        "Option4" : "To happen quickly ",
        "Question" : "15- The meaning of \"Strikes\" is ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiKi2VT0a_YYcQ3hVE" : {
        "Answer" : "Politely, Immediately, Carefully",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:14:39",
        "Option1" : "Politely, Immediately, Carefully",
        "Option2" : "Nephew, Sister, Brother",
        "Option3" : "Play, Catch, Jump",
        "Option4" : "Tall, Thick, Blunt",
        "Question" : "16- Choose the set of \"Adverb\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiLG9eyexHrRwI2toR" : {
        "Answer" : "Kitten",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:17:3",
        "Option1" : "Kitten",
        "Option2" : "Catch",
        "Option3" : "Slowly ",
        "Option4" : "Red",
        "Question" : "17- Identify \"Noun\" in given words. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiLe_aFTb278-Wss8a" : {
        "Answer" : "Polite",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:18:47",
        "Option1" : "Mare",
        "Option2" : "Polite",
        "Option3" : "Stitch ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "18- Identify \"Adjective\" in given words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiM97RuhWQa18lE2LD" : {
        "Answer" : "Little",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:20:56",
        "Option1" : "Little",
        "Option2" : "Jump",
        "Option3" : "Laugh",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "19- Choose the \"Adjective\" and fill the gape.\nThe ____ puppy.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiMeEkyFJieFq2o_0b" : {
        "Answer" : "Noun",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:23:8",
        "Option1" : "Adverb",
        "Option2" : "Verb",
        "Option3" : "Noun",
        "Option4" : "Adjective",
        "Question" : "20- ____ is a naming word.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiNUbJN0jaQNgGpfaH" : {
        "Answer" : "Declarative sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:26:46",
        "Option1" : "Declarative sentence",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Option3" : "Imperative sentence ",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Question" : "21- Identify given sentence.\nOceans are very deep.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiOB75xC8hVLhSnkWi" : {
        "Answer" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:29:49",
        "Option1" : "Declarative sentence",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Option3" : "Imperative sentence",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Question" : "22- Do you like this poem?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiOrjmwyWdkHbgORjc" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:32:47",
        "Option1" : "Declarative sentence",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Option3" : "Imperative sentence",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Question" : "23- Identify given sentence \nI wish tomorrow is a holiday.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiPYnFmsx0TLA-QjNC" : {
        "Answer" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:35:48",
        "Option1" : "Declarative sentence ",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Option3" : "Imperative sentence",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Question" : "24-Oh no!We have boarded the wrong train.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiQpgg64nAQDZxkpLL" : {
        "Answer" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:41:23",
        "Option1" : "Declarative sentence ",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative sentence",
        "Option3" : "Imperative sentence ",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory sentence",
        "Question" : "25- Are you fond of animals?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "ICT" : {
      "-MGHB57kSfL8NxTT0oXW" : {
        "Answer" : "Hardware",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:18:56",
        "Option1" : "Hardware",
        "Option2" : "Software",
        "Option3" : "Firmware",
        "Option4" : "Systemware",
        "Question" : "The physical parts of the computer that we can see and touch are called________.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHBUygApaBAONsVaSI" : {
        "Answer" : "Network card",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:20:42",
        "Option1" : "Hard disk",
        "Option2" : "Network card",
        "Option3" : "Web cam",
        "Option4" : "ROM",
        "Question" : "It is a communication device______.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHBraGdYnXD_qS6cIu" : {
        "Answer" : "Motherboard",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:22:18",
        "Option1" : "Keyboard",
        "Option2" : "Modem",
        "Option3" : "Motherboard",
        "Option4" : "Mouse",
        "Question" : "All the computer components are plugged or connected with it _______.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHCC0m50A104Maq-pi" : {
        "Answer" : "AU",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:23:46",
        "Option1" : "LU",
        "Option2" : "CU",
        "Option3" : "AU",
        "Option4" : "ALU",
        "Question" : "All mathematical problems are solved in this potion of the processor______.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHCjTJLdAE6muYmO9M" : {
        "Answer" : "RAM",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:26:7",
        "Option1" : "ROM",
        "Option2" : "Harddisk",
        "Option3" : "RAM",
        "Option4" : "Modem",
        "Question" : "Its holds data temporarily before and after processing _____.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHKtHFVhGUC_VSnKkO" : {
        "Answer" : "Software",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:1:45",
        "Option1" : "Hardware",
        "Option2" : "Software",
        "Option3" : "Beware",
        "Option4" : "Firmware",
        "Question" : "The set of instructions that are given to a Computer,called-------",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHNqXiWrPYhavHI6yw" : {
        "Answer" : "System software",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:14:40",
        "Option1" : "Hardware",
        "Option2" : "Application software",
        "Option3" : "System software",
        "Option4" : "Operating system",
        "Question" : "It controls and directs the operation of a computer......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHQiEXazlTqsQrDkYA" : {
        "Answer" : "Operating system",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:27:12",
        "Option1" : "Operating system",
        "Option2" : "Application software",
        "Option3" : "Utilities",
        "Option4" : "Rom",
        "Question" : "A computer is useless with out a (n)....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHV5iKC0Yr52fZCWCC" : {
        "Answer" : "Window",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:46:21",
        "Option1" : "Window",
        "Option2" : "Linux",
        "Option3" : "Macos",
        "Option4" : "Device",
        "Question" : "It is the most widely used opoperating system....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHWBCO1LNm48xC0sNe" : {
        "Answer" : "Output operation",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:51:6",
        "Option1" : "Input operation",
        "Option2" : "Output operation",
        "Option3" : "Storage operation",
        "Option4" : "Application operation",
        "Question" : "In this operation a computer produce results......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH_c0m0KMDvqZdaYZv" : {
        "Answer" : "Instrucation",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:10:28",
        "Option1" : "Instrucation",
        "Option2" : "Task",
        "Option3" : "Command",
        "Option4" : "Control",
        "Question" : "A software is a set of ....tha are given to a computer......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHaZUo0q8RoLekv4ZZ" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:14:36",
        "Option1" : "2",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "5",
        "Option4" : "4",
        "Question" : "There are----main type of  software",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHbLyxk9pAUjWiBMxB" : {
        "Answer" : "Data",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:18:3",
        "Option1" : "Data",
        "Option2" : "Files",
        "Option3" : "Control",
        "Option4" : "Modem",
        "Question" : "The input operation a computer accept----_",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHc8B6_LGTnpFWssFJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Application",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:21:29",
        "Option1" : "Stirages",
        "Option2" : "Processing",
        "Option3" : "Application",
        "Option4" : "Operating",
        "Question" : "Computer games are types of----software.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHd01kUZGlS6AaRNMN" : {
        "Answer" : "Keyboard",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:25:17",
        "Option1" : "Keyboard",
        "Option2" : "Mouse",
        "Option3" : "Cds",
        "Option4" : "Cpu",
        "Question" : "Computer received numbers and instruction from the......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHdzijwaDEDouk45bu" : {
        "Answer" : "Flas  Drive",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:29:34",
        "Option1" : "Flas  Drive",
        "Option2" : "Monitor",
        "Option3" : "Cpu",
        "Option4" : "DVD",
        "Question" : "Computer shows result on the.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHfhVY-B6u80xrsVAa" : {
        "Answer" : "Soul",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:37:4",
        "Option1" : "Room",
        "Option2" : "Air",
        "Option3" : "Soul",
        "Option4" : "Life",
        "Question" : "An operating system is the just like.....of a computer.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHgLNh5VIlZaC9anEr" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:39:51",
        "Option1" : "1",
        "Option2" : "4",
        "Option3" : "2",
        "Option4" : "5",
        "Question" : "There are .....types of Modem.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHhCo6ZhXoyzgXgMo6" : {
        "Answer" : "Small",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:43:38",
        "Option1" : "Small",
        "Option2" : "Main",
        "Option3" : "Big",
        "Option4" : "Important",
        "Question" : "A Net Work Card is a..,..circuit board.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHi1Gd9Qx_teqjNUNW" : {
        "Answer" : "Rom",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:47:13",
        "Option1" : "Ram",
        "Option2" : "Rom",
        "Option3" : "Network card",
        "Option4" : "Modem",
        "Question" : ".....is fixed in the Mother board.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHisZcES3AfiJJRDvQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Ram",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:50:55",
        "Option1" : "Ram",
        "Option2" : "Rom",
        "Option3" : "Memory",
        "Option4" : "Control unit",
        "Question" : "......is also known as  volatile memory.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHjH9FBtAdCGnxU6vo" : {
        "Answer" : "Rom",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:52:40",
        "Option1" : "Rom",
        "Option2" : "Network",
        "Option3" : "Ram",
        "Option4" : "Mother board",
        "Question" : "Random Access Memory means....,",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHknmbzcJXWUCkczJV" : {
        "Answer" : "All these",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 11:59:20",
        "Option1" : "Addition",
        "Option2" : "Multiplication",
        "Option3" : "All these",
        "Option4" : "Subtraction",
        "Question" : "ALU performs on.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHlbC1ssZUxWrQs_lp" : {
        "Answer" : "All these",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 12:2:51",
        "Option1" : "All these",
        "Option2" : "Keyboard",
        "Option3" : "Mointor",
        "Option4" : "Printer",
        "Question" : "Peripherals which are attached with ......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHwFLxdFp5pQBSrn2j" : {
        "Answer" : "AU",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 12:49:21",
        "Option1" : "AU",
        "Option2" : "LU",
        "Option3" : "CU",
        "Option4" : "ALu",
        "Question" : "All mathematical problem are solved in this portion of the processor",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Islamiyat" : {
      "-MG1bBQ_zJ72ld-LEyjS" : {
        "Answer" : "Parents/Non Muslims/Own Children",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 8:43:24",
        "Option1" : "Parents/Children.",
        "Option2" : "Parents/Non Muslims.",
        "Option3" : "Parents/Non Muslims/Own Children",
        "Option4" : "Any one",
        "Question" : "Zakat cannot be given to  one,s.",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1bod8R75ohimFYXnx" : {
        "Answer" : "06",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 8:46:9",
        "Option1" : "03",
        "Option2" : "02",
        "Option3" : "06",
        "Option4" : "04",
        "Question" : "Faith have____Articals.",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1cbeIPtzVx_wquxgs" : {
        "Answer" : "one time",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:46:24",
        "Option1" : "one time",
        "Option2" : "two time ",
        "Option3" : "three time",
        "Option4" : "four time",
        "Question" : "Zakat is to paid only______ in a year",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1dekArtzNL0PdDpLv" : {
        "Answer" : "poor people",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:53:20",
        "Option1" : "poor people",
        "Option2" : "rich people",
        "Option3" : "women",
        "Option4" : "old people",
        "Question" : "Zakat provide security to the_______",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1h7I8YEKPiXv2hWx5" : {
        "Answer" : "All Mighty Allah",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:9:20",
        "Option1" : "god",
        "Option2" : "People",
        "Option3" : "All Mighty Allah",
        "Option4" : "Fire",
        "Question" : "I believe in …\n\n",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1hzmtociQ2yN7uRJh" : {
        "Answer" : "Pillar",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:13:7",
        "Option1" : "Steps",
        "Option2" : "Pillar",
        "Option3" : "Style",
        "Option4" : "List",
        "Question" : "Zakat is one of the... Of Islam.",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1mNjzwUcQwJnU7O8M" : {
        "Answer" : "Iman-e-Mufassal",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:32:18",
        "Option1" : "Iman-e-Unity",
        "Option2" : "Iman-e-Islam",
        "Option3" : "Iman-e-Mufassal",
        "Option4" : "Iman-e-Bayaan",
        "Question" : "The faith belief are  stated in.....",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1nARBvhNvOsNAOK9e" : {
        "Answer" : "Makkah",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:35:46",
        "Option1" : "Makkah",
        "Option2" : "Madinah",
        "Option3" : "Abbssinia",
        "Option4" : "Bader",
        "Question" : "Zakat was made compulsory at....same time as Salat.",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCHWIsP41PFZvs4hPe" : {
        "Answer" : "Allah",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:28:54",
        "Option1" : "Allah",
        "Option2" : "god",
        "Option3" : "socity",
        "Option4" : "people",
        "Question" : "Unity or oneness of _________ is belief.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCNxx0spsGXh1MAhUh" : {
        "Answer" : "Wealth",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:57:4",
        "Option1" : "Wealth",
        "Option2" : "Lands",
        "Option3" : "Goods",
        "Option4" : "Sliver",
        "Question" : "Zakat is also prevents the accumulation of-----in a few hand.\nW",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCQR32PpFdOcvrOguj" : {
        "Answer" : "Hereafter",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:7:52",
        "Option1" : "Hereafter",
        "Option2" : "Old age",
        "Option3" : "In the world",
        "Option4" : "In childhood",
        "Question" : "Those who don't pay Zakat,they will get punished of the-----",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUxYgHEkPe70G6jsK" : {
        "Answer" : "Good/bad",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:27:38",
        "Option1" : "Good/bad",
        "Option2" : "Bad/worse",
        "Option3" : "Nice/good",
        "Option4" : "Good/fair",
        "Question" : "In His messengers,in the last Day and in the fact that every thing----or----is decided.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCW2b9HBr3h1Veguja" : {
        "Answer" : "Nisab",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:32:24",
        "Option1" : "Nisab",
        "Option2" : "Lesson",
        "Option3" : "Chapter",
        "Option4" : "Lecture",
        "Question" : "The Zakat rate  is called.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXOoHAwlSyQeFQ7ey" : {
        "Answer" : "All of these",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:38:17",
        "Option1" : "Jewerly",
        "Option2" : "Crops",
        "Option3" : "Gold",
        "Option4" : "All of these",
        "Question" : "Zakat is also paid in-----,and  trade goods.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC_IMYKGTqRxr_zFcu" : {
        "Answer" : "Newly musilm",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:50:58",
        "Option1" : "Newly musilm",
        "Option2" : "Non musilm",
        "Option3" : "All musilm",
        "Option4" : "Only women",
        "Question" : "Zakat is also paid for---musilm.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCat67UaUD8e-yYeYD" : {
        "Answer" : "Fundamental",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:57:54",
        "Option1" : "Fundamental",
        "Option2" : "Secondary",
        "Option3" : "Formal",
        "Option4" : "Compulsary",
        "Question" : "The beliefs which serves as the foundation of a religion.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCc1SnhtUz5lH8qSkM" : {
        "Answer" : "All of these",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:2:55",
        "Option1" : "Poor,needy",
        "Option2" : "Newly Muslims,slaves",
        "Option3" : "Travellers",
        "Option4" : "All of these",
        "Question" : "According to a verse of the Holy Quran,Zakat is to be paid to the____",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCd2pLJjmvgpT-uUCZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Worship",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:7:22",
        "Option1" : "Worship",
        "Option2" : "Warning",
        "Option3" : "Enjoyment",
        "Option4" : "Compulsory",
        "Question" : "Zakat is an act of ____ performed by giving away a portion of one's wealth for the benefit of the poor.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGGzyxveFDqP0yuiCaE" : {
        "Answer" : "Purify",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:26:1",
        "Option1" : "Clean",
        "Option2" : "Purify",
        "Option3" : "Washed",
        "Option4" : "Neat",
        "Question" : "The literal meaning of the word Zakat is to-----",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH-Ro9h2z_UZLn_ohb" : {
        "Answer" : "Salat",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:28:3",
        "Option1" : "Salat",
        "Option2" : "Fast",
        "Option3" : "Nouafil",
        "Option4" : "Hajj",
        "Question" : "Zakat is always mentioned with_-----",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH07cSevaImSvyFB-6" : {
        "Answer" : "Warning",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:31:3",
        "Option1" : "Requesest",
        "Option2" : "Command",
        "Option3" : "Order",
        "Option4" : "Warning",
        "Question" : "There are also many ----of the Holy Prophet who do not pay Zakat.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH0_U-2yqezdkBR-kc" : {
        "Answer" : "2.5%",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:33:1",
        "Option1" : "3.5%",
        "Option2" : "1.5%",
        "Option3" : "2.5%",
        "Option4" : "4.5%",
        "Question" : "Zakat is pay able at the rate of------.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH1PvIIEGXw41VM6Vo" : {
        "Answer" : "1st",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:36:40",
        "Option1" : "1st",
        "Option2" : "2econd",
        "Option3" : "3red",
        "Option4" : "6th",
        "Question" : "Zakat is ------principle of Islam is belifes in the oneness and unity of Allah.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH4SOx5ymU6KkO-TXN" : {
        "Answer" : "Master",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 8:49:56",
        "Option1" : "Master",
        "Option2" : "Brother",
        "Option3" : "Parents",
        "Option4" : "Children",
        "Question" : "Zakat is pay to slaves who have an agreement with their----to purchase their freedom.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH8aw56Ryehcmtf5J-" : {
        "Answer" : "9:60",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:8:4",
        "Option1" : "9:70",
        "Option2" : "9:60",
        "Option3" : "9:80",
        "Option4" : "9:50",
        "Question" : "According to a verse of the Holy Quran -----Zakat is to be paid to the asked people.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Math" : {
      "-MFnVTs5ZDric04rKusq" : {
        "Answer" : "thousands",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:19:47",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "The digit 5 is in the________ place in 15 218.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnVl9MmfHcLmXU2-ZU" : {
        "Answer" : "35 432",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:21:2",
        "Option1" : "35 423",
        "Option2" : "34 532",
        "Option3" : "35 432",
        "Option4" : "35 431",
        "Question" : "30 000 + 5 000 + 400 + 30 + 2 = ? ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnW2UyIrO-ClDpsF_b" : {
        "Answer" : "2 473",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:22:17",
        "Option1" : "2 473",
        "Option2" : "2 347",
        "Option3" : "2 734",
        "Option4" : "7 342",
        "Question" : "The digit 7 is in tens place in____.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnX_ONSOW2ww-0QnNL" : {
        "Answer" : "4 795",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:28:58",
        "Option1" : "5 974",
        "Option2" : "9 745",
        "Option3" : "7 495",
        "Option4" : "4 795",
        "Question" : "4 thousands + 7 hundreds + 9 tens + 5 ones = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnXiLiKm8cUJdpNNSX" : {
        "Answer" : "565",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:29:34",
        "Option1" : "565",
        "Option2" : "566",
        "Option3" : "655",
        "Option4" : "757",
        "Question" : "Complete the sequence, 555, ____,575.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnXui7MHGaDePCTDFg" : {
        "Answer" : "4 000",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:30:25",
        "Option1" : "40",
        "Option2" : "400",
        "Option3" : "4 000",
        "Option4" : "4",
        "Question" : "10 000 + _____ + 300 + 90 + 7 = 14 397",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnY48yamru7HdPXFOE" : {
        "Answer" : "3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:31:8",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "6",
        "Option4" : "9",
        "Question" : "What is the digit in the place of ten thousands in 938 674?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYM2o22FOTJ24ru3Z" : {
        "Answer" : "hundred thousands",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:32:21",
        "Option1" : "thousands",
        "Option2" : "hundreds",
        "Option3" : "hundred thousands",
        "Option4" : "tens",
        "Question" : "The digit 5 is in ______ place in 578 693.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYgt6Akv4APZ7dvGq" : {
        "Answer" : "3 723",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:33:51",
        "Option1" : "3 726",
        "Option2" : "3 720",
        "Option3" : "3 725",
        "Option4" : "3 723",
        "Question" : "Complete the sequence, 3 721, 3 722,_____,3 724.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYwrP0bl0k1QgZLhK" : {
        "Answer" : "8 102",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:34:56",
        "Option1" : "11 402",
        "Option2" : "8 102",
        "Option3" : "14 402",
        "Option4" : "none of these",
        "Question" : "What is 700 more than 7 402?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZ5GcRHZEbFHD1SZS" : {
        "Answer" : "ones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:35:35",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "thousands",
        "Option4" : "hundreds",
        "Question" : "In 86 513, the digit 3 is in the _________ place.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZHvwsulvkbKqDhZO" : {
        "Answer" : "greater than",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:36:27",
        "Option1" : "less than",
        "Option2" : "equal to",
        "Option3" : "greater than",
        "Option4" : "none of these",
        "Question" : "362 407 is _________ 325 704.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZZmK_yR1itpqCAnB" : {
        "Answer" : "800",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:37:40",
        "Option1" : "80",
        "Option2" : "8",
        "Option3" : "8 000",
        "Option4" : "800",
        "Question" : "24 800 = 20 000 + 4 000 + ______ + 00 + 0",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZjJrYK09kmQSDoq9" : {
        "Answer" : "hundreds",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:38:23",
        "Option1" : "hundreds",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "ones",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "The value of 2 in 364 275 is_________.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZuSlBqJokKN3cW8c" : {
        "Answer" : "10 111",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:39:8",
        "Option1" : "10 011",
        "Option2" : "1 101",
        "Option3" : "11 111",
        "Option4" : "10 111",
        "Question" : "10 000  + 100 + 10 + 1 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_3qPNr6Ja_SZ_c54" : {
        "Answer" : "9 999",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:39:51",
        "Option1" : "9 090",
        "Option2" : "9 099",
        "Option3" : "9 999",
        "Option4" : "9 000",
        "Question" : "9 000 + 900 + 90 + 9 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_FiXLd-zP0aEjRMa" : {
        "Answer" : "4 821",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:40:40",
        "Option1" : "4 821",
        "Option2" : "4 021",
        "Option3" : "4 820",
        "Option4" : "4 281",
        "Question" : "Four thousand, eight hundred and twenty-one.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_S72q0BE1Def1WpU" : {
        "Answer" : "7 234",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:41:30",
        "Option1" : "5 234",
        "Option2" : "7 234",
        "Option3" : "8 234",
        "Option4" : "7 324",
        "Question" : "1 000 more then 6 234.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_fBbYbWCbSBJMeCa" : {
        "Answer" : "60",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:42:28",
        "Option1" : "6",
        "Option2" : "06",
        "Option3" : "60",
        "Option4" : "600",
        "Question" : "4 000 + 300 + _________ + 9 = 4 369",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_qwOGX019cwWeczu" : {
        "Answer" : "5 763",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:43:16",
        "Option1" : "6 573",
        "Option2" : "7 563",
        "Option3" : "5 763",
        "Option4" : "5 636",
        "Question" : "100 less than 5 863.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFna0Z_0jasxvr-2MjS" : {
        "Answer" : "3 720",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:44:0",
        "Option1" : "3 702",
        "Option2" : "7 230",
        "Option3" : "3 720",
        "Option4" : "3 270",
        "Question" : "3 000 + 700 + 20 + 0 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnaKYfDZLsrG3ncBiU" : {
        "Answer" : "8 649",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:45:21",
        "Option1" : "8 694",
        "Option2" : "8 684",
        "Option3" : "8 649",
        "Option4" : "8 764",
        "Question" : "Eight thousand, six hundred and forty-nine.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnab7sozG-3gIfWkT3" : {
        "Answer" : "8 634",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:46:34",
        "Option1" : "7 534",
        "Option2" : "9 534",
        "Option3" : "8 634",
        "Option4" : "8 934",
        "Question" : "100 more then 8 534.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnauZ3jX0iDJ27VmTH" : {
        "Answer" : "90",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:47:53",
        "Option1" : "9",
        "Option2" : "99",
        "Option3" : "90",
        "Option4" : "09",
        "Question" : "7 000 + 200 + _________  + 3 = 7 293",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnb7wL7HBubJWxaBsp" : {
        "Answer" : "5 363",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:48:52",
        "Option1" : "5 363",
        "Option2" : "5 963",
        "Option3" : "5 763",
        "Option4" : "5 863",
        "Question" : "500 less than 5 863.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Science" : {
      "-MFnhOh1qrefpVWzhn0F" : {
        "Answer" : "Frontal lobe",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:16:14",
        "Option1" : "Cerebrum",
        "Option2" : "Frontal lobe",
        "Option3" : "Temporal lobe",
        "Option4" : "Occipital lobe",
        "Question" : "Problem solving controlled by the....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnhpuOHNeoyNwC74mz" : {
        "Answer" : "The skull",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:18:9",
        "Option1" : "The skeleton ",
        "Option2" : "The ribcage ",
        "Option3" : "The skull",
        "Option4" : "The stomach",
        "Question" : "The lungs are protected by.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnixO2WtgLHSbJu-gJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Digestive system",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:23:2",
        "Option1" : "Digestive system",
        "Option2" : "Circulatory system",
        "Option3" : "Respiratory system",
        "Option4" : "Nervous system",
        "Question" : "The intestine are the part of the.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnl8QGsjtCK9WFDeNX" : {
        "Answer" : "Shorter",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:32:35",
        "Option1" : "Taller",
        "Option2" : "Longer",
        "Option3" : "Shorter",
        "Option4" : "Remain same",
        "Question" : "When muscles contract they become......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnn5Q2Bf8XcBzArdqJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Brain stem",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:41:8",
        "Option1" : "Brain stem",
        "Option2" : "Cerebrum",
        "Option3" : "Cerebellum",
        "Option4" : "Kidney",
        "Question" : "........links the brain to the rest of the body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFznPcN68UCzsYJD8ZV" : {
        "Answer" : "Bigger",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:37:57",
        "Option1" : "Smaller",
        "Option2" : "Bigger",
        "Option3" : "Remain same",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "When you breath in your lungs get........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFznxQppNCVa-B6EJZG" : {
        "Answer" : "Carbon dioxide",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:40:20",
        "Option1" : "Oxygen ",
        "Option2" : "Carbon dioxide",
        "Option3" : "Nutrients ",
        "Option4" : "Germs",
        "Question" : "When you breath out you are getting rid of...........that your body doesn't need.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzo9WgUhiZrcAsIzNJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Two",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:41:13",
        "Option1" : "Two",
        "Option2" : "Three",
        "Option3" : "Four",
        "Option4" : "One",
        "Question" : "There are ........ intestines.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzoXrvHygW5rhOlzCf" : {
        "Answer" : "Six",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:42:53",
        "Option1" : "Six",
        "Option2" : "Two",
        "Option3" : "One",
        "Option4" : "Three",
        "Question" : "Small intestine is.......meter long.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzohhcLRmWF0ovmkdL" : {
        "Answer" : "600",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:43:38",
        "Option1" : "600",
        "Option2" : "750",
        "Option3" : "950",
        "Option4" : "100",
        "Question" : "The human body has more than ..........muscles.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzouzojurATdXPC0YT" : {
        "Answer" : "Contracting and relaxing",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:44:32",
        "Option1" : "Contracting and relaxing",
        "Option2" : "Veins",
        "Option3" : "Vessels ",
        "Option4" : "Blood",
        "Question" : "Muscles work by.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzp6s_XNVCtvho0MxV" : {
        "Answer" : "Brain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:45:25",
        "Option1" : "Stomach",
        "Option2" : "Kidneys",
        "Option3" : "Heart",
        "Option4" : "Brain",
        "Question" : "Your.......tells your muscles what yo do.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzpPOMkib1_zOjH3uP" : {
        "Answer" : "Brain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:46:42",
        "Option1" : "Lungs",
        "Option2" : "Brain",
        "Option3" : "Kidbeys",
        "Option4" : "Heart",
        "Question" : "Your.......is part of body's nervous system. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzqxMtwTrNU3cPQKnR" : {
        "Answer" : "Working",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 19:53:27",
        "Option1" : "Sleeping too",
        "Option2" : "Working",
        "Option3" : "Taking rest",
        "Option4" : "Talking",
        "Question" : "When you are asleep, the brain is.....\n\n.\n",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzt7HOs2ErR-9qKam3" : {
        "Answer" : "Cerebellum",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:3:19",
        "Option1" : "Frontal lobe",
        "Option2" : "Occipital lobe",
        "Option3" : "Parietal lobe",
        "Option4" : "Cerebellum",
        "Question" : "........controls balance and movement.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFztYFmdLatpYYQSqwn" : {
        "Answer" : "Occipital lobe",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:4:46",
        "Option1" : "Occipital lobe",
        "Option2" : "Temporal lobe",
        "Option3" : "Parietal lobe",
        "Option4" : "Frontal lobe",
        "Question" : "........ process what you see.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFztu7o1kmT5GQlzPL9" : {
        "Answer" : "Oxygen",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:6:19",
        "Option1" : "Oxygen",
        "Option2" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Option3" : "Sugar",
        "Option4" : "Salts",
        "Question" : "The left atrium contains blood with ........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzu5OTIBOikha-nyoY" : {
        "Answer" : "Blood",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:7:10",
        "Option1" : "Blood",
        "Option2" : "Food",
        "Option3" : "Water",
        "Option4" : "Germs",
        "Question" : "The heart's job is to pump........around your body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzuanhutvZ5ct7LGWO" : {
        "Answer" : "Smaller",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:9:22",
        "Option1" : "Smaller",
        "Option2" : "Bigger",
        "Option3" : "Same",
        "Option4" : "Tilted ",
        "Question" : "The left lung is....... than the right lung.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFzumBvc0Ibv6KOYlir" : {
        "Answer" : "Stomach ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-30 20:10:9",
        "Option1" : "Stomach ",
        "Option2" : "Liver",
        "Option3" : "Kidney",
        "Option4" : "Mouth",
        "Question" : "The intestine take food from......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCEFFI4XN6B_dzY1WK" : {
        "Answer" : "Oxygen",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:14:37",
        "Option1" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Option2" : "Oxygen",
        "Option3" : "Germs",
        "Option4" : "Water",
        "Question" : "Blood with.......is sent around the body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCEO4AN4BazA4tMdua" : {
        "Answer" : "Four",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:15:13",
        "Option1" : "Three",
        "Option2" : "Four",
        "Option3" : "Seven",
        "Option4" : "Ten",
        "Question" : "Your heart is divided into......chambers.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCEf2gQy69I4dZkZbN" : {
        "Answer" : "Beat ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:16:27",
        "Option1" : "Beat ",
        "Option2" : "Breaks ",
        "Option3" : "Divide ",
        "Option4" : "Contract",
        "Question" : "Your heart.....about 37 million times a year ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCEqY42okeoeGS4f40" : {
        "Answer" : "Heart ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:17:14",
        "Option1" : "Heart ",
        "Option2" : "Brain",
        "Option3" : "Kidneys ",
        "Option4" : "Tongue ",
        "Question" : "Your lungs are positioned around the....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCF3VKl1_ybeZwKr4E" : {
        "Answer" : "Cerebrum ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:18:11",
        "Option1" : "Cerebrum ",
        "Option2" : "Cerebellum ",
        "Option3" : "Brain stem ",
        "Option4" : "Frontal lobe ",
        "Question" : "......is the largest part of the brain.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Social Studies" : {
      "-MFuNzHu-nm1-9tC8fqQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Earth",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:24:22",
        "Option1" : "Moon",
        "Option2" : "Earth",
        "Option3" : "Climate ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "12- Lines of tropics mark the middle regions of ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuOIpkl6tCFPK5DTo1" : {
        "Answer" : "Sun",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:25:46",
        "Option1" : "Sun",
        "Option2" : "Earth ",
        "Option3" : "Moon",
        "Option4" : "Climate ",
        "Question" : "13- ____light does not directly strike areas between the tropics.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuOjPYva_3Tawnzfya" : {
        "Answer" : "Moderate Climate ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:27:39",
        "Option1" : "Tropical Climate ",
        "Option2" : "Moderate Climate ",
        "Option3" : "Dry Climate ",
        "Option4" : "Continental Climate ",
        "Question" : "14- ____ means warm summers and cool winters.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuPVxeKg3orC87kTom" : {
        "Answer" : "Temperature",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:31:2",
        "Option1" : "Wind",
        "Option2" : "Temperature",
        "Option3" : "Altitude ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "15- ____ is usually measured in standard units such as Celsius degree (°C) or Fahrenheit (F).",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuPwWmwCrKtbmZm8ip" : {
        "Answer" : "18°C",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:32:55",
        "Option1" : "18°C",
        "Option2" : "19°C",
        "Option3" : "20°C",
        "Option4" : "21°C",
        "Question" : "16- Most tropical areas have average temperature above ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuQN0HTzblP5g-Y8-8" : {
        "Answer" : "Amount ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:34:48",
        "Option1" : "Quantity ",
        "Option2" : "Amount ",
        "Option3" : "Value",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "17- Humidity is the ____ of water vapour in the air.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuQv7mYGL3r06xhXjv" : {
        "Answer" : "Global",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 18:37:11",
        "Option1" : "Wind",
        "Option2" : "Global",
        "Option3" : "Humidity ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "18- Greenhouse gasses help balance the ____ temperature.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuY-RwiJLu9OWg5LVt" : {
        "Answer" : "Polar",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:8:8",
        "Option1" : "Continental ",
        "Option2" : "Polar",
        "Option3" : "Dry",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "19- ____ climate is characterized by absence of trees and fairly cold atmosphere.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuYGNncBIUOOubiXiX" : {
        "Answer" : "Wind",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:9:18",
        "Option1" : "Humidity ",
        "Option2" : "Rainfall ",
        "Option3" : "Wind",
        "Option4" : "Temperature",
        "Question" : "20- The air moves, it is called ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuYgCVZ8DVXKcJlzLZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Temperature",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:11:7",
        "Option1" : "Temperature",
        "Option2" : "Altitude ",
        "Option3" : "Wind",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "21- ____ shows how hot or cold a place is.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuZt_oXX5AKu212lgz" : {
        "Answer" : "Humidity",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:16:24",
        "Option1" : "Humidity",
        "Option2" : "Cloud Cover",
        "Option3" : "Rain",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "22- ____ is the amount of water vapour in the air.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFu_VToCu_P4e_g8W68" : {
        "Answer" : "Rain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:19:4",
        "Option1" : "Rain",
        "Option2" : "Storm",
        "Option3" : "Snowfall ",
        "Option4" : "Temperature",
        "Question" : "23- Fast or strong wind patterns can bring us ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFu_yON29v7Jyj0OoQN" : {
        "Answer" : "Cloud Cover ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:21:6",
        "Option1" : "Atmosphere ",
        "Option2" : "Cloud Cover ",
        "Option3" : "Rainfall ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "24- The amount of sky covered with clouds is called ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFuaMMt48wcyN1lEhNC" : {
        "Answer" : "Altitude ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-29 19:22:48",
        "Option1" : "Temperature",
        "Option2" : "Altitude ",
        "Option3" : "Wind",
        "Option4" : "Rain",
        "Question" : "25- ____ is the height of a place from the sea level.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbqp8nenjCqzZR-AjS" : {
        "Answer" : "Globe",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 14:17:41",
        "Option1" : "Map",
        "Option2" : "Atlas",
        "Option3" : "Globe",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The model of Earth is called ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbrQSj4opinHcYWTFm" : {
        "Answer" : "Land and Water ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 14:20:17",
        "Option1" : "Land and Continent ",
        "Option2" : "Land and Water ",
        "Option3" : "Water and Ocean",
        "Option4" : "Water and River",
        "Question" : "In a map the green and blue colours represent the ___ and ___ respectively. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbrsBTi82HkEfpd4pU" : {
        "Answer" : "Continents",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 14:22:15",
        "Option1" : "Continents",
        "Option2" : "Mountains",
        "Option3" : "Fields ",
        "Option4" : "Oceans ",
        "Question" : "The areas of the land on Earth are called ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbs9RQd5DV00DPQWYB" : {
        "Answer" : "Pacific ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 14:23:30",
        "Option1" : "Arctic ",
        "Option2" : "Pacific ",
        "Option3" : "Indian",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "__ is the largest Ocean. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbskcrpnHMAADRWcTd" : {
        "Answer" : "Arctic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 14:26:6",
        "Option1" : "Arctic",
        "Option2" : "Pacific ",
        "Option3" : "Southern ",
        "Option4" : "Indian",
        "Question" : "The smallest ocean is ___ .",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc5Hr_rdkpF9ibj6mU" : {
        "Answer" : "Water",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:25:14",
        "Option1" : "Land",
        "Option2" : "Water",
        "Option3" : "Ice",
        "Option4" : "Sand",
        "Question" : "70% of Earth is ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc5uUjj7tUC0EUZjWv" : {
        "Answer" : "Rodinia",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:27:56",
        "Option1" : "Oceanic",
        "Option2" : "Rodinia",
        "Option3" : "Eurasia",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "All the seven continents have emerged from a supercontinent known as ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc6JL3LSFVFlXU-IUj" : {
        "Answer" : "Indian",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:29:42",
        "Option1" : "Pacific ",
        "Option2" : "Arctic ",
        "Option3" : "Indian",
        "Option4" : "1,2 both",
        "Question" : "___ ocean borders Asia,Africa and Australia. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc6akoy-lXy4liUOXB" : {
        "Answer" : "Four",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:30:58",
        "Option1" : "Four",
        "Option2" : "Five ",
        "Option3" : "Six",
        "Option4" : "Two",
        "Question" : "Long ago people knew only ___ continents. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc6sEf3CmNAw9O8xTe" : {
        "Answer" : "Pacific ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:32:9",
        "Option1" : "Southern ",
        "Option2" : "Indian",
        "Option3" : "Pacific ",
        "Option4" : "Arctic ",
        "Question" : "Both the North and South Americas lie between Atlantic and ___ ocean.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGc7Q03t9CSqx1tbeCF" : {
        "Answer" : "Dry Climate ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 15:34:32",
        "Option1" : "Tropical ",
        "Option2" : "Dry Climate ",
        "Option3" : "Moderate Climate ",
        "Option4" : "Continental Climate ",
        "Question" : "__ type of climate is present in areas that have little rainfall. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYrQxrI2ss8LEIqf0e" : {
        "Answer" : "Social",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:34:30",
        "Option1" : "Social",
        "Option2" : "Political ",
        "Option3" : "Cultural ",
        "Option4" : "Economical",
        "Question" : "The ___ behaviour of a society comes from its culture. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYs38hlnw8agq8gw6b" : {
        "Answer" : "Badshahi",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:37:14",
        "Option1" : "Faisal",
        "Option2" : "Badshahi",
        "Option3" : "Wazeer khan",
        "Option4" : "Shah Jahan",
        "Question" : "___ mosque was built during the rule of Aurangzeb. \n",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYsLOOhOUI1tqs1y33" : {
        "Answer" : "Mirza Ghalib",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:38:29",
        "Option1" : "Mir taki Mir",
        "Option2" : "Allama Iqbal ",
        "Option3" : "Mirza Ghalib",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "One of the well known poets of Urdu is __.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYscEDU-OWKWSDDd4O" : {
        "Answer" : "Qawwali",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:39:42",
        "Option1" : "Naat",
        "Option2" : "Ghazal",
        "Option3" : "Qawwali",
        "Option4" : "Poetry ",
        "Question" : "___ was introduced by Amir Khusro.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYsz-DELhUav_S2OGr" : {
        "Answer" : "British ",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:41:16",
        "Option1" : "British ",
        "Option2" : "Indian ",
        "Option3" : "Muslims ",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "Victorian style churches in Karachi were built by the ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYtI2jnjPT0r-fSYqa" : {
        "Answer" : "Pork",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:42:38",
        "Option1" : "Chicken ",
        "Option2" : "Beef",
        "Option3" : "Pork",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "As Muslims we cannot eat ___ which comes from a haram animal. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYtX7xHIeo_y6I2dGL" : {
        "Answer" : "Curry",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:43:39",
        "Option1" : "Curry",
        "Option2" : "Sauce ",
        "Option3" : "Spices",
        "Option4" : "B, C both",
        "Question" : "Pakistani food usually have spices and ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYtnDZUSr0qx_6Wf7f" : {
        "Answer" : "Islamic",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:44:49",
        "Option1" : "Indian",
        "Option2" : "Islamic",
        "Option3" : "British ",
        "Option4" : "D, C both",
        "Question" : "Pakistani lifestyle shows many lining of ___ culture. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYuDp3dhfBYKOtLEjE" : {
        "Answer" : "Eid Milad un Nabi",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:46:42",
        "Option1" : "Eid ul Azha",
        "Option2" : "Eid ul Fitr ",
        "Option3" : "Eid Milad un Nabi",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "___ is observed to celebrate birthday of Hazrat Muhammad (PBUH).",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MRYuT8vsBoRMsKC3rq8" : {
        "Answer" : "Urdu",
        "Date" : "2021-1-21 12:47:45",
        "Option1" : "Pashto",
        "Option2" : "Saraiki",
        "Option3" : "Urdu",
        "Option4" : "Balochi",
        "Question" : "The most commonly spoken language in Pakistan is ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Urdu" : {
      "-MFl-1CkB-BEeJyd-f0D" : {
        "Answer" : "قوم کا رہنما ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 22:38:46",
        "Option1" : "قوم کا رہنما ",
        "Option2" : "وکیل ",
        "Option3" : "بادشاہ ",
        "Option4" : "جج ",
        "Question" : "            قائدِملت کا مطلب کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl05OhnyrEGVkrY7fR" : {
        "Answer" : "کرکٹ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 22:43:26",
        "Option1" : "ہاکی",
        "Option2" : "کرکٹ",
        "Option3" : "فٹبال",
        "Option4" : "شترنج",
        "Question" : "  لیاقت علی خان فارغ اوقات میں کھیلتے \n                          تھے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl2NZ2P-2DfYaCIIpK" : {
        "Answer" : "قائداعظم کے",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 22:53:25",
        "Option1" : "علامہ اقبال کے",
        "Option2" : "قائداعظم کے",
        "Option3" : "سرسید احمد خان کے ",
        "Option4" : "کسی کے بھی نہیں ",
        "Question" : "لیاقت علی خان کس کے قریبی دوست تھے؟ ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl3K6qg_mnQyiObaNB" : {
        "Answer" : "آزادی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 22:57:33",
        "Option1" : "آزادی",
        "Option2" : "ہریالی ",
        "Option3" : "طاقت",
        "Option4" : "قربانی",
        "Question" : "نظم پیارا وطن میں خوشحالی کی کیا وجہ \n                          تھی؟  ",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl4A3AsJvG23mU42Lh" : {
        "Answer" : "آزاد فضا میں جھومنا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:1:14",
        "Option1" : "صاف اور ستھری حالت",
        "Option2" : "نہ کوئی کم تر نہ کوئی برتر",
        "Option3" : "آزاد فضا میں جھومنا",
        "Option4" : "دل میں سب کی چاہت",
        "Question" : " جھوم رہی ہے ڈالی ڈالی سے کیا مراد ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFl5ydakH0QPxvzV8dE" : {
        "Answer" : "چھوٹا بڑا سب کے حقوق برابر",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:9:7",
        "Option1" : "اس سے مراد ہم سب مل کے رہیں گے",
        "Option2" : "نہ کوئی کمتر نہ کوئی برتر",
        "Option3" : "چھوٹا بڑا سب کے حقوق برابر",
        "Option4" : "چاروں صوبے ہیں یک جاں",
        "Question" : "ہر بچہ \"گلشن کا مالی ہے\" اس سے آپ \n                کیا سمجھتے ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlBQ9I6VpT_FDXkUYw" : {
        "Answer" : "بسکٹ اور اچار",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:32:54",
        "Option1" : "چائے اور مٹھائی",
        "Option2" : "بسکٹ اور اچار",
        "Option3" : "چائے اور جلیبیاں",
        "Option4" : "چائے اور حلوہ",
        "Question" : "  سکھر شہر کھانے کی کن چیزوں کی وجہ \n                    سے مشہور ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlCqFy8hc9Ta3sy0mW" : {
        "Answer" : "لب مہران باغ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:39:7",
        "Option1" : "دریا باغ",
        "Option2" : "ریلوے باغ",
        "Option3" : "لب مہران باغ",
        "Option4" : "لیک ویو پارک",
        "Question" : "  سکھر شہر کے مشہور باغ کا نام کیا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlDGsmCUJS-LDeflqM" : {
        "Answer" : "عربی زبان سے",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:41:1",
        "Option1" : "فارسی زبان سے",
        "Option2" : "عربی زبان سے",
        "Option3" : "اردو زبان سے",
        "Option4" : "پنجابی زبان سے",
        "Question" : "          سکھر کس زبان سے نکلا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlE2upuUVFFzmNEj_r" : {
        "Answer" : "نماز اور روزے کا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:44:25",
        "Option1" : "گھڑ سواری کرنے کا",
        "Option2" : "کھیلنے کا",
        "Option3" : "دوسروں کی مدد کرنے کا",
        "Option4" : "نماز اور روزے کا",
        "Question" : " لیاقت علی خان کو بچپن سے کس چیز کا \n                       شوق تھا؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlEexOhf8GjAXsgjGf" : {
        "Answer" : "مضمون",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:47:5",
        "Option1" : "کہانی",
        "Option2" : "مضمون",
        "Option3" : "خط",
        "Option4" : "قصہ",
        "Question" : "  کسی بھی موضوع یا عنوان پر خیالات کا \n             اظہار کرنا کیا کہلاتا ہے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlH2fgd7nKOLGCMDV9" : {
        "Answer" : "سادہ الفاظ میں",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 23:57:31",
        "Option1" : "اچھے الفاظ میں",
        "Option2" : "سادہ الفاظ میں",
        "Option3" : "لمبے الفاظ میں",
        "Option4" : "چھوٹے الفاظ میں",
        "Question" : "مضمون میں اپنے خیالات کا اظہار کن الفاظ \n                   میں کرنا چاہیے؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlHqCuAA3sRKI1jJVK" : {
        "Answer" : "املا کی غلطیاں",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:0:58",
        "Option1" : "املا کی غلطیاں",
        "Option2" : "عبارات",
        "Option3" : "عنوان",
        "Option4" : "ان میں سے کوئی بھی نہیں",
        "Question" : "مضمون لکھنے کے بعد ایک دفعہ ضرور پڑھنا \n        چاہیے تاکہ درست کی جا سکیں",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlK--G-fSiYUKG7RRA" : {
        "Answer" : "سوالیہ جملہ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:10:23",
        "Option1" : "منفی جملہ",
        "Option2" : "مثبت جملہ",
        "Option3" : "سوالیہ جملہ",
        "Option4" : "فعل جملہ",
        "Question" : "  کیا تمہں کہانیاں پڑھنا پسند ہے؟ یہ جملہ  \n                        کہلاتا ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlLHol8xah21x0UwRf" : {
        "Answer" : "منفی جملے",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:16:2",
        "Option1" : "منفی جملے",
        "Option2" : "سکتہ جملے",
        "Option3" : "مثبت جملے",
        "Option4" : "سوالیہ جملے",
        "Question" : " ایسے جملے جن میں کسی کام کا نہ کرنا \n          یا نہ ہونا ظاہر ہو کہلاتے ہیں",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlLiqD6SFXqX_f7BXs" : {
        "Answer" : "تین ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:17:58",
        "Option1" : "تین ",
        "Option2" : "چار",
        "Option3" : "دو",
        "Option4" : "چھ",
        "Question" : "            جملے کی کتنی اقسام ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlMWjvtwFbeTiDgSKx" : {
        "Answer" : "جمع",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:21:25",
        "Option1" : "مترادف",
        "Option2" : "متضاد ",
        "Option3" : "جمع",
        "Option4" : "واحد",
        "Question" : " ایک سے زیادہ اشخاص یا چیزوں کو کہتے \n                           ہیں",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlO21Q_ktj6fkXsXpP" : {
        "Answer" : "مثبت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:28:3",
        "Option1" : "مترادف",
        "Option2" : "مزکر",
        "Option3" : "مثبت",
        "Option4" : "منفی",
        "Question" : " بچے سکول سے واپس آ گیے ہیں یہ جملہ \n                        کہلاتا ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlPaWReg54oE6BLjAc" : {
        "Answer" : "منفی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:34:50",
        "Option1" : "سوالیہ ",
        "Option2" : "منفی",
        "Option3" : "مثبت",
        "Option4" : "نا مکلمل",
        "Question" : "     علی نے سبق یاد نہیں کیا۔ یہ جملہ \n                        کہلاتا ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlRqvEyQT0wV4qQXZa" : {
        "Answer" : "سوالیہ (?)",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:44:42",
        "Option1" : "ختمہ(-)",
        "Option2" : "سکتہ(.)",
        "Option3" : "ندائیہ(!)",
        "Option4" : "سوالیہ (?)",
        "Question" : "   سوالیہ جملے کے آخر میں علامت لگائی \n                        جاتی ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlSc3iG2Wbkt3vaG_3" : {
        "Answer" : "امارتیں",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:48:4",
        "Option1" : "امرتوں",
        "Option2" : "امارتیں",
        "Option3" : "امارتے",
        "Option4" : "امارتی",
        "Question" : "                 امارت کے جمع ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlTGByuw_5bxvBVnWC" : {
        "Answer" : "آباد",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:50:52",
        "Option1" : "آباد",
        "Option2" : "ابادی",
        "Option3" : "ابادوں",
        "Option4" : "ان میں سے کوئی نہیں",
        "Question" : "                   ابد کی جمع ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFlTdxuNerO-OjrKpa3" : {
        "Answer" : "اشجار",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 0:52:33",
        "Option1" : "شجروں",
        "Option2" : "اشجار",
        "Option3" : "اشجارات",
        "Option4" : "اشجارتی",
        "Question" : "                  شجر کی جمع ہے",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaszpRiBX8PmQBlO-G" : {
        "Answer" : "سخت یا شديد گرمی کے",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:47:30",
        "Option1" : "سخت یا شديد گرمی کے",
        "Option2" : "سخت سردی کے",
        "Option3" : "سخت گرمی اور سردی کی",
        "Option4" : "ان میں سے کوئی بھی نہیں ",
        "Question" : "              سقر کے کیا معنی ہیں؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGatmCuA7ez-l87KqGx" : {
        "Answer" : "عربی کے لفظ سقر سے بگڑ کر پڑا",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:50:57",
        "Option1" : "بادشاہ نے رکھا",
        "Option2" : "عربی کے لفظ سقر سے بگڑ کر پڑا",
        "Option3" : "عربوں نے رکھا",
        "Option4" : "ان میں سے کوئی بھی نہیں ",
        "Question" : "          سکھر شہر کا نام کیسے پڑا؟",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      }
    }
  },
  "Class V" : {
    "English" : {
      "-MFnIDSuthL0sUUf4yw2" : {
        "Answer" : "Darren",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:21:52",
        "Option1" : "Darren",
        "Option2" : "Barren",
        "Option3" : "Martin",
        "Option4" : "Jack",
        "Question" : "1- What was the name of boy in story \"Crack a Dawn\"?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnIbTSv5OD6wh4T5ig" : {
        "Answer" : "Quatermain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:23:34",
        "Option1" : "Sir Henry",
        "Option2" : "Twala",
        "Option3" : "Quatermain",
        "Option4" : "Mr. Neville ",
        "Question" : "2- Who is describing the story in novel \"King Solomon's Mines\"?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnJEux8FnbUrbJqDah" : {
        "Answer" : "He was one of the Zulu people ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:26:20",
        "Option1" : "He was servant ",
        "Option2" : "He was king",
        "Option3" : "He was one of the Zulu people ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "3-Who was Umbopa?(King Solomon's Mines)",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnJc4cIv5GPL2z43vn" : {
        "Answer" : "Adventure",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:27:59",
        "Option1" : "Adventure",
        "Option2" : "Enjoy",
        "Option3" : "Suspense",
        "Option4" : "A, B both",
        "Question" : "4-\"Expedition\" means ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnKBTYND73UtMUFGKB" : {
        "Answer" : "Temporary stop",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:30:28",
        "Option1" : "Temporary slow",
        "Option2" : "Temporary stop",
        "Option3" : "Temporary stay",
        "Option4" : "Temporary off",
        "Question" : "5-\"Pause\" means",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnKaW1Aw6XhCqhrUsq" : {
        "Answer" : "Rubbish",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:32:14",
        "Option1" : "Lavish ",
        "Option2" : "Rubbish",
        "Option3" : "Radish",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "6-\"Useless\" is the meaning of ____. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnKmftaKmFoR5M20YE" : {
        "Answer" : "Reason",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:33:4",
        "Option1" : "Reason",
        "Option2" : "Reasonable ",
        "Option3" : "Excuse ",
        "Option4" : "Call",
        "Question" : "7-\"Cause\" means",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnLAs6M2MoiuQO5a4q" : {
        "Answer" : "Wrong idea",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:34:47",
        "Option1" : "Good idea",
        "Option2" : "Bad idea",
        "Option3" : "Wrong idea",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "8-\"Illusion\" means ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnLh0gIJndxYLif0_3" : {
        "Answer" : "He",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:37:3",
        "Option1" : "She",
        "Option2" : "We",
        "Option3" : "He",
        "Option4" : "I",
        "Question" : "9-Choose correct \"Pronoun\" for given sentence.\nJamal is happy.____ is smiling.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnM5bogiuXPs6NxvZo" : {
        "Answer" : "Quickly",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:38:48",
        "Option1" : "Quickly",
        "Option2" : "Slow",
        "Option3" : "Kitten",
        "Option4" : "Brown",
        "Question" : "10-Choose the \"Adverb\"",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnMWcIsDOgHwKVFKTU" : {
        "Answer" : "Fairly",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:40:39",
        "Option1" : "Quickly ",
        "Option2" : "Slowly ",
        "Option3" : "Calmly ",
        "Option4" : "Fairly",
        "Question" : "11-Choose correct \"Adverb\" for given sentence.\nThe weather is ____ good.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnMx8d-IgQiTj5a2zu" : {
        "Answer" : "They",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:42:31",
        "Option1" : "Us",
        "Option2" : "Her",
        "Option3" : "They",
        "Option4" : "Him",
        "Question" : "12- Complete the sentence with \"Pronoun\"\n_____ will learn swimming this year.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnND9xrxHCUBNzjHhG" : {
        "Answer" : "Their",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:43:41",
        "Option1" : "Slow",
        "Option2" : "Their",
        "Option3" : "Is",
        "Option4" : "Was",
        "Question" : "13- Choose \"Pronoun\"",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnO-KsErPWK4hWxUOX" : {
        "Answer" : "He, It",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:47:7",
        "Option1" : "She, It",
        "Option2" : "They, It",
        "Option3" : "He, It",
        "Option4" : "We, It",
        "Question" : "14- Choose \"Adverb\" for given sentence.\nThe Dog is guarding the bone.____ will chew ____ later.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnOs1tk7nrQ6E8Lq3i" : {
        "Answer" : "Quaid e Azam, Murree, Ravi",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:50:55",
        "Option1" : "Teacher, House, Bird",
        "Option2" : "Quaid e Azam, Murree, Ravi",
        "Option3" : "Pencil, Pen, Book",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "15- Choose the set of \"Proper Noun\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnQOP86fX0iRL4sDlY" : {
        "Answer" : "Teacher, Truck, Mountain",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:57:34",
        "Option1" : "Teacher, Truck, Mountain",
        "Option2" : "Islamabad, Shan oil, Iqbal",
        "Option3" : "City, Saira, Ali",
        "Option4" : "A, C both",
        "Question" : "16- Choose the set of      \"Common Noun\".",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnQvmqNIvPQ6Yc8Bxi" : {
        "Answer" : "Caught",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:59:55",
        "Option1" : "Caught",
        "Option2" : "Peeped",
        "Option3" : "Stitch",
        "Option4" : "Whisper",
        "Question" : "17- Complete the sentence with \"Verb\"\nThe wicketkeeper ____ the ball.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnS6VJTRCy0Pqc1Q39" : {
        "Answer" : "Whisper",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:5:4",
        "Option1" : "Stitch",
        "Option2" : "Whisper",
        "Option3" : "Peeper",
        "Option4" : "Celebrate",
        "Question" : "18- Choose \"Verb\" for given sentence.\nWhat did Sara ____ in your ear?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSd3WH1MEmg3DVIJd" : {
        "Answer" : "Adjectives",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:7:22",
        "Option1" : "Nouns",
        "Option2" : "Pronouns",
        "Option3" : "Adjectives",
        "Option4" : "Adverbs",
        "Question" : "19- ____ are describing words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSwmS1DB4AB2yaBVa" : {
        "Answer" : "Noun",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:8:43",
        "Option1" : "Verb",
        "Option2" : "Noun",
        "Option3" : "Adverb",
        "Option4" : "Adjective",
        "Question" : "20- ____ is a naming word. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTuHOkuzztd0K_VBu" : {
        "Answer" : "Shady",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:12:55",
        "Option1" : "Shady",
        "Option2" : "Small",
        "Option3" : "Deep",
        "Option4" : "Striped ",
        "Question" : "21- Choose the \"Adjective\" for given sentence.\nThe farmer sat under a ____ tree.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnUvva10AJkXaklFIF" : {
        "Answer" : "Prepositions",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:17:24",
        "Option1" : "Nouns",
        "Option2" : "Pronouns",
        "Option3" : "Prepositions",
        "Option4" : "Adjectives ",
        "Question" : "22-Words that connect nouns or pronouns to other words in a sentence are called _____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnVX4JQ4Ab1EajOXd2" : {
        "Answer" : "We",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:20:0",
        "Option1" : "Between ",
        "Option2" : "We",
        "Option3" : "Are",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "23-Choose \"Pronoun\"in given words.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnW8ygPPdhMDogpbYR" : {
        "Answer" : "Behind, At, On",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:22:43",
        "Option1" : "Is, Are, Am",
        "Option2" : "Was, Were, On",
        "Option3" : "Behind, At, On",
        "Option4" : "I, We, You",
        "Question" : "24- Choose the set of \"Pronoun\"",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnXEkIOri65ClId_HK" : {
        "Answer" : "Verb",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:27:29",
        "Option1" : "Adjective",
        "Option2" : "Adverb",
        "Option3" : "Verb",
        "Option4" : "Pronoun",
        "Question" : "25-A sentence is incomplete without ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "ICT" : {
      "-MGHE3V5qhYXLch_L2Ys" : {
        "Answer" : "Computer network",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:31:56",
        "Option1" : "Computer network",
        "Option2" : "Software ",
        "Option3" : "Hardware ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is a collection of inter connected computer and devices.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHEZUZDDBHatmrP5J0" : {
        "Answer" : "Communication ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:34:7",
        "Option1" : "Conversation ",
        "Option2" : "Combination ",
        "Option3" : "Communication ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "The exchange of data/information from one computer to another is called. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHF8flnspiPnaZQHYE" : {
        "Answer" : "Communication device",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:36:39",
        "Option1" : "Sending device",
        "Option2" : "Communication device",
        "Option3" : "Receiving device",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It enables a computer to communicate with other computers.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHFnvJ3h20tGyfZMDk" : {
        "Answer" : "Wireless medium",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:39:32",
        "Option1" : "Wire based medium",
        "Option2" : "Wireless medium",
        "Option3" : "Air medium ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The medium that transmits signals through air or space is known as...",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHGBuNJBzZ6vdgGFix" : {
        "Answer" : "Client",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:41:14",
        "Option1" : "Client",
        "Option2" : "Workstation ",
        "Option3" : "Server",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It shares its resources with other computer on a network. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHHTk3rFAJy_r-tiQX" : {
        "Answer" : "Number of computer connected ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:46:50",
        "Option1" : "Area covered by them ",
        "Option2" : "Number of computer connected ",
        "Option3" : "Transmission medium used by them ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Computer networks are classified on the basic of..",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHHyvz_bZzqY9O6GmO" : {
        "Answer" : "Local Area Network ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:49:2",
        "Option1" : "Lower Area Network ",
        "Option2" : "Local Area Network ",
        "Option3" : "Local Air Network ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "LAN stands for.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHIseQUrVSmYvTfBa1" : {
        "Answer" : "Fire opt cable",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:52:58",
        "Option1" : "Fiber optical cable",
        "Option2" : "Fire opt cable",
        "Option3" : "Fiber over cable",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is a wire based medium for a network. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHJH-bI05_rZ8BAVdL" : {
        "Answer" : "MAN",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:54:42",
        "Option1" : "MAN",
        "Option2" : "WAN",
        "Option3" : "LAN ",
        "Option4" : "CAN",
        "Question" : "It is designed to share resources of different LANS in a city.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHMwK-gb_fUCEtoRAq" : {
        "Answer" : "WAN",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:10:41",
        "Option1" : "LAN",
        "Option2" : "MAN",
        "Option3" : "WAN",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Internet is an example of…",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHNPKPooY4xYITlCky" : {
        "Answer" : "Message ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:12:44",
        "Option1" : "Message ",
        "Option2" : "Receiving ",
        "Option3" : "Order",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "The data information communicated on a network is called...",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHNhEZLIoGw6pmtcJY" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:14:2",
        "Option1" : "3",
        "Option2" : "2",
        "Option3" : "4",
        "Option4" : "6",
        "Question" : "Transmission medium is based on ___ types of medium. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHNyHuPREcSfTf4_SD" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:15:12",
        "Option1" : "3",
        "Option2" : "1",
        "Option3" : "2",
        "Option4" : "5",
        "Question" : "The simple network can be formed with ___ computer. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHOhtf_8KfsB-aVLAd" : {
        "Answer" : "Limited ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:18:27",
        "Option1" : "Limited ",
        "Option2" : "W.W.W",
        "Option3" : "Metropolitan ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "A LAN is a computer network in a ___ geographical area. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHP9NAoPaYTdA59O8r" : {
        "Answer" : "Virus",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:20:23",
        "Option1" : "Virus",
        "Option2" : "Antivirus ",
        "Option3" : "Flash memory ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "It infacts a computer. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHPjWm6UGykavESNap" : {
        "Answer" : "Worm",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:22:55",
        "Option1" : "Worm",
        "Option2" : "Virus ",
        "Option3" : "Adware ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It fills the entire disk and occupy space in the memory. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHQMm5irS6FQCVhf-p" : {
        "Answer" : "Adware",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:25:40",
        "Option1" : "Worm",
        "Option2" : "Adware",
        "Option3" : "Trojan",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "These programs disrupt the privacy of a user.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHQquTiuhCGX3KPsoW" : {
        "Answer" : "Hacking",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:27:48",
        "Option1" : "Surfing",
        "Option2" : "Searching ",
        "Option3" : "Hacking",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "The act of gaining access to a computer illegally is called..",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHRAGBYlfn1Ia10B63" : {
        "Answer" : "Trojan",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:29:12",
        "Option1" : "Trojan",
        "Option2" : "Worm",
        "Option3" : "Virus",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is hidden in a legal software. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHRgqHIVUsbtnU5NxR" : {
        "Answer" : "Infected E.mail",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:31:29",
        "Option1" : "Infected E.mail",
        "Option2" : "Web Searching ",
        "Option3" : "Word Processing ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is one of the major source of spreading viruses.\n",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHSi4mZ3ApfeAfE2iN" : {
        "Answer" : "Pirated Software ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:35:56",
        "Option1" : "Pirated Software ",
        "Option2" : "System Software ",
        "Option3" : "Application Software ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "These software are also one of the cause of spreading viruses. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHTFy0_OpC6EjGTIFW" : {
        "Answer" : "Antivirus ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:38:19",
        "Option1" : "Antivirus ",
        "Option2" : "Ms Word ",
        "Option3" : "Ms excel",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is used to protect a computer from malicious software. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHTb-iOLHQXlsLWymP" : {
        "Answer" : "Trojan",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:39:49",
        "Option1" : "Virus",
        "Option2" : "Trojan",
        "Option3" : "Adware",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "It automatically displays advertisements.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHTujhIZijCzWZFeV3" : {
        "Answer" : "Useful",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:41:10",
        "Option1" : "Harmful",
        "Option2" : "Damage",
        "Option3" : "Useful",
        "Option4" : "Helpful ",
        "Question" : "An antivirus is a ___ software. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGI2lCokSda7YQLOnFJ" : {
        "Answer" : "MsWord",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 13:22:10",
        "Option1" : "Linux",
        "Option2" : "MsWord",
        "Option3" : "Unix",
        "Option4" : "Macos",
        "Question" : "....Word is a type of application software",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Islamiyat" : {
      "-MGCVGa91bxH68A8AXrB" : {
        "Answer" : "The Holy Quran",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:28:59",
        "Option1" : "Bible ",
        "Option2" : "Zabur",
        "Option3" : "Toura",
        "Option4" : "The Holy Quran",
        "Question" : "The Arabic word______ means reading or recitation.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCVewLD7K6CyBJ09R2" : {
        "Answer" : "Arabic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:30:43",
        "Option1" : "Latin",
        "Option2" : "Urdu",
        "Option3" : "Arabic",
        "Option4" : "English",
        "Question" : "Quran was revealed in the_____ language.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWG-NviZvj4-IK-Cl" : {
        "Answer" : "Ramazan",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:33:19",
        "Option1" : "Ramazan",
        "Option2" : "Muharram",
        "Option3" : "Shawal",
        "Option4" : "Safar",
        "Question" : "The first revelation came to Holy prophet in the cave of hira in the month of ______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWZkQBxt-O2qctTHK" : {
        "Answer" : "23",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:34:40",
        "Option1" : "20",
        "Option2" : "22",
        "Option3" : "23",
        "Option4" : "27",
        "Question" : "Qurran was revealed for a period _____ years.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWuN37B-CteZZsg4M" : {
        "Answer" : "Makkah",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:36:8",
        "Option1" : "Taif",
        "Option2" : "Makkah",
        "Option3" : "Madina",
        "Option4" : "Najaf",
        "Question" : "Makki serahs was revealed in ________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXDjRVv8HyjUvfiIX" : {
        "Answer" : "114",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:37:32",
        "Option1" : "115",
        "Option2" : "112",
        "Option3" : "114",
        "Option4" : "118",
        "Question" : "The Holy quran has______ surahs or parts.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXV46EmsbwLsOlGMo" : {
        "Answer" : "96",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:38:43",
        "Option1" : "95",
        "Option2" : "96",
        "Option3" : "97",
        "Option4" : "98",
        "Question" : "Surah Alaq is_______ Surah of the Quran.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCYYI7XuvN_PsijeMX" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Maidah",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:43:18",
        "Option1" : "Al-Maidah",
        "Option2" : "Al-Baqarah",
        "Option3" : "Al-Nas",
        "Option4" : "Al- fatiha",
        "Question" : "The last revelation of surah______ three verses was revealed befor the death of the Holy prophet (Pbuh).",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZ28U51JO48BNtk76" : {
        "Answer" : "Alaq",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:45:29",
        "Option1" : "Al- Nas",
        "Option2" : "Alaq",
        "Option3" : "Al-fatihah",
        "Option4" : "Al-qadar",
        "Question" : "The first surah of the Holy Quran is_______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZW_-8KFZS3LgcwFQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Any way",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:47:33",
        "Option1" : "Any way",
        "Option2" : "All the time",
        "Option3" : "Some time ",
        "Option4" : "Part of day",
        "Question" : "We should not disobey Allah in ______ way.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZpffGUQss5m6aARB" : {
        "Answer" : "Last book ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:48:56",
        "Option1" : "Last book ",
        "Option2" : "Third book",
        "Option3" : "Fourth book",
        "Option4" : "Fifth book",
        "Question" : "The Holy Quran is the _______ book.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC_CJ8THkFPPqhE1T1" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Baqarah",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:50:32",
        "Option1" : "Al-Baqarah",
        "Option2" : "Al-Imran",
        "Option3" : "Al-Falaq",
        "Option4" : "Al-Alaq",
        "Question" : "The longest surah of the Holy Quran is______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC_Ve4NPK-cm3LzFFo" : {
        "Answer" : "286",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:51:52",
        "Option1" : "280",
        "Option2" : "286",
        "Option3" : "288",
        "Option4" : "289",
        "Question" : "How many verses in Surah Al-Baqarah?",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCa82nukNig2Sf2EZ3" : {
        "Answer" : "Jibrael",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:54:37",
        "Option1" : "Israfil",
        "Option2" : "Mikaell",
        "Option3" : "Jibrael",
        "Option4" : "Izrael",
        "Question" : "The angel whi brought revelation to the Holy Prophet (Pbuh) is ________.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCafPFNs-VykU7Qcai" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-kausar",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:56:59",
        "Option1" : "Al- Falaq",
        "Option2" : "An-nas",
        "Option3" : "Al-kausar",
        "Option4" : "Al-Alaq",
        "Question" : "The shortest surah is_____ which has three verses.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCazYBRnVguMMAwJAS" : {
        "Answer" : "Muslims",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:58:20",
        "Option1" : "Muslims",
        "Option2" : "Jews",
        "Option3" : "Christians",
        "Option4" : "Hindus",
        "Question" : "The Holy Quran is the scared book of the ______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCbTD7nX01wodVZI7Z" : {
        "Answer" : "Tauhid",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:0:26",
        "Option1" : "Salat",
        "Option2" : "Zakat",
        "Option3" : "Tauhid",
        "Option4" : "Fast",
        "Question" : "The basic theme of the Quran is ______ or unity of Allah.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCbuaD0fOpNZhXri-J" : {
        "Answer" : "The Holy Quran",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:2:22",
        "Option1" : "Bible ",
        "Option2" : "The Holy Quran",
        "Option3" : "Toura",
        "Option4" : "Zabur",
        "Question" : "We should therefor follow the teaching and guidance laid down in the _______.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCcTDzjvjMjRblN5z8" : {
        "Answer" : "Heaven",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:4:48",
        "Option1" : "Heaven",
        "Option2" : "Hell ",
        "Option3" : "Whole world ",
        "Option4" : "Sky",
        "Question" : "Quran says that those who believe will be rewarded with ______ after death.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCcpY3gztX5HfeuMWo" : {
        "Answer" : "Wuzu ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:6:24",
        "Option1" : "Washing hands",
        "Option2" : "Ghusl",
        "Option3" : "Wuzu ",
        "Option4" : "Washing face",
        "Question" : "Perform ______ before touching the Holy Quran.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCdOZ5lrF26dSxaMUf" : {
        "Answer" : "Wicked/wrongdoers",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:8:51",
        "Option1" : "Wicked/nice",
        "Option2" : "Wicked/wrongdoers",
        "Option3" : "Wicked and poor",
        "Option4" : "Rich and nice",
        "Question" : "The ______ and _______ will be punished hell.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCdn0hg14tWDvTaOU6" : {
        "Answer" : "Man",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:10:38",
        "Option1" : "Man",
        "Option2" : "Animals",
        "Option3" : "Soul",
        "Option4" : "Birds",
        "Question" : "The Holy Quran addresses______ directly and encourages him to adopt the right way or path.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCeIFeaVltOivz9ev0" : {
        "Answer" : "40 years",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:12:48",
        "Option1" : "41 years",
        "Option2" : "40 years",
        "Option3" : "42 years",
        "Option4" : "45 years",
        "Question" : "At age of _______ the revelation started on Holy Prophet (Pbuh).",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCeg00a1ot9771B5Au" : {
        "Answer" : "Prophets",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 12:14:29",
        "Option1" : "People",
        "Option2" : "Prophets",
        "Option3" : "Angel",
        "Option4" : "Birds",
        "Question" : "Book had been revealed to previous_______ as well as.",
        "author" : "tehzeebaslam866@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGH9lvdfMT84ENrClC7" : {
        "Answer" : "Holy Quran",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 9:13:11",
        "Option1" : "Taurah",
        "Option2" : "Zabur",
        "Option3" : "Injeel",
        "Option4" : "Holy Quran",
        "Question" : "We should follow the teachings and guidance laid down in the _________.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Math" : {
      "-MFnLZSpXKEXbOekeJLD" : {
        "Answer" : "tens",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:36:28",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds ",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "The digit 1 is in the________ place in 23 016.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnLt20yqEdBAHb2z6N" : {
        "Answer" : "305 432",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:37:53",
        "Option1" : "305 432",
        "Option2" : "354 320",
        "Option3" : "300 540",
        "Option4" : "354 321",
        "Question" : "300 000 + 5 000 + 400 + 30 + 2 = ? ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnM5OB11xjf8LP2YEc" : {
        "Answer" : "23 740",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:38:47",
        "Option1" : "75 300",
        "Option2" : "57 023",
        "Option3" : "23 740",
        "Option4" : "47 251",
        "Question" : "The digit 7 is in hundreds place in____.s",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnMOs2RfJoP1nhG4QZ" : {
        "Answer" : "4 795",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:40:7",
        "Option1" : "4 975",
        "Option2" : "5 749",
        "Option3" : "9 745",
        "Option4" : "4 795",
        "Question" : "4 thousands + 7 hundreds + 9 tens + 5 ones = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnMdWTwMXdQlx0TLtM" : {
        "Answer" : "533",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:41:11",
        "Option1" : "535",
        "Option2" : "533",
        "Option3" : "545",
        "Option4" : "543",
        "Question" : "Complete the sequence, 532, ____, 534.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnMwt5JQ2sL34jOLSs" : {
        "Answer" : "4 000",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:42:31",
        "Option1" : "400",
        "Option2" : "4 000",
        "Option3" : "4",
        "Option4" : "40 000",
        "Question" : "10 000 + _____ + 300 + 90 + 7 = 14 397",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnNCIxfkZuc5K6laoF" : {
        "Answer" : "8",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:43:38",
        "Option1" : "9",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "8",
        "Option4" : "6",
        "Question" : "What is the digit in the place of thousands in     98 674?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnNhuz3Yt-zNgxtHE1" : {
        "Answer" : "hundred thousands",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:45:51",
        "Option1" : "hundred thousands",
        "Option2" : "hundreds",
        "Option3" : "thousands",
        "Option4" : "tens",
        "Question" : "The digit 5 is in ______ place in 578 693.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnNyPxm3-xNevAnLWB" : {
        "Answer" : "2 500",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:46:59",
        "Option1" : "2 150",
        "Option2" : "2 105",
        "Option3" : "2 050",
        "Option4" : "2 500",
        "Question" : "Two thousand and five hundred.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnOV8ceU99IW588SqI" : {
        "Answer" : "16 409",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:49:17",
        "Option1" : "16 490",
        "Option2" : "16 904",
        "Option3" : "16 409",
        "Option4" : "60 409",
        "Question" : "Sixteen thousand four hundred and nine",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnOivsZAYeRSwyFBXA" : {
        "Answer" : "thousands",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:50:18",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "In 83 510, the digit 3 is in the _________ place.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnP-8E8SyjsqT4HASr" : {
        "Answer" : "greater than",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:51:28",
        "Option1" : "less than ",
        "Option2" : "greater than",
        "Option3" : "equal to ",
        "Option4" : "descendant to",
        "Question" : "362 407 is _________ 325 704.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnPG52AatmzuttK-8U" : {
        "Answer" : "700",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:52:38",
        "Option1" : "70",
        "Option2" : "707",
        "Option3" : "700",
        "Option4" : "070",
        "Question" : "24 700 = 20 000 + 4 000 + ______+ 00 + 0",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnPSFuYMc1yB69dhK-" : {
        "Answer" : "ones",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:53:27",
        "Option1" : "ones",
        "Option2" : "tens",
        "Option3" : "hundreds",
        "Option4" : "thousands",
        "Question" : "The value of 2 in 364 572 is_________.s",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnPgrDQyI8msz0MNdQ" : {
        "Answer" : "111 111",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:54:31",
        "Option1" : "111 111",
        "Option2" : "11 111",
        "Option3" : "1 111",
        "Option4" : "111",
        "Question" : "100 000 + 10 000 + 1 000 + 100 + 10 + 1 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnQr5D1ciV5wFHNDbw" : {
        "Answer" : "999 999",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 9:59:35",
        "Option1" : "999 909",
        "Option2" : "99 999",
        "Option3" : "999 999",
        "Option4" : "909 909",
        "Question" : "900 000 + 90 000 + 9 000 + 900 + 90 + 9 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnREEFJUO5sG6mmPiz" : {
        "Answer" : "453 821",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:1:14",
        "Option1" : "438 201",
        "Option2" : "453 821",
        "Option3" : "453 218",
        "Option4" : "458 312",
        "Question" : "Four hundred and fifty three thousand, eight hundred and twenty one.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnRX1IdHG5Szu3WJ33" : {
        "Answer" : "57 234",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:2:31",
        "Option1" : "57 234",
        "Option2" : "66 234",
        "Option3" : "15 342",
        "Option4" : "43 265",
        "Question" : "1 000 more than 56 234.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnRtm-PrTnZUgQyxLB" : {
        "Answer" : "5 000",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:4:8",
        "Option1" : "50",
        "Option2" : "500",
        "Option3" : "5",
        "Option4" : "5 000",
        "Question" : "200 000 + 30 000 + _________ + 600 + 80 + 9  =  235 689",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSBdIvYHUOC5Joq9v" : {
        "Answer" : "52 763",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:5:26",
        "Option1" : "50 863",
        "Option2" : "52 863",
        "Option3" : "52 763",
        "Option4" : "52 963",
        "Question" : "100 less than 52 863.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSaGsmPPDzNq7VcpL" : {
        "Answer" : "5 903",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:7:11",
        "Option1" : "5 903",
        "Option2" : "5 390",
        "Option3" : "9 305",
        "Option4" : "5 309",
        "Question" : "The digit 9 is in hundreds place in____.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSqnby8LB3MLcOxT9" : {
        "Answer" : "6 138",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:8:18",
        "Option1" : "6 138",
        "Option2" : "5 632",
        "Option3" : "6 831",
        "Option4" : "6 132",
        "Question" : "6 thousands + 1 hundreds + 3 tens + 8 ones = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTEvz3g-QisKPYstR" : {
        "Answer" : "330",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:10:1",
        "Option1" : "303",
        "Option2" : "323",
        "Option3" : "333",
        "Option4" : "330",
        "Question" : "Complete the sequence, 329, ____, 331.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTT15NQuu44wpCKWY" : {
        "Answer" : "100",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:10:59",
        "Option1" : "10",
        "Option2" : "101",
        "Option3" : "1 000",
        "Option4" : "100",
        "Question" : "9 000 + _____ + 40 + 3 = 9 143",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTbbzwBGLdKccR0Za" : {
        "Answer" : "6",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:11:38",
        "Option1" : "5",
        "Option2" : "6",
        "Option3" : "7",
        "Option4" : "8",
        "Question" : "What is the digit in the place of ten thousands in 67 895?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Science" : {
      "-MG911opN0wusiXesBJD" : {
        "Answer" : "Involuntary ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:18:3",
        "Option1" : "Involuntary ",
        "Option2" : "Voluntary ",
        "Option3" : "Valid",
        "Option4" : "Stronger",
        "Question" : "The smooth muscles are......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG91K6Y4MbaSFepLnCl" : {
        "Answer" : "Arms",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:19:22",
        "Option1" : "Feet",
        "Option2" : "Arms",
        "Option3" : "Ears",
        "Option4" : "Nose",
        "Question" : "Your biceps muscles are in your........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG91_f1AiJKnGvmEu4r" : {
        "Answer" : "Two ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:20:25",
        "Option1" : "One ",
        "Option2" : "Two ",
        "Option3" : "Three",
        "Option4" : "Four",
        "Question" : "The nervous system has........main parts",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG92DJXo-Tv1yQawwUl" : {
        "Answer" : "Blood ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:23:12",
        "Option1" : "Blood ",
        "Option2" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Option3" : "Germs",
        "Option4" : "Water",
        "Question" : "The heart pumps......arpund the body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG92hqP17SmNxCtzUBo" : {
        "Answer" : "Capillaries",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:25:22",
        "Option1" : "Lungs",
        "Option2" : "Heart",
        "Option3" : "Capillaries",
        "Option4" : "Stomach ",
        "Question" : "........ are small blood vessels that links the arteries with veins. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG937H05vM29bwiW1tF" : {
        "Answer" : "Septum ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:27:10",
        "Option1" : "Ventricle ",
        "Option2" : "Atrium ",
        "Option3" : "Aorta ",
        "Option4" : "Septum ",
        "Question" : "The....... is a wall that separates the right and left sides of the heart. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG93XuFatcW7vehmMHv" : {
        "Answer" : "Voluntary ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:28:59",
        "Option1" : "Valid",
        "Option2" : "Involuntary ",
        "Option3" : "Voluntary ",
        "Option4" : "Biceps ",
        "Question" : "......... muscles are those whose movement can't be controlled.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG94Npm86xsQH7BIigK" : {
        "Answer" : "Oesophagus  ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:32:40",
        "Option1" : "Oesophagus  ",
        "Option2" : "Stomach",
        "Option3" : "Teeth",
        "Option4" : "Tongue ",
        "Question" : "The food travels down the......when swallowed. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG950S1HU0kRxXxCHOC" : {
        "Answer" : "Tendons ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:35:26",
        "Option1" : "Tendons ",
        "Option2" : "Filament ",
        "Option3" : "Ligament ",
        "Option4" : "Joint ",
        "Question" : "Skeletal muscles are attached to your bones by a fibre called..... ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG95iFoqiEhDA6LCqv4" : {
        "Answer" : "Alveoli ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:38:30",
        "Option1" : "Pores ",
        "Option2" : "Stomach ",
        "Option3" : "Alveoli ",
        "Option4" : "Non of the above ",
        "Question" : "The tiny air sacs in the lungs are called.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG96Yya72Kmgerk5gzY" : {
        "Answer" : "Nutrients ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:42:9",
        "Option1" : "Nutrients ",
        "Option2" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Option3" : "Germs ",
        "Option4" : "Bacteria ",
        "Question" : "The circulatory system is the system that sends oxygen and....... around the body ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG96jgkVtZ8T77DuI5k" : {
        "Answer" : "Three",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:42:58",
        "Option1" : "One ",
        "Option2" : "Three",
        "Option3" : "Eight",
        "Option4" : "Ten",
        "Question" : "There are...... types of blood vessels.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG98HscuFfKtFN1H39O" : {
        "Answer" : "Nose",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:49:44",
        "Option1" : "Nose",
        "Option2" : "Skin",
        "Option3" : "Stomach ",
        "Option4" : "Heart",
        "Question" : "When you breath in, air is inhaled through your......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG98ReLYnCVVuEluORB" : {
        "Answer" : "600",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:50:24",
        "Option1" : "650",
        "Option2" : "700",
        "Option3" : "600",
        "Option4" : "100",
        "Question" : "There are more than.......muscles in the human body.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG98wMfWSxyu_o9h-iw" : {
        "Answer" : "Cardiac muscle",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:52:33",
        "Option1" : "Cardiac muscle",
        "Option2" : "Biceps muscle ",
        "Option3" : "Triceps muscle ",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "Your heart is a muscle known as......muscle.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG99AMdoRute78QaCYO" : {
        "Answer" : "206",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:53:35",
        "Option1" : "406",
        "Option2" : "706",
        "Option3" : "206",
        "Option4" : "906",
        "Question" : "An adult human has.......bones.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG99OImKcQKfpvILcDe" : {
        "Answer" : "Skeleton ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:54:32",
        "Option1" : "Lungs",
        "Option2" : "Skeleton ",
        "Option3" : "Heart ",
        "Option4" : "Stomach ",
        "Question" : ".........protect your internal organ from damage.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG99azWliaPXn1SSnP8" : {
        "Answer" : "Joint ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:55:28",
        "Option1" : "Joint ",
        "Option2" : "Muscles ",
        "Option3" : "Tendon ",
        "Option4" : "Ligament ",
        "Question" : "The point where two bones meet or join is called.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG99zO1OtyQxknREi55" : {
        "Answer" : "Saliva ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:57:8",
        "Option1" : "Blood ",
        "Option2" : "Saliva ",
        "Option3" : "Insects ",
        "Option4" : "Oxygen ",
        "Question" : "...... breaks down food and make it easier to bite and swallowed.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG9A_JtCaXM-5zPWNYR" : {
        "Answer" : "Hinge joint ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 19:59:43",
        "Option1" : "Hinge joint ",
        "Option2" : "Ball and socket joint ",
        "Option3" : "Skull",
        "Option4" : "Ribs",
        "Question" : "The knee and elbow joint are example of...... joint.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG9AnMxDWjoa9i9R4Lr" : {
        "Answer" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 20:0:41",
        "Option1" : "Oxygen",
        "Option2" : "Carbon dioxide ",
        "Option3" : "Acids ",
        "Option4" : "Food",
        "Question" : "When you breath out you exhale....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG9B3aATwBll-pfuibL" : {
        "Answer" : "Two",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 20:1:51",
        "Option1" : "One ",
        "Option2" : "Two",
        "Option3" : "Three",
        "Option4" : "Four",
        "Question" : "Human body has.....lungs.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCGiaiwUEDp14rk8kA" : {
        "Answer" : "Spinal cord ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:25:26",
        "Option1" : "Spinal cord ",
        "Option2" : "Blood",
        "Option3" : "Nerves ",
        "Option4" : "Vessels ",
        "Question" : "The central nervous system is the brain and....\n\n.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCHgAFOQobFphu5syo" : {
        "Answer" : "Three",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:29:38",
        "Option1" : "Three",
        "Option2" : "Four",
        "Option3" : "Five",
        "Option4" : "Seven",
        "Question" : "There are.....\n.types of blood vessels.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCHq0KCL6SedLT4btJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Veins ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:30:18",
        "Option1" : "Veins ",
        "Option2" : "Capillaries ",
        "Option3" : "Arteries ",
        "Option4" : "Stomach",
        "Question" : "....... carry blood to the heart.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Social Studies" : {
      "-MGRuTL5MVK_oaP889IJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Persian",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:17:45",
        "Option1" : "Arabic ",
        "Option2" : "British ",
        "Option3" : "Persian",
        "Option4" : "Urdu",
        "Question" : "Mughal is___ pronunciation of Mangol.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRugX8zDRRupoyGOPL" : {
        "Answer" : "Agra",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:18:44",
        "Option1" : "Panipat ",
        "Option2" : "Agra",
        "Option3" : "Dehli",
        "Option4" : "Mumbai ",
        "Question" : "Babur chose ___ as the capital of Mughal Empire. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRv4Uh5TOD05Wd6i4Y" : {
        "Answer" : "Tuzk-e-babri ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:20:26",
        "Option1" : "Ram Bagh",
        "Option2" : "Tuzk-e-babri ",
        "Option3" : "Sultanate of Babur ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Babur's autobiography is known as ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRvS1y57-CUd3r056i" : {
        "Answer" : "Humayun ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:22:2",
        "Option1" : "Humayun ",
        "Option2" : "Jahangir",
        "Option3" : "Shah Jahan ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "___ was the sun of Babur.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRvrXR_T1V4cOJlIsJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Sher Shah Suri ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:23:51",
        "Option1" : "Shah Jahan ",
        "Option2" : "Jahangir ",
        "Option3" : "Sher Shah Suri ",
        "Option4" : "Babur",
        "Question" : "Humayun lost his throne to ___ and was forced to flee India.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRwBemnm-guyZCyu_r" : {
        "Answer" : "Bengal",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:25:17",
        "Option1" : "Daccan",
        "Option2" : "Bengal",
        "Option3" : "Mumbai",
        "Option4" : "Dehli",
        "Question" : "Sher Shah Suri was the king of ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRwYeKZ6TaKR0qiO7r" : {
        "Answer" : "Ten",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:26:52",
        "Option1" : "Ten",
        "Option2" : "Twenty ",
        "Option3" : "Thirty ",
        "Option4" : "Fifty",
        "Question" : "Akbar made financial planning for ___ years.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRwz5M-OQrwn5Oo2EE" : {
        "Answer" : "Urdu",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:28:44",
        "Option1" : "Hindi",
        "Option2" : "Telugo",
        "Option3" : "Urdu",
        "Option4" : "French ",
        "Question" : "Rich culture in Akbar's time gave birth to a new language. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRxGBsL_fhpvNsf0_T" : {
        "Answer" : "Chain of justice ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:29:58",
        "Option1" : "Court",
        "Option2" : "Chain of justice ",
        "Option3" : "Judiciary ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "In order to establish justice Jahangir built a ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRze4IpM60qkOd-uF4" : {
        "Answer" : "Jama Masjid Dehli",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:40:24",
        "Option1" : "Badshahi Masjid ",
        "Option2" : "Shah Faisal Masjid ",
        "Option3" : "Jama Masjid Dehli",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "___ is the largest \"Mosque\" in India at this time. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaoZeegsZ24mM6_x-z" : {
        "Answer" : "1857",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:28:10",
        "Option1" : "1657",
        "Option2" : "1857",
        "Option3" : "1957",
        "Option4" : "1947",
        "Question" : "The war of independence of ___ is a turning point in the history of the subcontinent. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGapBcd-qRgwhgAVWId" : {
        "Answer" : "British Raj ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:30:54",
        "Option1" : "British Raj ",
        "Option2" : "Control of India ",
        "Option3" : "Period of Hindus ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The period in which British had full and direct control of India is called ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGapaFTNoB3zyp5uhFz" : {
        "Answer" : "Economy",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:32:39",
        "Option1" : "Country ",
        "Option2" : "Economy",
        "Option3" : "People ",
        "Option4" : "Nation ",
        "Question" : "When the British Raj started, the Indian ___ was very prosperous. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGapwwFuWXt9DKJft9r" : {
        "Answer" : "Sir Syed Ahmad khan ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:34:12",
        "Option1" : "Allama Iqbal ",
        "Option2" : "Muhammad Ali Jinnah ",
        "Option3" : "Sir Syed Ahmad khan ",
        "Option4" : "Liaqat Ali khan ",
        "Question" : "___ built Muhammadan Anglo Oriental College. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaqcPcXMgU2QRUnDKa" : {
        "Answer" : "Lucknow ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:37:10",
        "Option1" : "Lucknow ",
        "Option2" : "Mumbai ",
        "Option3" : "Dehli",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The headquarter of the \"All India Muslim League\" was at ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGarLUASc6zkZ0ED-HB" : {
        "Answer" : "Indian Muslim League ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:40:19",
        "Option1" : "Congress ",
        "Option2" : "Indian Muslim League ",
        "Option3" : "Constitution of Pakistan ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Maulana Muhammad Ali Johar wrote the first constitution of ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGasMVn5wMjIXN_KbR7" : {
        "Answer" : "Karachi, 1876",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:44:45",
        "Option1" : "Karachi, 1976",
        "Option2" : "Karachi, 1876",
        "Option3" : "Karachi, 1676",
        "Option4" : "Karachi, 1576",
        "Question" : "Quaid e Azam was born in ___ on December 25, ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGats8ANLllfXZwnzrw" : {
        "Answer" : "Knighthood",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:51:21",
        "Option1" : "Knighthood",
        "Option2" : "Knight mare",
        "Option3" : "Rank of knight ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Viceroy Lord Reading offered Muhammad Ali Jinnah ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGauUseazJSpTgwZ3jT" : {
        "Answer" : "Dehli to Karachi ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:54:4",
        "Option1" : "Mumbai to Karachi ",
        "Option2" : "Dehli to Karachi ",
        "Option3" : "Lahore to Karachi ",
        "Option4" : "India to Karachi ",
        "Question" : "Quaid-e-Azam with Mohtarma Fatima Jinnah flew from ___ to ___ on 7 August 1947.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGav1P-Llwls4FZgsy_" : {
        "Answer" : "14 August 1947",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:56:25",
        "Option1" : "14 August 1947",
        "Option2" : "12 August 1948",
        "Option3" : "13 August 1948",
        "Option4" : "7 August 1947",
        "Question" : "Pakistan came into existence on ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGavylQupKbNDGdUqYu" : {
        "Answer" : "1658-1707",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:0:32",
        "Option1" : "1658-1707",
        "Option2" : "1556-1605",
        "Option3" : "1526-1530",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Aurangzeb began to rule from ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGawMpozrqGeKGAnPDH" : {
        "Answer" : "1556-1605",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:2:15",
        "Option1" : "1526-1530",
        "Option2" : "1556-1605",
        "Option3" : "1658-1707",
        "Option4" : "1947-1948",
        "Question" : "Akbar began to rule from.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaxOeA2OP2GwFhaj-4" : {
        "Answer" : "Muhi ud din Aurangzeb Alamgir ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:6:45",
        "Option1" : "Shahab ud din Muhammad Shah jahan ",
        "Option2" : "Muhi ud din Aurangzeb Alamgir ",
        "Option3" : "Zaheer ud din ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The full name of Aurangzeb is ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaxnORDyCVV7TKH670" : {
        "Answer" : "1920",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:8:30",
        "Option1" : "1930",
        "Option2" : "1948",
        "Option3" : "1920",
        "Option4" : "1900",
        "Question" : "Muhammad Ali Jinnah opposed Congress disobedience movement against British power in ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGay9qU1PNFm-3g7l_5" : {
        "Answer" : "Aligarh University ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:10:6",
        "Option1" : "Aligarh University ",
        "Option2" : "Aligarh Madrissah",
        "Option3" : "Aligarh College ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Muhammadan Anglo Oriental College in Aligarh later became ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Urdu" : {
      "-MFnjM6pf3rfVANy7jxP" : {
        "Answer" : "باب الاسلام",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:24:47",
        "Option1" : "باب الاسلام",
        "Option2" : "درہ اسلام",
        "Option3" : "باب یمن",
        "Option4" : "باب کبری",
        "Question" : "س۔1صوبہ سندھ کو کہا جاتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnjshcr38wbNDt5yvU" : {
        "Answer" : "12 ہزار",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:27:5",
        "Option1" : "9 ہزار",
        "Option2" : "10 ہزار",
        "Option3" : "11 ہزار",
        "Option4" : "12 ہزار",
        "Question" : "س2۔محمد بن قاسم کی فوج سپاہیوں پر مشتمل تھی۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnl4frkF52CwZ3pl5k" : {
        "Answer" : "711ء",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:32:20",
        "Option1" : "711ء",
        "Option2" : "710ء",
        "Option3" : "713ء",
        "Option4" : "714ء",
        "Question" : "س4۔محمد بن قاسم نے سندھ پہنچا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmSrIG1gtcZom1--U" : {
        "Answer" : "منجینیق",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:38:22",
        "Option1" : "ٹینک",
        "Option2" : "منجینیق",
        "Option3" : "بلڈوزر",
        "Option4" : "ٹریکٹر",
        "Question" : "مضبوط فیصلوں کو توڑنے والی مشین یے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmvPHRNxGZIoGgPFK" : {
        "Answer" : "بولنےکی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:40:22",
        "Option1" : "بولنےکی",
        "Option2" : "سننےکی",
        "Option3" : "دیکھنےکی",
        "Option4" : "سونگھنےکی",
        "Question" : "اللہ ڈ نو کس صلاحیت سے محروم تھا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnG3xCUCS4Er4qTtS" : {
        "Answer" : "نانی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:41:51",
        "Option1" : "نانی",
        "Option2" : "دادی",
        "Option3" : "خالہ",
        "Option4" : "چچا",
        "Question" : "اللہ ڈ نو کو کس نے پالا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnzrb3fECtCczezJR" : {
        "Answer" : "آگ لگائ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:45:3",
        "Option1" : "مرمت",
        "Option2" : "سنوارا",
        "Option3" : "آگ لگائ",
        "Option4" : "سجایا",
        "Question" : "اللہ ڈ نو نے اپنی جھونپڑی کےساتھ کیا کیا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnoaI2ejJqYiCcLo2r" : {
        "Answer" : "500آدمی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:47:40",
        "Option1" : "600آدمی",
        "Option2" : "500آدمی",
        "Option3" : "400آدمی",
        "Option4" : "700آدمی",
        "Question" : "العروس نامی منجینیق کو کتنے آدمی چلاتے تھے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnpC9XfAPRHAe1nSMD" : {
        "Answer" : "60 ہزار",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:50:19",
        "Option1" : "40 ہزار",
        "Option2" : "50 ہزار",
        "Option3" : "60 ہزار",
        "Option4" : "70 ہزار",
        "Question" : "راجا داہر کی فوج کتنے سپاہیوں پر مشتمل تھی۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnpmYJBXGlM9eAtuej" : {
        "Answer" : "حجاج بن یوسف",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:52:53",
        "Option1" : "حجاج بن یوسف",
        "Option2" : "حجاج بن سیف",
        "Option3" : "حجاج بن قاسم",
        "Option4" : "محمد بن قاسم",
        "Question" : "عراق کا گورنر تھا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnqD12WJNHaWyRWglC" : {
        "Answer" : "مچھلی کا جال",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:54:45",
        "Option1" : "مچھلی کا جال",
        "Option2" : "کشتیاں",
        "Option3" : "دروازے",
        "Option4" : "گھر",
        "Question" : "اللہ ڈ نو بناتا تھا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnr9Chuid_73DJTCqw" : {
        "Answer" : "ثروت سلطانہ ثروت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:58:51",
        "Option1" : "ثروت اعجاز",
        "Option2" : "ثروت سلطانہ ثروت",
        "Option3" : "ثروت صدیقی",
        "Option4" : " ثروت سلطان",
        "Question" : "نظم غصہ کی شاعرہ ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFns1vU5h40CotsClj_" : {
        "Answer" : "دل بہت سخت ہو جانا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:2:44",
        "Option1" : "دل نرم پڑجانا",
        "Option2" : "دل پریشان ہو جانا",
        "Option3" : "دل بہت سخت ہو جانا",
        "Option4" : "دل خوش ہونا",
        "Question" : "دل پتھر بن جانا کا مطلب ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnw-eC8SX1pjSL-9FC" : {
        "Answer" : "نزدیکی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:20:4",
        "Option1" : "دوری",
        "Option2" : "نزدیکی",
        "Option3" : "فاصلہ",
        "Option4" : "ہنگامہ",
        "Question" : "قربت کا مطلب ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnwakJZv_UszPUbaE7" : {
        "Answer" : "انصاف کرنے والا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:22:39",
        "Option1" : "انصاف کرنے والا",
        "Option2" : "لڑائی کرنے والا",
        "Option3" : "مشورہ دینے والا",
        "Option4" : "صلح کرنے والا",
        "Question" : "منصف کا مطلب ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnxneUJd9xq-5K2JsR" : {
        "Answer" : "مچھلیاں پکڑنا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:27:54",
        "Option1" : "مچھلیاں پکانا",
        "Option2" : "مچھلیاں پکڑنا",
        "Option3" : "مچھلیاں پالنا",
        "Option4" : "مچھلیاں بیچنا",
        "Question" : "ماہی گیری کہتے ہیں۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnyBWmUe7fVghU-Si8" : {
        "Answer" : "امن",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:29:37",
        "Option1" : "لڑائی",
        "Option2" : "امن",
        "Option3" : "دوستی",
        "Option4" : "دشمنی",
        "Question" : "جنگ کا متضاد ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnyYgul8dnEyulBZZU" : {
        "Answer" : "انجام",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:31:11",
        "Option1" : "ابتدا",
        "Option2" : "شر",
        "Option3" : "انجام",
        "Option4" : "انتہا",
        "Question" : "آغاز کا متضاد ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnypL1W7MG5_Pu4arf" : {
        "Answer" : "محبت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:32:23",
        "Option1" : "ذلت",
        "Option2" : "ملکیت",
        "Option3" : "محبت",
        "Option4" : "نفرت",
        "Question" : "الفت کا مترادف ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnzGUGtC4Jf_v6GXbL" : {
        "Answer" : "کنجوس",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:34:19",
        "Option1" : "رحم دل",
        "Option2" : "کنجوس",
        "Option3" : "بہادر",
        "Option4" : "نالائق",
        "Question" : "بخیل کا مترادف ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnzkKotw9ymoxbZgG_" : {
        "Answer" : "حسن",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 12:36:25",
        "Option1" : "بد صورت",
        "Option2" : "حیا",
        "Option3" : "حسن",
        "Option4" : "ہمدرد",
        "Question" : "جمال کا مترادف ہو گا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1fm5nU_4_sDJPDF0q" : {
        "Answer" : "خانم",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:3:28",
        "Option1" : "خالہ",
        "Option2" : "خانے",
        "Option3" : "خانم",
        "Option4" : "خانو",
        "Question" : "خان کا مونث ہو گا۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1gSny5dqRjg3t5Azl" : {
        "Answer" : "سوتیلی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:6:27",
        "Option1" : "سوتیلے",
        "Option2" : "سوتیلو",
        "Option3" : "سوتیلی",
        "Option4" : "ستیل",
        "Question" : "سوتیلا کا مونث ہو گا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1iJImM6t8NY5Z1kT2" : {
        "Answer" : "؟",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:14:32",
        "Option1" : "،",
        "Option2" : "۔",
        "Option3" : "؟",
        "Option4" : "!",
        "Question" : "سوالیہ جملوں کے آخر میں آتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1j9iLTMKJTek3-Jo7" : {
        "Answer" : "نہیں",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 9:18:15",
        "Option1" : "نہیں",
        "Option2" : "جی ہاں",
        "Option3" : "ہاں",
        "Option4" : "کیا",
        "Question" : "منفی جملوں میں استعمال ہوتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      }
    }
  },
  "Class VI" : {
    "English" : {
      "-MFnQwz25E4t78OVge6N" : {
        "Answer" : "Anxiously",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:0:0",
        "Option1" : "Anxiously",
        "Option2" : "Absolutly",
        "Option3" : "Mouth",
        "Option4" : "Tongue",
        "Question" : "\"Impatiently\" means.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnRjIOsZfgbt8gIuGe" : {
        "Answer" : "Hunt",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:3:26",
        "Option1" : "Hunt",
        "Option2" : "Anger",
        "Option3" : "Shoot",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "\"Spear\" means.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnS0nx4e1mwJQmJqj3" : {
        "Answer" : "Spread something",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:4:42",
        "Option1" : "Spread something",
        "Option2" : "Egg of pig",
        "Option3" : "Egg of fish",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "\"Fished out\" means.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSMCtR1BaIE73PHD_" : {
        "Answer" : "Cooked at boiling point",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:6:9",
        "Option1" : "Aim at",
        "Option2" : "Don't cook",
        "Option3" : "Cooked at boiling point",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "\"Simmer\" means....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSazko4exHkQPxkTn" : {
        "Answer" : "Yelling",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:7:14",
        "Option1" : "Yelling",
        "Option2" : "Laughing",
        "Option3" : "Hesitating",
        "Option4" : "Asking",
        "Question" : "\"Hollering\" means....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnSzAljIGs709mfO5n" : {
        "Answer" : "Pushed roughly",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:8:53",
        "Option1" : "Shower",
        "Option2" : "Bath",
        "Option3" : "Pushed roughly",
        "Option4" : "Both 1 and 2",
        "Question" : "\"Shoved\" means....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnTDOsMKHmfADp7-67" : {
        "Answer" : "Creep",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:9:55",
        "Option1" : "Creep",
        "Option2" : "Walk",
        "Option3" : "Walk lamely",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "\"Crawl\" means......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnU0HLr2RDL39kn8BU" : {
        "Answer" : "Robin Klein ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:13:24",
        "Option1" : "Irene Chua",
        "Option2" : "Robin Klein ",
        "Option3" : "James Buechler",
        "Option4" : "None of the above",
        "Question" : "\"Penny Pollard's Letters\" are written by..... ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnV1Yq8GaBxhNuss0r" : {
        "Answer" : "Fictional",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:17:51",
        "Option1" : "Fictional",
        "Option2" : "Non-fictional",
        "Option3" : "Funny",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "\"Penny Pollard's Letters\" is a ........collection of letters.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnVNVDNzQoOdVHy-9W" : {
        "Answer" : "Beauty of character ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:19:21",
        "Option1" : "Beauty of character ",
        "Option2" : "Beauty of cloth",
        "Option3" : "Beauty of face",
        "Option4" : "Beauty of house",
        "Question" : "\"Inner beauty\" means...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnWSonfVuMZ733W9JF" : {
        "Answer" : "Lisa",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:24:5",
        "Option1" : "Mrs Bettany",
        "Option2" : "Lisa",
        "Option3" : "Aunt Winifred",
        "Option4" : "To herself",
        "Question" : "Penny teach .......how to crawl.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnWoxNANLpZ4tSfPmE" : {
        "Answer" : "Sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:25:40",
        "Option1" : "Noun ",
        "Option2" : "Sentence",
        "Option3" : "Subject",
        "Option4" : "Verb",
        "Question" : "A group of words which make complete sense is called......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnXBAntqGzTF6t1wHR" : {
        "Answer" : "Statement",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:27:15",
        "Option1" : "Statement",
        "Option2" : "Command",
        "Option3" : "Question",
        "Option4" : "Exclamation",
        "Question" : "A sentence that makes a ......... is called a declarative sentence.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYAkibsg8docJR459" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:31:35",
        "Option1" : "Declarative",
        "Option2" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option3" : "Imperative",
        "Option4" : "Interrogative",
        "Question" : "A sentence that expresses a command is called......... sentence.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYZCEgFbnPuAlUjDJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Exclamatory",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:33:14",
        "Option1" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option2" : "Declarative",
        "Option3" : "Interrogative",
        "Option4" : "Imperative",
        "Question" : "I am so excited! I passed the test.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnYng9C6zhCEKP5aBQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Interrogative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:34:18",
        "Option1" : "Declarative",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative",
        "Option3" : "Imperative",
        "Option4" : "Exclamatory",
        "Question" : "Can you cancel the concert?",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZ7N726njJNubffC0" : {
        "Answer" : "Subject",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:35:42",
        "Option1" : "Subject",
        "Option2" : "Predicate",
        "Option3" : "Sentence",
        "Option4" : "Imperative",
        "Question" : "The part which name a person or a thing we are speaking about is called.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnZei_ev-BExMxZM-Z" : {
        "Answer" : "Borrowed garments is a Subject",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:38:3",
        "Option1" : "Borrowed garments is a Subject",
        "Option2" : "Borrowed garments is a Predicate",
        "Option3" : "Borrowed garments is question",
        "Option4" : "Borrowed garments is Excalamation",
        "Question" : "Borrowed garments never fit well.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_Ct5qiiNa3bh2tZG" : {
        "Answer" : "Catches the worm is predicate",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:40:27",
        "Option1" : "Catches the worm is predicate",
        "Option2" : "Catches the worm is Subject",
        "Option3" : "Catches the worm is Interrogation",
        "Option4" : "Catches the worm is command",
        "Question" : "The early bird catches the worm.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn__fSUytmbFWM9KSV" : {
        "Answer" : "Predicate",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:42:4",
        "Option1" : "Sign of interrogation",
        "Option2" : "Exclamation mark",
        "Option3" : "Predicate",
        "Option4" : "Verb",
        "Question" : "The subject of the sentence usually comes first but occasionally put after...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFn_wouqrXvzgwbEJsZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Predicate",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:43:39",
        "Option1" : "Imperative",
        "Option2" : "Question",
        "Option3" : "Predicate",
        "Option4" : "Noun",
        "Question" : "The part which tells something about the subject is.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnaAYNyK_YAhpGq4Ra" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:44:40",
        "Option1" : "Declarative",
        "Option2" : "Imperative",
        "Option3" : "Question ",
        "Option4" : "Exclamation ",
        "Question" : "Have mercy upon us.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnaXhBGEFrlRDhsLIV" : {
        "Answer" : "Islamabad is Subject",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:46:14",
        "Option1" : "Islamabad is Subject",
        "Option2" : "Islamabad is predicate",
        "Option3" : "Islamabad is question",
        "Option4" : "Islamabad is sentence",
        "Question" : "Islamabad is the capital of Pakistan.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnakHhZaj8UKul68Yt" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:47:10",
        "Option1" : "Interogative",
        "Option2" : "Declarative",
        "Option3" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option4" : "Imperative",
        "Question" : "What a shame!",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Geography" : {
      "-MGamp3j0tJ3WfA8Gmnr" : {
        "Answer" : "3",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:20:34",
        "Option1" : "5",
        "Option2" : "4",
        "Option3" : "3",
        "Option4" : "2",
        "Question" : "Geography is usually divide in to ....main areas of the study",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGapOoPy39yh53hh9JQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Physical  Geogrphy",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:31:48",
        "Option1" : "Physical  Geogrphy",
        "Option2" : "Environmental  Geogrphy",
        "Option3" : "Animals  Geogrphy",
        "Option4" : "Human  Geogrphy",
        "Question" : "The study of the EArth,s Land is called....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaryb4WtBbfZD5oFcZ" : {
        "Answer" : "All  these",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:43:3",
        "Option1" : "Earth",
        "Option2" : "Planet",
        "Option3" : "All  these",
        "Option4" : "Weather",
        "Question" : "Geogrphy is the study of ....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaxvMYbqAatQJF8v40" : {
        "Answer" : "Soil",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:9:3",
        "Option1" : "Sand",
        "Option2" : "Pabbles",
        "Option3" : "Soil",
        "Option4" : "Clay",
        "Question" : "..... Is the top layer of loose Earth in which plants grow.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGazW4_t1XrjoEmQ7Xx" : {
        "Answer" : "Geo",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:16:0",
        "Option1" : "Geo",
        "Option2" : "Galaxy",
        "Option3" : "Debris",
        "Option4" : "Climate",
        "Question" : "The word,s....means Earth.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGfqpMoMqqVKqC_eAbT" : {
        "Answer" : "Environment",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 8:56:10",
        "Option1" : "Social",
        "Option2" : "Environment",
        "Option3" : "Economic",
        "Option4" : "Culture",
        "Question" : "Working in the agriculture and industrial Sectors  are examples of----activities",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGfrg-2F-PiHn3m5iXg" : {
        "Answer" : "Weather",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 8:59:53",
        "Option1" : "Climate",
        "Option2" : "Weather",
        "Option3" : "Season",
        "Option4" : "Polar",
        "Question" : ".....Is the condition of the atmosphere at any given times.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGftEnN9QBMTI_vJ-rk" : {
        "Answer" : "Human",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 9:6:42",
        "Option1" : "Environment",
        "Option2" : "Human",
        "Option3" : "Physical",
        "Option4" : "Resource",
        "Question" : "In.....Geography we study man made features, place and human activities.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGg7xzFJv2p2HCqUNWL" : {
        "Answer" : " Pineapple  plantation",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:15:23",
        "Option1" : "Man grow swamp",
        "Option2" : " Pineapple  plantation",
        "Option3" : "Tropical rainforest",
        "Option4" : "Land",
        "Question" : "Which one of the following is a human feature?",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgKG2yysvUo2UKL3Az" : {
        "Answer" : "Huge land mass formed by the continent of the world",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:9:7",
        "Option1" : "Earth Crust that is broken up due to  Earth quake",
        "Option2" : "Huge land mass formed by the continent of the world",
        "Option3" : "Cretaceous",
        "Option4" : "Mid-Atlantic Ridge",
        "Question" : "What is Pangea?",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgKez2M-jk5iyRL9ce" : {
        "Answer" : "3",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:10:53",
        "Option1" : "2 ",
        "Option2" : "1",
        "Option3" : "4",
        "Option4" : "3",
        "Question" : "The Earth has.....layer,s.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgML8CfX_4oOjSMSSi" : {
        "Answer" : "5000",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:18:12",
        "Option1" : "5000",
        "Option2" : "1000",
        "Option3" : "6000",
        "Option4" : "7000",
        "Question" : "The Earth Crust is soild and the temperatures here can be as high as ..,....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgOGYPtw1ceLjqdr4x" : {
        "Answer" : "_175-400 c",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:26:38",
        "Option1" : "_175-400 c",
        "Option2" : "_275-400 c",
        "Option3" : "_200-400 c",
        "Option4" : "_300--400 c",
        "Question" : "Mercuy is not suitable for living,as it can be as cold as ....c and as hot as.....c",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgPbTcJcmLapxMfzh6" : {
        "Answer" : "70%",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:32:30",
        "Option1" : "75%",
        "Option2" : "70%",
        "Option3" : "65%",
        "Option4" : "90%",
        "Question" : "About....%of the Earth,s surface is covered with water.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgQlIKOOwhP3IEepsu" : {
        "Answer" : "Galaxy",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:37:32",
        "Option1" : "Milkyway",
        "Option2" : "Galaxy",
        "Option3" : "Big Ban",
        "Option4" : "Spiral",
        "Question" : "A......is a community of stars",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgXvr62fuhWdctVfIX" : {
        "Answer" : "30",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:8:50",
        "Option1" : "20",
        "Option2" : "30",
        "Option3" : "40",
        "Option4" : "35",
        "Question" : "The Milkeay is one of the galaxy in a cluster of galaxies called the local Group.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgaZVYYA21v7K4yPs5" : {
        "Answer" : "8",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:24:43",
        "Option1" : "7",
        "Option2" : "8",
        "Option3" : "9",
        "Option4" : "6",
        "Question" : "The  solar system consists of the sun and...planets.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgcMO66TehBfh7mw-k" : {
        "Answer" : "75 %",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:32:34",
        "Option1" : "75 %",
        "Option2" : "95 %",
        "Option3" : "55%",
        "Option4" : "65 %",
        "Question" : "About....% of Earth surface is covered by ocean.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgd354EqEFAGKf_iNU" : {
        "Answer" : "6to70km",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:35:37",
        "Option1" : "3to70km",
        "Option2" : "6to70km",
        "Option3" : "7to70km",
        "Option4" : "9to70km",
        "Question" : "The crust is the outer most layer is solid and....km thick ",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgdfekfWgcVgHPI_x3" : {
        "Answer" : "-214c",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:38:19",
        "Option1" : "-214c",
        "Option2" : "-220c",
        "Option3" : "225c",
        "Option4" : "-225c",
        "Question" : "The sun has an average temperature of ...c while Mecury",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgeLfq1Uurr15CW2VS" : {
        "Answer" : "150 million",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:41:15",
        "Option1" : "300 million",
        "Option2" : "250 million",
        "Option3" : "150 million",
        "Option4" : "200 million",
        "Question" : "Earth Is about ...km away from the Sun.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgm1vxZytCMZyfgJrj" : {
        "Answer" : "Pineapple plantation",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 13:14:51",
        "Option1" : "Man grow seamp",
        "Option2" : "Pineapple plantation",
        "Option3" : " Tropical rainforest",
        "Option4" : "Amazon river",
        "Question" : "Which one of the following is a human feature?",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgn776ELLHcTDiH-Ef" : {
        "Answer" : "_60c",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 13:19:35",
        "Option1" : "+69cl",
        "Option2" : "_50c",
        "Option3" : "_60c",
        "Option4" : "_40c",
        "Question" : "Mars has ....average temperature",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGqINe4VOD9-YbxHKF0" : {
        "Answer" : "Pineapple plantation",
        "Date" : "2020-9-9 21:25:17",
        "Option1" : "Man grow swamp",
        "Option2" : "Pineapple plantation",
        "Option3" : "Mount everest",
        "Option4" : "Tropical rain forest ",
        "Question" : "Which one of the following is the human feature?",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGqIl8fe9B94oqSIcwS" : {
        "Answer" : "15 billions",
        "Date" : "2020-9-9 21:26:57",
        "Option1" : "16 billions",
        "Option2" : "14 billions",
        "Option3" : "15 billions",
        "Option4" : "12 billions",
        "Question" : "Univers came into being about ______ billions years ago?",
        "author" : "ambertahir303@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "History" : {
      "-MGR_qsudnwicLCGTi-E" : {
        "Answer" : "River",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 9:47:42",
        "Option1" : "River",
        "Option2" : "Desert",
        "Option3" : "Mountain",
        "Option4" : "Valleys",
        "Question" : "Civilization began mostly around------",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRaooVDOts4WTFmVDq" : {
        "Answer" : "Aegean sea",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 9:51:55",
        "Option1" : "Red sea",
        "Option2" : "Aegean sea",
        "Option3" : "Caspian sea",
        "Option4" : "Dead sea",
        "Question" : "The ancient Greek civilization which grew around the.....sea.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRbd3dfEvARc_mr4uz" : {
        "Answer" : "Between two rivers",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 9:55:29",
        "Option1" : "Rivers ",
        "Option2" : "Under the water",
        "Option3" : "Between land",
        "Option4" : "Between two rivers",
        "Question" : "Mesopotamian means.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRcWTjjA59ESBo1Oyz" : {
        "Answer" : "Sumerisn",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 9:59:20",
        "Option1" : "Sumerisn",
        "Option2" : "Arbic",
        "Option3" : "English",
        "Option4" : "Latin",
        "Question" : "Mesopotamian language was known as.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGReUSxv2N0UTNrOnwG" : {
        "Answer" : "Code of Hammurabi",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 10:7:56",
        "Option1" : "Code of Hammurabi",
        "Option2" : "Ashura",
        "Option3" : "Pharaohs",
        "Option4" : "Stars",
        "Question" : "Mesopotamian had their own region and law called......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRhxhyH994Uvr2Kb72" : {
        "Answer" : "1700BCE",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 10:23:7",
        "Option1" : "1900BCE",
        "Option2" : "1700BCE",
        "Option3" : "1800BCE",
        "Option4" : "2020BCE",
        "Question" : "Babylonian ruler who rule....BCE.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRiZDlB4GwYOGEzBVE" : {
        "Answer" : "7days",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 10:25:45",
        "Option1" : "6days",
        "Option2" : "5days",
        "Option3" : "8days",
        "Option4" : "7days",
        "Question" : "Sumerisn calendar was based on the.....weak.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRjE01gtQG9SXCHX8o" : {
        "Answer" : "Cuneiform",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 10:28:40",
        "Option1" : "Script",
        "Option2" : "Mayan",
        "Option3" : "Cuneiform",
        "Option4" : "Olmecs",
        "Question" : "Sumerisn was invented a writing called.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRk17X-giBdVqMZyBx" : {
        "Answer" : "Iraq",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 10:32:9",
        "Option1" : "Iran",
        "Option2" : "Iraq",
        "Option3" : "Pskistain",
        "Option4" : "Arab",
        "Question" : "Mesopotamian civilization covers the entire area of modern......today.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRuNXORE5LpY7wBYPi" : {
        "Answer" : "Hanging  Garden",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:17:22",
        "Option1" : "Temples",
        "Option2" : "Hanging  Garden",
        "Option3" : "Carving wall",
        "Option4" : "Stupa",
        "Question" : "Nebuchadnezzar was famous for his one of the seven wonder  the ancient world",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRvDEDV5X5usezBRXL" : {
        "Answer" : "All these answers",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:21:2",
        "Option1" : "Art and architecture",
        "Option2" : "Fine art and language",
        "Option3" : "All these answers",
        "Option4" : "Ari and Science",
        "Question" : "Mesopotamian civilzation is also known for its......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGRwYqT4IlXIwuf8Juh" : {
        "Answer" : "gods",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:26:53",
        "Option1" : "gods",
        "Option2" : "Idols",
        "Option3" : "Fire",
        "Option4" : "Sun",
        "Question" : "Sumerians believed in and worshipped..... They believed were very powerful but were like human.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS-VoQbV9tWnXVyUNq" : {
        "Answer" : "2nd cen",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:44:9",
        "Option1" : "2nd cen",
        "Option2" : "1st cen",
        "Option3" : "4th cen",
        "Option4" : "3rd cen",
        "Question" : "Persia took over many civilization and kingdoms in the....Century Bce",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS0Xvqz9bsWvxXv1I0" : {
        "Answer" : "5000 years",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:48:40",
        "Option1" : "4000 years",
        "Option2" : "5500  yesrs",
        "Option3" : "5000 years",
        "Option4" : "3000 years",
        "Question" : "Nearly..... ago and ancient civilization existed along the River Nile in Egypt.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS1_9ssvrwk5HjuxWo" : {
        "Answer" : "River Nile",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 11:53:11",
        "Option1" : "River Nile",
        "Option2" : "River Indus",
        "Option3" : "Yellow River",
        "Option4" : "Imezon River",
        "Question" : "The....nearly 4000 miles long and is the longest river in the world.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS3yrjnmW1EA5oKx1w" : {
        "Answer" : "Arabic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:3:41",
        "Option1" : "Urdu",
        "Option2" : "Latin",
        "Option3" : "Arabic",
        "Option4" : "Hindi",
        "Question" : "The word \"Mummy\" comes from the....word \"Mumiya\" for corpse.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS4bi352d7O7bXn9DK" : {
        "Answer" : "Pharaoh",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:6:28",
        "Option1" : "King",
        "Option2" : "Pharaoh",
        "Option3" : "Minister",
        "Option4" : "Chief",
        "Question" : "The ruler of Egypt was called.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS5Fqh4Uj34Q7l8ny6" : {
        "Answer" : "2000",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:9:17",
        "Option1" : "4000",
        "Option2" : "3000",
        "Option3" : "2000",
        "Option4" : "5000",
        "Question" : "The ancient Egypt and were had nearly.....gods and goddesses.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS6bBudDOH51ofqlQA" : {
        "Answer" : "Rows and  columus",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:15:10",
        "Option1" : "Top  to batom",
        "Option2" : "Right  to left",
        "Option3" : "Rows and  columus",
        "Option4" : "Only Rows",
        "Question" : "Hieriglyphy are written in......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS7_PhEOgz07nWtn3k" : {
        "Answer" : "1799",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:19:25",
        "Option1" : "1699",
        "Option2" : "1799",
        "Option3" : "1899",
        "Option4" : "1599",
        "Question" : "The Rosetta Stone was found in the Egyptian village of Rashreda near the Nile Delta in ......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGS9pFQqiZg-Gf135zH" : {
        "Answer" : "Lake Tanganyika",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:29:14",
        "Option1" : "Suez Canal",
        "Option2" : "Lake Victoria",
        "Option3" : "Lake Tanganyika",
        "Option4" : "Lake  Tana",
        "Question" : "The source of River Nile is the.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGSBG8qkC-VUkoYO72p" : {
        "Answer" : "French soldiers",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:35:31",
        "Option1" : "Egyptian scribes",
        "Option2" : "British Museum",
        "Option3" : "French soldiers",
        "Option4" : "The city Rashreda,s people",
        "Question" : "The Rosetta Stone was discovered by.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGSFy2LFaSGV_YvnZDa" : {
        "Answer" : "All  these answers",
        "Date" : "2020-9-5 12:56:3",
        "Option1" : "All  these answers",
        "Option2" : "The words of God",
        "Option3" : "Demotic  Language",
        "Option4" : "Magic symbols",
        "Question" : "The ancient Egyptian called hieroglyphs.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGaivY3x1nbdQ2E5LQR" : {
        "Answer" : "Seven  wonder",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 9:3:32",
        "Option1" : "Three  wonder",
        "Option2" : "Five   wonder",
        "Option3" : "Seven  wonder",
        "Option4" : "Two  wonder",
        "Question" : "Pyramids which are counted as the one of the.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgD_2yv4OIqjwNgPsf" : {
        "Answer" : "A mythical creature ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:39:54",
        "Option1" : "An Egyptian monument ",
        "Option2" : "An Egyptian God",
        "Option3" : "A mythical creature ",
        "Option4" : "Idol ",
        "Question" : "The Sphinx is .......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Islamiyat" : {
      "-MGCO4xMaN91FZEUwy0b" : {
        "Answer" : "Oneness",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:57:36",
        "Option1" : "Oneness",
        "Option2" : "Twice",
        "Option3" : "Multiple ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The first principal of islam is belief in the ___ and unity of Allah.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCON5MCKSVjdqH5POc" : {
        "Answer" : "Worthy",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:58:51",
        "Option1" : "Richer",
        "Option2" : "Worthy",
        "Option3" : "Kind",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Allah alone is ___ of worship. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCOnrSW76OqtRcBumf" : {
        "Answer" : "God",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:0:44",
        "Option1" : "God",
        "Option2" : "Godess",
        "Option3" : "Idol",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "There is no ___ but Allah.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCPV6-lnLyUYAf6mbp" : {
        "Answer" : "Quran",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:3:46",
        "Option1" : "Torah",
        "Option2" : "Bible",
        "Option3" : "Quran",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The main emphasis of the ____ is Touhid.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCQFHlgQUUnUShxOrv" : {
        "Answer" : "Several",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:7:3",
        "Option1" : "Several",
        "Option2" : "Twice",
        "Option3" : "One",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "There are ___ verses in Quran which highlight the concept of  Touhid.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCQ_abEMhpwgLZaFbr" : {
        "Answer" : "Partner",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:8:30",
        "Option1" : "Brother ",
        "Option2" : "Sister",
        "Option3" : "Partner",
        "Option4" : "Mother",
        "Question" : "Allah is one and does not have ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCRPReerKNWN3XahAk" : {
        "Answer" : "Last",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:12:7",
        "Option1" : "Second ",
        "Option2" : "Third",
        "Option3" : "Last",
        "Option4" : "Fourth",
        "Question" : "Allah is the first and the ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCRjW4QJEVj5IcsKeG" : {
        "Answer" : "All",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:13:33",
        "Option1" : "All",
        "Option2" : "Power",
        "Option3" : "Knowledge ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "He is incomparable in ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCS9h2XEUdTeQYH4MG" : {
        "Answer" : "Allah",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:15:24",
        "Option1" : "Satan",
        "Option2" : "Allah",
        "Option3" : "Idol",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "We should have firm faith in ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUCjW7eqJsC_SKws1" : {
        "Answer" : "Greatest",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:24:21",
        "Option1" : "Greatest",
        "Option2" : "Huge",
        "Option3" : "Big",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Allah is ___ , No one like Him.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUWquorfzFCbDiYwJ" : {
        "Answer" : "Witness",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:25:43",
        "Option1" : "Witness",
        "Option2" : "Saying",
        "Option3" : "Accept ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "I bear ___ that there is no God but Allah.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUxaR2OqBqDkeuxgZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Respond",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:27:37",
        "Option1" : "Get quite ",
        "Option2" : "Make a noise",
        "Option3" : "Respond",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "It is necessary for Muslim to___ to the Azan.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCVaRYCqrim0Hszdbz" : {
        "Answer" : "Carefully ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:30:25",
        "Option1" : "Don't bother",
        "Option2" : "Carefully ",
        "Option3" : "Sit quiet ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "When Azan is called out, we should listen ___ to it.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCVs0BgKNj--89Sy1h" : {
        "Answer" : "Sleep",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:31:36",
        "Option1" : "Sleep",
        "Option2" : "Play",
        "Option3" : "Singing ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "Prayer is better than ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWzraRqc5CRyXfz2E" : {
        "Answer" : "Ist",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:36:31",
        "Option1" : "2nd",
        "Option2" : "3rd",
        "Option3" : "Ist",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Masjid e Nabvi constructed in the ___ year of Hijrat.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXMkxacxY6XvQaFLe" : {
        "Answer" : "Basic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:38:9",
        "Option1" : "Basic",
        "Option2" : "Final",
        "Option3" : "Last",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The ___ message of Islam is carried five time a day.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXcv6Z6L--yw2Qnel" : {
        "Answer" : "Power",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:39:19",
        "Option1" : "Power",
        "Option2" : "In hand",
        "Option3" : "In command ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "There is no ____ nor might except with Allah.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXsSbdJBydDNOxU1r" : {
        "Answer" : "Key",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:40:23",
        "Option1" : "Key",
        "Option2" : "Lock",
        "Option3" : "Sword ",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "Prayer is the ___ of paradise. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCY7U87PywJ-FMtp08" : {
        "Answer" : "Prayer",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:41:28",
        "Option1" : "Prayer",
        "Option2" : "Fight",
        "Option3" : "Gift",
        "Option4" : "A,B both",
        "Question" : "Come to ___ ,come to success. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCYQfjkmMaWnrR6S4r" : {
        "Answer" : "Four time",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:42:47",
        "Option1" : "3 times",
        "Option2" : "Twice time",
        "Option3" : "Four time",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Allah is great,repeat ___ in Azan.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCYkiLF51KanSv-Ys6" : {
        "Answer" : "Once",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:44:13",
        "Option1" : "Once",
        "Option2" : "Twice ",
        "Option3" : "Four",
        "Option4" : "Two",
        "Question" : "There is no god but Allah.How many times call out in Azan?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZ03I34lEOaiU5AXi" : {
        "Answer" : "Muezzin ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:45:20",
        "Option1" : "Master",
        "Option2" : "Muezzin ",
        "Option3" : "Hajji",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Person, who calls the Azan called ____.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZK41TCJsxTAYotF_" : {
        "Answer" : "Faith",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:46:42",
        "Option1" : "Salat",
        "Option2" : "Touhid",
        "Option3" : "Faith",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Holy Prophet (PBUH) said, the one who responds out of ___.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHKvcmBaEa2PQYTI7P" : {
        "Answer" : "Hazrat Bilal ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:1:54",
        "Option1" : "Hazrat Umar ",
        "Option2" : "Hazrat Bilal ",
        "Option3" : "Hazrat Usman",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "___ was appointed for \"Azan\" by Holy Prophet (PBUH).",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGHLdnsoiLftBAy2Ipx" : {
        "Answer" : "Hazrat Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "Date" : "2020-9-3 10:5:3",
        "Option1" : "Hazrat Adam",
        "Option2" : "Hazrat Usman ",
        "Option3" : "Hazrat Muhammad (PBUH)",
        "Option4" : "Hazrat Ismael ",
        "Question" : "Who is the last Prophet?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Math" : {
      "-MFnjZk_PMrK8LWGRB7p" : {
        "Answer" : "Prime number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:25:43",
        "Option1" : "Prime number",
        "Option2" : "Composite number",
        "Option3" : "Improper number",
        "Option4" : "Estate number",
        "Question" : "The numbers that have only two factors, 1 and the number itself.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnjpnAa4kDnDeP4Gg0" : {
        "Answer" : "Composite number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:26:53",
        "Option1" : "Improper number",
        "Option2" : "Prime number",
        "Option3" : "Composite number",
        "Option4" : "Infinite number",
        "Question" : "The number 87 is a :",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnjzK6hXjb_Eyu4FWz" : {
        "Answer" : "72",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:27:32",
        "Option1" : "76",
        "Option2" : "78",
        "Option3" : "72",
        "Option4" : "74",
        "Question" : "2x2x2x3x3  is the prime factorization of:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnk8bkz5etvIWEU-VH" : {
        "Answer" : "8",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:28:14",
        "Option1" : "6",
        "Option2" : "9",
        "Option3" : "60",
        "Option4" : "8",
        "Question" : "√66 ≈ ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnkGs-DXxNVFgOi5IC" : {
        "Answer" : "90",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:28:48",
        "Option1" : "90",
        "Option2" : "19",
        "Option3" : "91",
        "Option4" : "80",
        "Question" : "2x3x3x5  is the prime factorization of:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnkQ4wHA-e-imW6pdW" : {
        "Answer" : "9",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:29:26",
        "Option1" : "9",
        "Option2" : "8",
        "Option3" : "81",
        "Option4" : "90",
        "Question" : "The nearest evaluation of √80 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnl4GMKJnpoEPnUPmH" : {
        "Answer" : "Prime number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:32:18",
        "Option1" : "Prime number",
        "Option2" : "Composite number",
        "Option3" : "Improper number",
        "Option4" : "Infinite number",
        "Question" : "Determine 29 is a ________ number.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnlCEkx3KIU7yW6y0Y" : {
        "Answer" : "1",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:32:51",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "2",
        "Option3" : "1",
        "Option4" : "3",
        "Question" : "If n x (n + 42) is a prime number, then n = ? ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnlKSHXkR-79pMafCx" : {
        "Answer" : "6",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:33:25",
        "Option1" : "6",
        "Option2" : "40",
        "Option3" : "12",
        "Option4" : "30",
        "Question" : "The HCF of 12 and 30 is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnlVYBjwThzTrNZvVk" : {
        "Answer" : "120",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:34:10",
        "Option1" : "120",
        "Option2" : "240",
        "Option3" : "300",
        "Option4" : "24",
        "Question" : "The Common Multiple (LCM) of the numbers 24 and 30 is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnm0Lu7s2Du82KafMJ" : {
        "Answer" : "792",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:36:24",
        "Option1" : "927",
        "Option2" : "792",
        "Option3" : "729",
        "Option4" : "297",
        "Question" : "2x2x2x3x3x11 = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmFcLf6TXWYTKcgEE" : {
        "Answer" : "2x3x5",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:37:27",
        "Option1" : "2x3x4",
        "Option2" : "2x3x6",
        "Option3" : "2x3x3",
        "Option4" : "2x3x5",
        "Question" : "30 in its prime factors:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmPXUUqxB20WBY9Bf" : {
        "Answer" : "10",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:38:8",
        "Option1" : "10",
        "Option2" : "20",
        "Option3" : "12",
        "Option4" : "2",
        "Question" : "A car covers 2m in 1 minute. It can cover 20m in ____ minutes.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmaul3Aq6kjzX7qY_" : {
        "Answer" : "Negative number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:38:58",
        "Option1" : "Prime number",
        "Option2" : "Negative number",
        "Option3" : "Infinite number",
        "Option4" : "Postive number",
        "Question" : "-0.3 is a_________.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmoifslNOCjMvGYZH" : {
        "Answer" : "<",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:39:55",
        "Option1" : "<",
        "Option2" : ">",
        "Option3" : "=",
        "Option4" : "!",
        "Question" : "16 _____60. Put an appropriate symbol.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnmyxSIVGyOCMiIoG9" : {
        "Answer" : ">",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:40:37",
        "Option1" : "<",
        "Option2" : "@",
        "Option3" : ">",
        "Option4" : "=",
        "Question" : "-11_____-11.5. Put an appropriate symbol.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnCgd9pGRU9H8Z0u1" : {
        "Answer" : "-273.15",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:41:37",
        "Option1" : "-273.15",
        "Option2" : "-273.25",
        "Option3" : "-273.35",
        "Option4" : "-273.45",
        "Question" : "Absolute zero as 0 Kelvin is =  ____°C",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnKXvLNN6wY5BeEtG" : {
        "Answer" : "0",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:42:9",
        "Option1" : "1",
        "Option2" : "2",
        "Option3" : "11",
        "Option4" : "0",
        "Question" : "On a number line, the number between -1 and 1 is____.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnnTva1Rw2hef_Etrz" : {
        "Answer" : "+60",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:42:48",
        "Option1" : "-60",
        "Option2" : "+6",
        "Option3" : "+60",
        "Option4" : "-6",
        "Question" : "If clockwise rotation is -60, then anti-clock wise rotations will be_____.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnngijYdrBox3UO7GN" : {
        "Answer" : "Positive number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:43:44",
        "Option1" : "Improper number",
        "Option2" : "Negative number",
        "Option3" : "Positive number",
        "Option4" : "Infinite number",
        "Question" : "The number ‘4’ is a ___________.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnntsr6282HkCqOe7C" : {
        "Answer" : "Composite number",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:44:38",
        "Option1" : "Prime number",
        "Option2" : "Infinite number",
        "Option3" : "Improper number",
        "Option4" : "Composite number",
        "Question" : "The number 100 is a :",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFno03_Zqe-KDGe546X" : {
        "Answer" : "36",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:45:8",
        "Option1" : "36",
        "Option2" : "26",
        "Option3" : "60",
        "Option4" : "30",
        "Question" : "2x2x3x3  is the prime factorization of:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFno779gHr9rZmj3eYM" : {
        "Answer" : "-4",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:45:37",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "-2",
        "Option3" : "-8",
        "Option4" : "-4",
        "Question" : "On a number line, the number between -5 and -3 is____.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnoEYxA5GMs3sxmCIY" : {
        "Answer" : "3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:46:7",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "8",
        "Option4" : "10",
        "Question" : "√9 ≈ ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnoK8QZTbp8rPVJSj3" : {
        "Answer" : "10",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:46:30",
        "Option1" : "10",
        "Option2" : "100",
        "Option3" : "99",
        "Option4" : "102",
        "Question" : "√101 ≈ ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Science" : {
      "-MG7FQqbNMoOSrUx3uEs" : {
        "Answer" : "Scientist",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:1:42",
        "Option1" : "Painter",
        "Option2" : "Photographer",
        "Option3" : "Scientist",
        "Option4" : "Artist",
        "Question" : "………… needs to know the science of mixing colors and painting materials.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7FjZa-zx6v57Yhfhd" : {
        "Answer" : "Scientific research",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:3:2",
        "Option1" : "Medical research",
        "Option2" : "Scientific research",
        "Option3" : "Chemical research",
        "Option4" : "Forest research",
        "Question" : "Our fight against diseases has largely been carried by…………… ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7FwndZqJNxW09riAu" : {
        "Answer" : "Air and water pollution",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:3:57",
        "Option1" : "Sea pollution",
        "Option2" : "Noise pollution",
        "Option3" : "Land pollution",
        "Option4" : "Air and water pollution",
        "Question" : "Scientists are continuously making use of science and technology to solve global problems such as global warming and…………….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7GBgGB_BG9-T1z1qk" : {
        "Answer" : "Science ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:5:2",
        "Option1" : "Medical",
        "Option2" : "Science ",
        "Option3" : "Forestery",
        "Option4" : "Pharmacology",
        "Question" : "…………… is not just for scientist.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7GmwUGNBaaHSwyM3X" : {
        "Answer" : "Out space",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:7:38",
        "Option1" : "Out space",
        "Option2" : "Empty space",
        "Option3" : "Inner space",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "Science is the study of stars, planets, moons and other objects or phenomena in …………. ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7H48FZPBwUPzSA-T-" : {
        "Answer" : "Geology",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:8:53",
        "Option1" : "Physiologyy",
        "Option2" : "Technology",
        "Option3" : "Geology",
        "Option4" : "Biology ",
        "Question" : "……………… is the study the structures of Earth.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7HMB7baySeZlDlbX8" : {
        "Answer" : "Physics",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:10:7",
        "Option1" : "Physics",
        "Option2" : "Chemistry",
        "Option3" : "Biology",
        "Option4" : "Biochemistry",
        "Question" : "………………… is the study of matter.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7HbzH0OArLKWCYXBq" : {
        "Answer" : "Living things ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:11:16",
        "Option1" : "Space",
        "Option2" : "Matter",
        "Option3" : "Nonliving things",
        "Option4" : "Living things ",
        "Question" : "Biology is the study of ……….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7L8MnK-xKMjQVRFav" : {
        "Answer" : "Isaac Newton",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:26:39",
        "Option1" : "Louis Pasteur",
        "Option2" : "Ibne Heshim",
        "Option3" : "Isaac Newton",
        "Option4" : "Marie Curie",
        "Question" : "…………….. studied the forces and the motion of objects and formulated the laws of motion.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7LSSKNUyZmR_4ipui" : {
        "Answer" : "Communication",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:28:1",
        "Option1" : "Curiosity",
        "Option2" : "Observation",
        "Option3" : "Communication",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "…………… is the skill which involves transmitting and recovering information presented in various places.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7OxkkIYM4qjVYwr4r" : {
        "Answer" : "Sensory",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:43:20",
        "Option1" : "Sight",
        "Option2" : "Taste",
        "Option3" : "Sensory",
        "Option4" : "Hearing",
        "Question" : "The scientists make careful and accurate observations with their ………… organs.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7PELExlow_1T9ubsM" : {
        "Answer" : "Inferring",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:44:32",
        "Option1" : "Inferring",
        "Option2" : "Conclusion",
        "Option3" : "Art and craft",
        "Option4" : "Bio chemical",
        "Question" : "…………… is the skill of drawing conclusion from observations or information gathered.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7PQaERHWDxTSsxOPS" : {
        "Answer" : "65",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:45:22",
        "Option1" : "67",
        "Option2" : "65",
        "Option3" : "63",
        "Option4" : "72",
        "Question" : " Dinosaurs became extinct …………… million years ago.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7PkeeJn6Os0QaHqnf" : {
        "Answer" : "Inferences",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:46:48",
        "Option1" : "Coherences",
        "Option2" : "Comerences",
        "Option3" : "Inferences",
        "Option4" : "Differences\t",
        "Question" : "The conclusion that you draw by inferring are called………….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7PzIgva_AIVmaop39" : {
        "Answer" : "Cell phone",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:47:48",
        "Option1" : "Television",
        "Option2" : "Computer",
        "Option3" : "Cell phone",
        "Option4" : "Internet",
        "Question" : "……………… makes communication easier.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7QDNXvdvtWCr1S3nM" : {
        "Answer" : "Marie Curie",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:48:50",
        "Option1" : "Isaac Newton",
        "Option2" : "Alberuni",
        "Option3" : "Marie Curie",
        "Option4" : "Louis Pasteur",
        "Question" : "…………… discovered and studied the nature of radium.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7QU64KMJlQcuvztj9" : {
        "Answer" : "Science and technology",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:49:58",
        "Option1" : "Science and technology",
        "Option2" : "Cell phone",
        "Option3" : "Media",
        "Option4" : "Computer",
        "Question" : "…………… cannot prevent earthquakes.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7QdtrFFKOVjaK4_rY" : {
        "Answer" : "1931",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:50:43",
        "Option1" : "1831",
        "Option2" : "1931",
        "Option3" : "1947",
        "Option4" : "1843",
        "Question" : "Thomas Edison was died in ……………",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7QsupUAYavh4JTpRZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Scientists",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:51:44",
        "Option1" : "Human beings",
        "Option2" : "Electritions",
        "Option3" : "Inventers\t",
        "Option4" : "Scientists",
        "Question" : "Science and technology have been misused or abused by ………….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7R8rQgM6W3BHW7ZLq" : {
        "Answer" : "Technology ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:52:54",
        "Option1" : "Computer technology",
        "Option2" : "Technology ",
        "Option3" : "Bio technology",
        "Option4" : "Science technology",
        "Question" : "The internet, cloning of animals, genetically modified food, man-made satellites and computer chips are all products of …….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7RRYQDOPHSI6aFq3I" : {
        "Answer" : "Jane Goodall",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:54:10",
        "Option1" : "Jane Goodall",
        "Option2" : "Marie Curie",
        "Option3" : "Louis Pasteur",
        "Option4" : "Isaac Newton\t",
        "Question" : "……… , British scientist, studied wild chimpanzees in their natural habitat in Africa.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7RcJ_iyqk8W3Ta5jZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Investigations",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 11:54:58",
        "Option1" : "Reforms",
        "Option2" : "Athletics",
        "Option3" : "Investigations",
        "Option4" : "Arts ",
        "Question" : "Much of the scientific knowledge that we have is the result of the numerous ……….",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCFcg6DXI21JOtmLVF" : {
        "Answer" : "Teacher's",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:20:39",
        "Option1" : "Teacher's",
        "Option2" : "Colleague's",
        "Option3" : "Monitor's",
        "Option4" : "Friend's",
        "Question" : "Do not enter the laboratory without your....... permission.",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCG-ZTJWpJGAhWb8ag" : {
        "Answer" : "Goggles",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:22:17",
        "Option1" : "Mask",
        "Option2" : "Goggles",
        "Option3" : "Nose cap",
        "Option4" : "Gloves",
        "Question" : "Wear...... when mixing or heating the chemicals.",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCGRDv8wzzSokcPGAC" : {
        "Answer" : "Inference ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:24:10",
        "Option1" : "Inference ",
        "Option2" : "Difference ",
        "Option3" : "Commerce ",
        "Option4" : "Coherence ",
        "Question" : "The conclusions that you draw by inferring are called......",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Urdu" : {
      "-MG1tCR5sdnieDOsfjom" : {
        "Answer" : "مال روڈ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:2:7",
        "Option1" : "مال روڈ",
        "Option2" : "ہال روڈ",
        "Option3" : "پنڈی پوائنٹ",
        "Option4" : "کشمیر پوائنٹ",
        "Question" : "مری میں واقع مرکزی سڑک کا نام ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1uC8ub1CPsnYQVtEx" : {
        "Answer" : "انگریزوں نے",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:6:28",
        "Option1" : "مغلوں نے",
        "Option2" : "سکھوں نے",
        "Option3" : "پٹھانوں نے",
        "Option4" : "انگریزوں نے",
        "Question" : "انیسویں صدی کی تیسری دہائی میں مری میں بیس کیمپ کس نے بنایا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1ulqlymWNSFUyaihv" : {
        "Answer" : "پنجاب",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:8:59",
        "Option1" : "خیبرپختونخواہ",
        "Option2" : "پنجاب",
        "Option3" : "بلوچستان",
        "Option4" : "کشمیر",
        "Question" : "مری کس علاقے کا تاریخی اور پہاڑی مقام ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1vdEPiVQWDJu4_E_a" : {
        "Answer" : "نوکر کو",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:12:45",
        "Option1" : "بیٹے کو",
        "Option2" : "پوتے کو",
        "Option3" : "نوکرانی کو",
        "Option4" : "نوکر کو",
        "Question" : "اشتہارات ضرورت نہیں ہے کہ\"میں بزرگ فہمائش کر رہے تھے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1wTOGNjWQI6YCN5lc" : {
        "Answer" : "بخار کا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:16:23",
        "Option1" : "نزلے کا",
        "Option2" : "بخار کا",
        "Option3" : "سر درد کا",
        "Option4" : "کھانسی کا",
        "Question" : "آقا پر کس بیمار ی کا حملہ ہوا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2-EInf3s935efE5H8" : {
        "Answer" : " ٹھیکے کا انتظامات، پلاٹ اور مکان بیچنا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:32:50",
        "Option1" : "تعلیم دینا،کتابیں بیچنا",
        "Option2" : " ٹھیکے کا انتظامات، پلاٹ اور مکان بیچنا",
        "Option3" : "دودھ اور دہی بیچنا، گائے خریدنا",
        "Option4" : "فصلیں کاشت کرنا، سیاست دان بننا",
        "Question" : "اخبارات میں چھپنے والے اشتہارات کی فہرست ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG20gXwg-9QFvnUo7TG" : {
        "Answer" : "عظمت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:39:12",
        "Option1" : "عظمت",
        "Option2" : "خوش نمائی",
        "Option3" : "پائیداری",
        "Option4" : "عزت",
        "Question" : "اللہ کی بنائی ہوئی ہر چیز سے ظاہر ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG21Dg0riBfzZZc_4fv" : {
        "Answer" : "اسمعیل میرٹھی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:41:32",
        "Option1" : "حفیظجالندھری",
        "Option2" : "اسمعیل میرٹھی",
        "Option3" : "احمد ندیم قاسمی",
        "Option4" : "غالب",
        "Question" : "حمد کے شاعر ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2EgZ8Uv0co6Rs_gAQ" : {
        "Answer" : "چٹک",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:40:22",
        "Option1" : "کھل",
        "Option2" : "مرجھا",
        "Option3" : "چٹک",
        "Option4" : "جھوم",
        "Question" : "ننھی کلیاں ۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔رہی ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2FA18wohnrAhD8ZpO" : {
        "Answer" : "خوشبو",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:42:26",
        "Option1" : "بدبو",
        "Option2" : "خوشبو",
        "Option3" : "نایاب",
        "Option4" : "نادر",
        "Question" : "عطر کا مطلب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2FjNHX8_HLGK5BJzM" : {
        "Answer" : "ٹھنڈا",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:44:55",
        "Option1" : "ٹھنڈا",
        "Option2" : "گرم",
        "Option3" : "متعدل",
        "Option4" : "ابرآلود",
        "Question" : "خنک کا مطلب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2M_dWeMYdmWygDTAF" : {
        "Answer" : "دوری",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:14:51",
        "Option1" : "قربت",
        "Option2" : "نزدیکی",
        "Option3" : "ملاپ",
        "Option4" : "دوری",
        "Question" : "مسافت کا مطلب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2NEab7meYvRgPRRVZ" : {
        "Answer" : "قابل",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:17:43",
        "Option1" : "قابل",
        "Option2" : "بیوقوف",
        "Option3" : "بدمعاش",
        "Option4" : "شوقین",
        "Question" : "حاذق کا مطلب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2O0H9C30cVI5LXAqc" : {
        "Answer" : "دوست",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:21:6",
        "Option1" : "دوست",
        "Option2" : "دشمن",
        "Option3" : "سرپرست",
        "Option4" : "معتبر",
        "Question" : "حبیب کا مترادف ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2PuKyzDXRuFvEQ6Jd" : {
        "Answer" : "افراتفری",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:29:22",
        "Option1" : "بربادی",
        "Option2" : "جلدبازی",
        "Option3" : "حقارت",
        "Option4" : "افراتفری",
        "Question" : "انتشار کا مترادف ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2QQszwph9NBpASnYZ" : {
        "Answer" : "گھونسلہ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:31:39",
        "Option1" : "چمن",
        "Option2" : "گھونسلہ",
        "Option3" : "درخت",
        "Option4" : "قفس",
        "Question" : "آشیانہ کا مترادف ہو گا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2RcUEK9cNHwGC-L-T" : {
        "Answer" : "ضرورت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:36:53",
        "Option1" : "بھروسہ",
        "Option2" : "اعتماد",
        "Option3" : "ضرورت",
        "Option4" : "افادیت",
        "Question" : "احتیاج کا مترادف ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2S4tIdLl52wRVlnay" : {
        "Answer" : "احترام",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:38:54",
        "Option1" : "تقریر",
        "Option2" : "تربیت",
        "Option3" : "توصیف",
        "Option4" : "احترام",
        "Question" : "تعظیم کا مترادف ہو گا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2TENP9MLUDyBwFwJ9" : {
        "Answer" : "زرخیز",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:43:55",
        "Option1" : "زرخیز",
        "Option2" : "ویراں",
        "Option3" : "صحرا",
        "Option4" : "نرم",
        "Question" : "بنجر کا متضاد ہے ",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2TZCo0MVo8L3C6pJ1" : {
        "Answer" : "نقلی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:45:20",
        "Option1" : "خالص",
        "Option2" : "اصل",
        "Option3" : "نقلی",
        "Option4" : "ملتا جلتا",
        "Question" : "اصلی کا متضاد ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2TwXmZzGj5S-d-cr5" : {
        "Answer" : "بد امنی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:46:59",
        "Option1" : "بد امنی",
        "Option2" : "لڑائی",
        "Option3" : "سازش",
        "Option4" : "جھگڑا",
        "Question" : "امن کا متضاد ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2V5CDW5HglCUyL9K5" : {
        "Answer" : "پستی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:52:1",
        "Option1" : "نیچے",
        "Option2" : "اوپر",
        "Option3" : "گہرائی",
        "Option4" : "پستی",
        "Question" : "بلندی کا متضاد ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2VQ8knudMTNnLfvob" : {
        "Answer" : "انجام",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:53:27",
        "Option1" : "ابتدا",
        "Option2" : "انجام",
        "Option3" : "آمد",
        "Option4" : "انتہا",
        "Question" : "آغاز کا متضاد ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2VyNFW6GSzljDz6oK" : {
        "Answer" : "حکمت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 12:55:52",
        "Option1" : "حکمت",
        "Option2" : "عقل",
        "Option3" : "خوش نمائی",
        "Option4" : "قدرت",
        "Question" : "۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔سے نہیں ہے کوئ خالی",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGayybgy16x0XbhFQ5H" : {
        "Answer" : "ڈالی",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:13:39",
        "Option1" : "ڈالی",
        "Option2" : "تالی",
        "Option3" : "بالی ",
        "Option4" : "جالی",
        "Question" : "میوے سے کیا چیز لدی ہوئ ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      }
    }
  },
  "Class VII" : {
    "English" : {
      "-MFi7S85MXC9YDM7o6lF" : {
        "Answer" : "Starvation",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:16:42",
        "Option1" : "Clever",
        "Option2" : "Starvation",
        "Option3" : "Complained",
        "Option4" : "Naughty",
        "Question" : "The meaning of \"famine\" is.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi802dgtiRvcNtQ9Qj" : {
        "Answer" : "Talkative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:19:9",
        "Option1" : "Talkative",
        "Option2" : "Collected",
        "Option3" : "Big",
        "Option4" : "Bossy",
        "Question" : "\"Chatty\" means....\n",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi8J6iBX4lu3i8XlEb" : {
        "Answer" : "Clever",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:20:27",
        "Option1" : "Clever",
        "Option2" : "Fungus",
        "Option3" : "Representative",
        "Option4" : "Boom",
        "Question" : "\"Cunning\" means",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi8ejc2dRPvztILswH" : {
        "Answer" : "Offer as a start",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:22:0",
        "Option1" : "Small offer",
        "Option2" : "Huge offer",
        "Option3" : "Offer as a start",
        "Option4" : "Information",
        "Question" : "\"Introductory offer\" means...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi8xmGVRzlSVvT5Y2s" : {
        "Answer" : "Dissatisfied",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:23:18",
        "Option1" : "Dissatisfied",
        "Option2" : "Disagree",
        "Option3" : "Dismiss",
        "Option4" : "Discover",
        "Question" : "\"Disappointed\" means....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi9B_Sx-CBNAq4Rm6u" : {
        "Answer" : "React",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:24:18",
        "Option1" : "Reach",
        "Option2" : "Question",
        "Option3" : "React",
        "Option4" : "Relaunch",
        "Question" : "\"Respond\" means...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFi9OetU3HWzo7KwDRT" : {
        "Answer" : "Effect",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:25:12",
        "Option1" : "Effect",
        "Option2" : "React",
        "Option3" : "Infact",
        "Option4" : "Text",
        "Question" : "\"Impact\" means...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiBvpCdR6HdA78-eig" : {
        "Answer" : "African folktale",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:36:17",
        "Option1" : "Indian folktale",
        "Option2" : "Russian folktale",
        "Option3" : "Chinese folktale ",
        "Option4" : "African folktale",
        "Question" : "\"Why the tortoise's shell is not smooth\" is adapted from....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiC_EwYDpwP_RRtW_G" : {
        "Answer" : "He didn't eat anything because of famine",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:39:6",
        "Option1" : "He didn't eat anything because of famine",
        "Option2" : "He was ill",
        "Option3" : "He has no house ",
        "Option4" : "He has no friends",
        "Question" : "Tortoise's throat began to itch at the thought of feast because...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiCljfue1Tnlf1u3V3" : {
        "Answer" : "Parrot",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:39:58",
        "Option1" : "Parrot",
        "Option2" : "Pigeon ",
        "Option3" : "Crow",
        "Option4" : "Owl",
        "Question" : "Tortoise gave his message to...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiCzNcYKLVfBAYo0IC" : {
        "Answer" : "All of you",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:40:53",
        "Option1" : "All of you",
        "Option2" : "All of me",
        "Option3" : "All for you",
        "Option4" : "For me only",
        "Question" : "What was tortoise adopted name",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiDg-IQ4An0MGnDIYS" : {
        "Answer" : "Interrogative ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:43:56",
        "Option1" : "Declarative",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative ",
        "Option3" : "Imperative ",
        "Option4" : "Exclamtory ",
        "Question" : "Is purple the best choice of colour for your hair? ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiDyI5YKRcAFSm2nPO" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:45:11",
        "Option1" : "Imperative",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative",
        "Option3" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option4" : "Declarative ",
        "Question" : "Take the trash out.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiELmdw8dvCL-ahryI" : {
        "Answer" : "Declarative ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:46:52",
        "Option1" : "Declarative ",
        "Option2" : "Interrogative",
        "Option3" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option4" : "Imperative ",
        "Question" : "I just finished reading that book.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiEma-hwVnzf8DudWD" : {
        "Answer" : "John is subject ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:48:46",
        "Option1" : "John is predicate",
        "Option2" : "John is subject ",
        "Option3" : "John is both subject and predicate",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "John went to the movie with his friend.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiFMZWpjWrChtGWyDk" : {
        "Answer" : "Predicate ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:51:17",
        "Option1" : "Subject",
        "Option2" : "Predicate ",
        "Option3" : "Both",
        "Option4" : "Non of these ",
        "Question" : "...... part of sentence tells what action the subject does.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiFdRMwcXFWhG8oaay" : {
        "Answer" : "Statement ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:52:30",
        "Option1" : "Statement ",
        "Option2" : "Command",
        "Option3" : "Exclamation ",
        "Option4" : "Question ",
        "Question" : "Declarative makes...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiFu9u7AhD8dd-h0BL" : {
        "Answer" : "Phrase ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:53:39",
        "Option1" : "Phrase ",
        "Option2" : "Clause ",
        "Option3" : "Subject ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "A group of words which make sense but not complete sense is called...",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiGKdcoeangOYjqpAW" : {
        "Answer" : "Clause",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:55:31",
        "Option1" : "Phrase",
        "Option2" : "Clause",
        "Option3" : "Predicate",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "A part of sentence which contains a subject and a predicate is called....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiH-LG2Z80gMZCY-v8" : {
        "Answer" : "Sentence",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 9:58:26",
        "Option1" : "Sentence",
        "Option2" : "Subject",
        "Option3" : "Noun ",
        "Option4" : "Predicate",
        "Question" : "A group of words which makes complete sense is called....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiHQ_EY4vu8b7kpCJn" : {
        "Answer" : "Four",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:0:18",
        "Option1" : "Four",
        "Option2" : "Three",
        "Option3" : "Two",
        "Option4" : "One",
        "Question" : "Sentences are  of ...... kinds ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiHteYykaajuAb6PWG" : {
        "Answer" : "Imperative",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:2:21",
        "Option1" : "Imperative",
        "Option2" : "Exclamatory",
        "Option3" : "Declarative",
        "Option4" : "Interrogative",
        "Question" : "A sentence that expresses a command is called.... ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiIFMTCcvKGxewv8Pm" : {
        "Answer" : "Beaten hard",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:3:54",
        "Option1" : "Beaten hard",
        "Option2" : "Love able",
        "Option3" : "Irritable ",
        "Option4" : "Master",
        "Question" : "\"Pounded\" means....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiI_UUIxzUhUibQXbH" : {
        "Answer" : "Oily tongue ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:5:20",
        "Option1" : "Oily tongue ",
        "Option2" : "Money",
        "Option3" : "Gift",
        "Option4" : "Family",
        "Question" : "Tortoise convinced the birds through his....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFiIo0fj9ff3HgaXE2c" : {
        "Answer" : "Moral lesson",
        "Date" : "2020-8-27 10:6:20",
        "Option1" : "Moral lesson",
        "Option2" : "Smell",
        "Option3" : "Name",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "Traditional stories has a strong....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Geography" : {
      "-MGgKYXfVsbmS4rmfG0B" : {
        "Answer" : "1,250",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:10:22",
        "Option1" : "1,250",
        "Option2" : "11,250",
        "Option3" : "1,350",
        "Option4" : "1,120",
        "Question" : "The inner core is soiled and is about-------km thick.",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgLThWowyEKSxCAKAn" : {
        "Answer" : "Iron",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:14:25",
        "Option1" : "Iron",
        "Option2" : "Nickel",
        "Option3" : "Steel",
        "Option4" : "Silver",
        "Question" : "The inner core is made up entirely if--------",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgLVOeAbgvm9zpVu7N" : {
        "Answer" : "Semi solid and hot",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:14:32",
        "Option1" : "Solid and hard made up mainly of iron",
        "Option2" : "Semi solid and hot",
        "Option3" : "Vigid,made up of very dense rocks",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The mantle of the Earth can be described as.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgMYd6QgagAPgJFzyj" : {
        "Answer" : "Lower part to upwards",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:19:7",
        "Option1" : "Lower part to upwards",
        "Option2" : "Upwards to lower part",
        "Option3" : "Lower part to lower art",
        "Option4" : "Upper part to upper part",
        "Question" : "Convection current are formed in the mantle,current flow-------",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgMk_DWvihr7FsfhBD" : {
        "Answer" : "Rotation of the Earth ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:20:1",
        "Option1" : "Elliptical shape of the Earth ",
        "Option2" : "Rotation of the Earth ",
        "Option3" : "Tilt of the Earth ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The postion of the sun changes with in a day due to the following. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgMuVjtzsLjIp_Cpnr" : {
        "Answer" : "Older",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:20:41",
        "Option1" : "New rocks",
        "Option2" : "Broken ",
        "Option3" : "Older",
        "Option4" : "Short",
        "Question" : "The continental plates are made up of --------rocks",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgNQQUFJ1mTA3UKA67" : {
        "Answer" : "250km",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:22:56",
        "Option1" : "250km",
        "Option2" : "350km",
        "Option3" : "450km",
        "Option4" : "400km",
        "Question" : "The solar system around the milky way galaxy speed is ------km.",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgOTmTEtBFMFCLWVeJ" : {
        "Answer" : "1,670",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 11:27:31",
        "Option1" : "1,670",
        "Option2" : "2,670",
        "Option3" : "1,870",
        "Option4" : "1,500",
        "Question" : "The earth actually spins or rotates at --------'km per hour",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgXD_CIAVaavoPdvGc" : {
        "Answer" : "The interior of Earth is hot",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:5:45",
        "Option1" : "The interior of Earth is hot",
        "Option2" : "The temperature increases Earth core",
        "Option3" : "The Earth's mantle is hottest ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Which of the following statement about the interior of the Earth is true?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgYYuf-m9lnGWQNl6V" : {
        "Answer" : "Distribute the temperature in the core",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:11:35",
        "Option1" : "Distribute the denser rocks to area of...",
        "Option2" : "Distribute the temperature in the core",
        "Option3" : "Enable volcanoes to erupt",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "The convection currents in the the mantle help in the following way.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgZYl0Pd_ZWVQjq9zT" : {
        "Answer" : "Days and night",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:15:56",
        "Option1" : "Days and night",
        "Option2" : "Days are longer",
        "Option3" : "Nights are longer",
        "Option4" : "1,2 both",
        "Question" : "Places near the equator have ___ and ___. ",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGg_GrLnpUE_HNoKFE2" : {
        "Answer" : "24 hours to complete one rotation ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:19:5",
        "Option1" : "Its rotates an axis about tilted 23.5°",
        "Option2" : "The rotation east to west",
        "Option3" : "24 hours to complete one rotation ",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Which of the following facts about the Earth rotation are correct?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgaN6ySVrdUIKxT3aP" : {
        "Answer" : "Equal amount",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:23:52",
        "Option1" : "Equal amount",
        "Option2" : "Lean North",
        "Option3" : "Lean South",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "Around 21 March is the-------equinox means",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgaq5b_KHJRYWyaeUx" : {
        "Answer" : "Day and night",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:25:55",
        "Option1" : "Day and night",
        "Option2" : "Season come",
        "Option3" : "Year complete",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "When rotation of the earth spins west to east it happens",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgb2b7w2pd_ztpv_8x" : {
        "Answer" : "The Northern Hemisphere leans to sun",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:26:51",
        "Option1" : "The sun shifts toward Arctic circle",
        "Option2" : "The Northern Hemisphere leans to sun",
        "Option3" : "Earth closest to the sun",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "On ths 21 June, it is officially summer in the Nothern Hemisphere on this day which of the following occur.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgbpWiq_jw8ZkwufYo" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:30:15",
        "Option1" : "2",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "4",
        "Option4" : "6",
        "Question" : "The earth is divided in to ------- halves called hemispheres",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgcqCPT23imSbjYvs5" : {
        "Answer" : "Days are shorter in Northern Hemisphere ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:34:40",
        "Option1" : "Days are shorter in Northern Hemisphere ",
        "Option2" : "Days and night are equal ",
        "Option3" : "The Antarctic doesn't see the sum",
        "Option4" : "None of these ",
        "Question" : "Which of the following happens during the winter Solstice?",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgd1aSn9sWT4ZznPxq" : {
        "Answer" : "Season",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:35:30",
        "Option1" : "Weather",
        "Option2" : "Season",
        "Option3" : "Climate",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "------are caused by the till of the earth and the earth'revolution is called",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgdJm6UElGV7IANI-v" : {
        "Answer" : "5 to 60",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:36:45",
        "Option1" : "5 to 60",
        "Option2" : "6 to 60",
        "Option3" : "7 to 60",
        "Option4" : "1,2 both",
        "Question" : "The crust is the outer most layer of the Earth is ___ km thickness.",
        "author" : "sadiamurtaza007@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgdbfhfXDOgZ7JJvcu" : {
        "Answer" : "0.5",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:38:2",
        "Option1" : "0.8",
        "Option2" : "0.6",
        "Option3" : "0.7",
        "Option4" : "0.5",
        "Question" : "The earth's rotation speed per second is -------",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgeFvyJ0XAH2FXkvjS" : {
        "Answer" : "3,7000c°",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:40:51",
        "Option1" : "3,7000c°",
        "Option2" : "2,7000c°",
        "Option3" : "4,7000c°",
        "Option4" : "3,5000c°",
        "Question" : "Inner core temperature is greater than --------",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgegCZ7mCw746wOKHd" : {
        "Answer" : "Orbit",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:42:44",
        "Option1" : "Orbit",
        "Option2" : "Revolution",
        "Option3" : "Spins",
        "Option4" : "None of these",
        "Question" : "The path around the sun is known as an-----'",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgf9WoNCo8lnW6q4bT" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:44:48",
        "Option1" : "4",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "2",
        "Option4" : "5",
        "Question" : "The continental drift theory has ------type of plate",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgfXBxCtIj8FvJ2nHH" : {
        "Answer" : "Mantle",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 12:46:25",
        "Option1" : "Core",
        "Option2" : "Curst",
        "Option3" : "Mantle",
        "Option4" : "All of above",
        "Question" : "The -------is about 2900k thick",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgl1PhIacffwba9YcV" : {
        "Answer" : "Lower part to up ward",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 13:10:27",
        "Option1" : "Lower part to up ward",
        "Option2" : "Up wards to lower partl",
        "Option3" : "Lower part to  lower partl",
        "Option4" : "Up to batom",
        "Question" : "Convection current are \n Formed in the Mantle current flow,..",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "History" : {
      "-MGb-9h17whed-a-XeAj" : {
        "Answer" : "476",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:18:50",
        "Option1" : "376",
        "Option2" : "576",
        "Option3" : "476",
        "Option4" : "276",
        "Question" : "The Roman Empire collapsed in........",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGb-mW3_dQjryofLZtT" : {
        "Answer" : "1258",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:21:33",
        "Option1" : "1258",
        "Option2" : "1358",
        "Option3" : "1458",
        "Option4" : "1258",
        "Question" : "Hulagu Khan captured and destroyed Baghdad in......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGb0SVnC_hLfcM2d-E4" : {
        "Answer" : "Arabic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 10:24:29",
        "Option1" : "Latin",
        "Option2" : "English",
        "Option3" : "Arabic",
        "Option4" : "Urdu",
        "Question" : "......was made the state language and a postal service was introduced.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGb9XXVC0QvymdowMxn" : {
        "Answer" : "Golden age of  islam",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:4:9",
        "Option1" : "Diamond age of islm",
        "Option2" : "Silver age of  islam",
        "Option3" : "Golden age of  islam",
        "Option4" : "Hightest age of islam",
        "Question" : "Bagh was famous as......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbAfxt2HIwAAh0-IKz" : {
        "Answer" : "Baghdad",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:9:10",
        "Option1" : "Cardoba",
        "Option2" : "Baghdad",
        "Option3" : "Granada",
        "Option4" : "Sufia",
        "Question" : "Mamoon-al-Radheed established the Bait-hlkmha -The House of Wisdom in---------.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbCrkR0pEUtoS4gGju" : {
        "Answer" : "Tariq bin  ziyad",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:18:43",
        "Option1" : "Umer bin Abdullha",
        "Option2" : "Tariq bin  ziyad",
        "Option3" : "Sad bin  Abi waqas",
        "Option4" : "Hazrat usama",
        "Question" : "In,an army led by....crossed the strait of Gibraltar and conquered all of Spain.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbE1KInKMVfcthHXpC" : {
        "Answer" : "Turkey",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:23:49",
        "Option1" : "Turkey",
        "Option2" : "Syria",
        "Option3" : "Egypt",
        "Option4" : "Oman",
        "Question" : "Seljuq,They were of Turko-Persian origin and were mainly based in.......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbIycLV4AIooxH1jRN" : {
        "Answer" : "Chivalry and  generosity",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:45:24",
        "Option1" : "Chivalry and  generosity",
        "Option2" : "Wealth",
        "Option3" : "Noble",
        "Option4" : "Wisdom",
        "Question" : "Salahuddin-al-Ayubi known for his .....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbJiRiSVjeleQjzCXI" : {
        "Answer" : "Arabic",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:48:39",
        "Option1" : "Greek",
        "Option2" : " Latin",
        "Option3" : "Englihs",
        "Option4" : "Arabic",
        "Question" : "Mamluk means salve in.........",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbLtRkjlMp492GzcGu" : {
        "Answer" : "Islam",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 11:58:9",
        "Option1" : "Hindu",
        "Option2" : "Islam",
        "Option3" : "Christian",
        "Option4" : "Roman",
        "Question" : "....as a religion took in the Holy cities of Makkah and Midina in the Arabian  Peninsula.\n",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbNF2qbAfIgyazqA2P" : {
        "Answer" : "Umayyed",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:4:3",
        "Option1" : "Ottomans",
        "Option2" : "Umayyed",
        "Option3" : "Abbasids",
        "Option4" : "Roman",
        "Question" : "Cordoba was the capital of the......Empire in Spain.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbON1X9eC_8FUGVAR3" : {
        "Answer" : "Ibn-Hytham",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:8:58",
        "Option1" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Hytham",
        "Option3" : "Ibn-Sina",
        "Option4" : "Al-Kharezemi",
        "Question" : "He is known as the father of optic......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbPWDERxu7Wy5ufzHX" : {
        "Answer" : "Ibn-Sina",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:13:58",
        "Option1" : "Ibn-Sina",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Batuts",
        "Option3" : "Al- Razi",
        "Option4" : "Al-Ifrisi",
        "Question" : "He was a famous  Doctor at the Royal court.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbQcij-o9Jl61Lz9El" : {
        "Answer" : "Abn-Rushd",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:18:51",
        "Option1" : "Abn-Rushd",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Haytham",
        "Option3" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option4" : "Al-Beruni",
        "Question" : "He laid the foundations of Algabra.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbRXO-XD-JD0lS7-KF" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Idrisi",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:22:47",
        "Option1" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option2" : "Al-Idrisi",
        "Option3" : "Ibn-Haytham",
        "Option4" : "Ibn-Batuta",
        "Question" : "His geographical maps led to cartography.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbTcC5UdKphshIhIx9" : {
        "Answer" : "Ibn-Khaldun",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:31:55",
        "Option1" : "Ibn-Rushd",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Khaldun",
        "Option3" : "Al-idrisi",
        "Option4" : "Ibn-Sina",
        "Question" : "Who explain the cycle of rise and fall of civilization",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbV-5o3HqPGr1jUgql" : {
        "Answer" : "Ibn-Batuta",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:37:55",
        "Option1" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Batuta",
        "Option3" : "Al-Khwarazmi",
        "Option4" : "Al-Beruni",
        "Question" : "Who covered 12000miles as a travellers....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbYYpnAy9-lNZErCac" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Khwarezmi",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 12:53:28",
        "Option1" : "Ibn-Rushd",
        "Option2" : "Al-Khwarezmi",
        "Option3" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option4" : "Ibn-Batuta",
        "Question" : "Who established the Indian numeral system and the use of zero in mathematics.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbbZy7ZlshYJ1kg_Yv" : {
        "Answer" : "Poliymaths",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 13:11:1",
        "Option1" : "Poliymaths",
        "Option2" : "Historiography",
        "Option3" : "Alchemist",
        "Option4" : "Beauction",
        "Question" : "Muslims scholars were also called.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbcXIjkRpvQOhFOuF3" : {
        "Answer" : "1017",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 13:15:13",
        "Option1" : "1017",
        "Option2" : "117",
        "Option3" : "927",
        "Option4" : "1317",
        "Question" : "When Al- Beruni visited India.....",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGbct_xSDh40OSEJJ7I" : {
        "Answer" : "970",
        "Date" : "2020-9-7 13:16:48",
        "Option1" : "970",
        "Option2" : "879",
        "Option3" : "770",
        "Option4" : "670",
        "Question" : "Al-Azhar mosque was established in......",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGfl-PiFcOulrwQHtAr" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Beruni",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 8:30:42",
        "Option1" : "Al-Kindi",
        "Option2" : "Al-Beruni",
        "Option3" : "Ibn-Sina",
        "Option4" : "Al-Farabi",
        "Question" : "He was the most famous Muslims scientist of earlier times.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGfmxP0phnogEHJ0PLs" : {
        "Answer" : "Al-Razi",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 8:39:14",
        "Option1" : "Al-Razi",
        "Option2" : "Ibn-Haytham",
        "Option3" : "Al-Farabi",
        "Option4" : "Al-Kindi",
        "Question" : "He brought set up hospitals,diagnosed illness by  observing the symptoms of patients.",
        "author" : "najamnisa3@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgE1RPxOINzYfwCL2W" : {
        "Answer" : "1492",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:41:54",
        "Option1" : "1492",
        "Option2" : "1592",
        "Option3" : "1692",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "Muslims rule in Spain eventually weakened and comes to an end in...... ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGgEZICAkKLcKMAhUnO" : {
        "Answer" : "Turkey",
        "Date" : "2020-9-8 10:44:13",
        "Option1" : "Turkey",
        "Option2" : "Syria",
        "Option3" : "Oman ",
        "Option4" : "India",
        "Question" : "Seljuq they were of Turko-Persian origin and were mainly based in........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Islamiyat" : {
      "-MGCNBF6mVGj_vh0Uewt" : {
        "Answer" : "Revelation ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:53:41",
        "Option1" : "Revelation ",
        "Option2" : "Naat",
        "Option3" : "Hadees ",
        "Option4" : "Worship ",
        "Question" : "........ is a special and invisible communication.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCO62Tt0vWKat3efbn" : {
        "Answer" : "Angel Jibrael ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:57:42",
        "Option1" : "Angel Mikhail ",
        "Option2" : "Angel Jibrael ",
        "Option3" : "Angel Israel ",
        "Option4" : "Prophets ",
        "Question" : "The revelation to the Holy Prophet PBUH was brought by......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCP4FegnJgPwE2cCJH" : {
        "Answer" : "Holy Quran ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:1:57",
        "Option1" : "Bible ",
        "Option2" : "Hadees ",
        "Option3" : "Holy Quran ",
        "Option4" : "Book",
        "Question" : "...... is the revelation of Allah and most comprehensive book.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCPoRNTbXcumUQi2cD" : {
        "Answer" : "Fortieth ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:5:10",
        "Option1" : "Twentieth ",
        "Option2" : "Fortieth ",
        "Option3" : "Thirtieth ",
        "Option4" : "Twenty fifth ",
        "Question" : "The divine revelation of Holy Quran started in the......year of Holy Prophet's PBUH life.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCQNnvjt80261jzHTZ" : {
        "Answer" : "Written down ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:7:39",
        "Option1" : "Written down ",
        "Option2" : "Sent to everyone ",
        "Option3" : "Sent to companions ",
        "Option4" : "Sent to wives of Holy Prophet PBUH",
        "Question" : "The revelation were not only memorized, but also.........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCRHu1clbuMGkOsbWR" : {
        "Answer" : "Ramzan ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:11:37",
        "Option1" : "Shawal",
        "Option2" : "Rajab ",
        "Option3" : "Ramzan ",
        "Option4" : "Zill Hajj ",
        "Question" : "The first revelation came to the Holy Prophet PBUH in the month of.......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCSMEX9WFBjgjvQmDE" : {
        "Answer" : "Cave of Hira ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:16:17",
        "Option1" : "Cave of Hira ",
        "Option2" : "Cave of Safa ",
        "Option3" : "Cave of Sore ",
        "Option4" : "Cave of Hunain ",
        "Question" : "The Holy Prophet PBUH received first revelation in the......where he used to retire for meditation. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCTEP7iGhKpCuSlTY8" : {
        "Answer" : "Read ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:20:7",
        "Option1" : "Write",
        "Option2" : "Start",
        "Option3" : "Read ",
        "Option4" : "Allah",
        "Question" : "One day when Holy Prophet PBUH was praying he heard a voice saying.....",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCU3vCK9Fxx0izOXhr" : {
        "Answer" : "Hazrat Khadija R.A",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:23:45",
        "Option1" : "Hazrat Khadija R.A",
        "Option2" : "Hazrat Ayesha R.A",
        "Option3" : "Hazrat Um-e-Kalsoom R.A",
        "Option4" : "Hazrat Jaweria R.A",
        "Question" : "The Holy Prophet PBUH told all the incident to His wife.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUSNr2gw4lmVDTNWQ" : {
        "Answer" : "Warqa bin Nawfil ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:25:26",
        "Option1" : "Warqa bin Nawfil ",
        "Option2" : "Warqa bin Aman ",
        "Option3" : "Warqa bin Adil ",
        "Option4" : "Qarqa bin Hayan ",
        "Question" : "His wife took Him to her cousin....... ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUqL_ccHoffc6eo31" : {
        "Answer" : "Arafat ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:27:8",
        "Option1" : "Hunain ",
        "Option2" : "Safa",
        "Option3" : "Marwa ",
        "Option4" : "Arafat ",
        "Question" : "The last revelation came to the Holy Prophet PBUH on the plain of......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCV7YVjEgN-N7ESSpr" : {
        "Answer" : "10th",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:28:23",
        "Option1" : "10th",
        "Option2" : "9th",
        "Option3" : "1st",
        "Option4" : "5th",
        "Question" : "Holy Prophet PBUH received last revelation on.........(A.H)",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCVaswCK-ubukPmZWl" : {
        "Answer" : "Zill Hajj ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:30:27",
        "Option1" : "Shawal ",
        "Option2" : "Ramzan ",
        "Option3" : "Zill Hajj ",
        "Option4" : "Muharram ",
        "Question" : "The Holy Prophet PBUH received last revelation in the month of........ ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCW-EHjpkI4Kurgumy" : {
        "Answer" : "Article ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:32:11",
        "Option1" : "Half",
        "Option2" : "Full",
        "Option3" : "Article ",
        "Option4" : "Third ",
        "Question" : "Belief in Prophethood is one of the .........of faith.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWL43gWqBR6yVx4Io" : {
        "Answer" : "Divine ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:33:40",
        "Option1" : "Divine ",
        "Option2" : "Worldly ",
        "Option3" : "Inner",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "Prophet means a person who speaks by..... inspiration.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWhJZaqRphB7jaJPH" : {
        "Answer" : "Prophets ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:35:15",
        "Option1" : "People ",
        "Option2" : "Prophets ",
        "Option3" : "Angels ",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "Allah has sent His guidance for mankind through His......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWvTWySzAHzN9JPTM" : {
        "Answer" : "Message ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:36:13",
        "Option1" : "Message ",
        "Option2" : "Prophet ",
        "Option3" : "Book ",
        "Option4" : "Angel ",
        "Question" : "As Allah is one so is His......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXGUlm-fmOGCFpOcu" : {
        "Answer" : "Partners ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:37:43",
        "Option1" : "Books ",
        "Option2" : "Partners ",
        "Option3" : "Links ",
        "Option4" : "Worships ",
        "Question" : "The Holy Quran has expressly forbidden to ascribe.......to Allah.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXpigLOqGMHXuaY-I" : {
        "Answer" : "Worship ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:40:12",
        "Option1" : "Worship ",
        "Option2" : "Not to worship Him ",
        "Option3" : "Talk with angels ",
        "Option4" : "None of the above ",
        "Question" : "According to Islam Allah created man to....... him.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCYSHzlnki0AwvYoyL" : {
        "Answer" : "Different period ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:42:54",
        "Option1" : "Same period ",
        "Option2" : "Different period ",
        "Option3" : "After ten years ",
        "Option4" : "After two years ",
        "Question" : "Prophets came in........of history as they were needed.\n\n\n\n",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCYt1xTEt38snugsxZ" : {
        "Answer" : "One hundred and twenty four thousands",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:44:47",
        "Option1" : "One hundred and twenty four thousands",
        "Option2" : "One hundred and twenty three",
        "Option3" : "One hundred and twenty two thousands ",
        "Option4" : "One hundred and twenty one thousands ",
        "Question" : "The number of Prophets are......",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZBsTui0uEx9puzHs" : {
        "Answer" : "Twenty five",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:46:9",
        "Option1" : "Twenty one ",
        "Option2" : "Twenty two",
        "Option3" : "Twenty three",
        "Option4" : "Twenty five",
        "Question" : "The Holy Quran mentions...... prominent prophets. ",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCZo-FRgWB3STI3BMV" : {
        "Answer" : "Hazrat Adam A.S",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:48:49",
        "Option1" : "Hazrat Adam A.S",
        "Option2" : "Hazrat Isa A.S",
        "Option3" : "Hazrat Ibrahim A.S",
        "Option4" : "Hazrat Dawood A.S",
        "Question" : "Allah's guidance  to mankind began with........",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC_4kl1AaSLDUkDavw" : {
        "Answer" : "Last ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:50:2",
        "Option1" : "First ",
        "Option2" : "Last ",
        "Option3" : "Fourth ",
        "Option4" : "Sixth ",
        "Question" : "Hazrat Muhammad PBUH is the....... prophet of Allah.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGC_Iv594NGh0i_54u5" : {
        "Answer" : "Community ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:51:0",
        "Option1" : "Home ",
        "Option2" : "Family ",
        "Option3" : "Friends ",
        "Option4" : "Community ",
        "Question" : "Prophets were the best in their...... spiritually and morally.",
        "author" : "sehartahir297@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Math" : {
      "-MG1uk5kN6dM_fMCIeZN" : {
        "Answer" : "15 x exp 2 + 11",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:8:51",
        "Option1" : "15 x exp 2 + 29",
        "Option2" : "15 x exp 2 - 11",
        "Option3" : "15 x exp 2 + 11",
        "Option4" : "11 x exp 2 + 15",
        "Question" : "The solution of 6x  <sup>2</sup> + 19 + 9x  <sup>2</sup> – 8 is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1x6fJuWYpMRoWgcH6" : {
        "Answer" : "30 x exp 2",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:19:12",
        "Option1" : "3 x exp 2",
        "Option2" : "30 x exp 2",
        "Option3" : "33 x exp 2",
        "Option4" : "13 x exp 2",
        "Question" : "(-3x) x (-10x) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1xP742B0jNAHeizMY" : {
        "Answer" : "60x",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:20:28",
        "Option1" : "6x",
        "Option2" : "60x",
        "Option3" : "16x",
        "Option4" : "17x",
        "Question" : "12 x (5x) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1xifciwsKVUpNf2oB" : {
        "Answer" : "30d exp 2 – 24d",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:21:52",
        "Option1" : "30d - 24",
        "Option2" : "30d exp 2 – 24d",
        "Option3" : "30d – 24d exp 2",
        "Option4" : "30d exp 2 + 24d",
        "Question" : "6d (5d - 4) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1yfTzQHbAkRsBQPxf" : {
        "Answer" : "12x exp 2 + 20x",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:26:1",
        "Option1" : "12x exp 2 + 20x",
        "Option2" : "12x exp 2 - 20x",
        "Option3" : "20x exp 2 + 12x",
        "Option4" : "7x exp 2 + 9x",
        "Question" : "4x (3x + 5) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1z3RNjBbDK4eZWylY" : {
        "Answer" : "a exp 2 - 8a - 9",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:27:43",
        "Option1" : "a exp 2 - 9a - 8",
        "Option2" : "a exp 2 + 9a + 9",
        "Option3" : "a exp 2 - 9a + 8",
        "Option4" : "a exp 2 - 8a - 9",
        "Question" : "The solution of (a + 1)(a - 9) is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1zQPqHaoPim9ZiqrX" : {
        "Answer" : "(b - 7)(b - 8)",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:29:17",
        "Option1" : "(b - 7)(b - 8)",
        "Option2" : "(b + 7)(b - 8)",
        "Option3" : "(b - 7)(b + 8)",
        "Option4" : "(b + 7)(b + 8)",
        "Question" : "The factorization of  b  <sup>2</sup> – 15b + 56 is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG1ztXW64sZQJSQTQJn" : {
        "Answer" : "m exp 2 + 3m + 2",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:31:21",
        "Option1" : "m exp 2 - 3m - 3",
        "Option2" : "m exp 2 + 3m + 3",
        "Option3" : "m exp 2 + 3m + 2",
        "Option4" : "m exp 2- 3m + 3",
        "Question" : "(m + 2)(m + 1) are the factors of :",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2-FfIMPXxFT78cWtD" : {
        "Answer" : "20f exp 2 – 35f",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:32:55",
        "Option1" : "20f exp 2 – 30f",
        "Option2" : "20f exp 2 – 35f",
        "Option3" : "10f exp 2 – 35f",
        "Option4" : "12f exp 2 – 30f",
        "Question" : "5f (4f - 7) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG20LJMoEwuvHBX7feQ" : {
        "Answer" : "60c",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:37:41",
        "Option1" : "6c",
        "Option2" : "16c",
        "Option3" : "5c",
        "Option4" : "60c",
        "Question" : "20 x (3c) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG20gSkWpkGfjB9ubfB" : {
        "Answer" : "b exp 2 + 2b - 3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:39:11",
        "Option1" : "b exp 2 – 2b - 3",
        "Option2" : "b exp 2 + 4b - 3",
        "Option3" : "b exp 2 + 2b - 3",
        "Option4" : "b exp 2 - 6b - 3",
        "Question" : "The solution of (b - 1)(b + 3) is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG21J8iuO8Dpz4BuETx" : {
        "Answer" : "14ck - 63c",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:41:54",
        "Option1" : "14ck + 63c",
        "Option2" : "14ck + 36c",
        "Option3" : "14ck - 63c",
        "Option4" : "9ck + 16c",
        "Question" : "7c (2k - 9) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG21WzoDYcSY-o9PVY2" : {
        "Answer" : "2ab – 3ac",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:42:51",
        "Option1" : "2ab -2ac",
        "Option2" : "2ac + 3ac",
        "Option3" : "2ab – 3c",
        "Option4" : "2ab – 3ac",
        "Question" : "a (2b – 3c) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG21ttBSDQPKmzZzgjp" : {
        "Answer" : "27x exp 5",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:44:29",
        "Option1" : "27x exp 4",
        "Option2" : "12x exp 5",
        "Option3" : "27x exp 6",
        "Option4" : "27x exp 5",
        "Question" : "9x  <sup>3</sup> x 3x  <sup>2</sup> = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG22iEQ5L58_AHKZNGG" : {
        "Answer" : "(a - b)(a + 4b)",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:48:3",
        "Option1" : "(a - b)(a + 4b)",
        "Option2" : "(a - 2b)(a + 4b)",
        "Option3" : "(a - b)(2a + 4b)",
        "Option4" : "(2a - b)(a + 2b)",
        "Question" : "The factorization of  a  <sup>2</sup> + 3ab – 4b  <sup>2</sup> is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG23HPBiudthpCNzsZ8" : {
        "Answer" : "24x exp 5 y exp 3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:50:31",
        "Option1" : "24x exp 5 y exp 2",
        "Option2" : "42x exp 5 y exp 3",
        "Option3" : "24x exp 5 y exp 3",
        "Option4" : "24x exp 7 y exp 2",
        "Question" : "4x  <sup>3</sup> y  <sup>2</sup> x 6x  <sup>2</sup> y= ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG23gPcjxKmulUzviHg" : {
        "Answer" : "18ek – 6eh",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:52:18",
        "Option1" : "6ek – 8eh",
        "Option2" : "18ek + 6eh",
        "Option3" : "18ek – 6eh",
        "Option4" : "28ek – 6eh",
        "Question" : "3e (6k – 2h) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG24A0AHH7Zr6hlSz8g" : {
        "Answer" : "6c exp 2 + 24d + 6f  ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:54:23",
        "Option1" : "6c exp 2 + 24d + 6f  ",
        "Option2" : "16c exp 2 + 42d + 60f  ",
        "Option3" : "60c exp 2 + 2d + 4f  ",
        "Option4" : "6c exp 2 - 24d - 6f  ",
        "Question" : "The solution of 9c  <sup>2</sup> + 24d – 3c  <sup>2</sup> + 6f  is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG24oDfuxLbPrirnO2t" : {
        "Answer" : "21z exp 2 + 46y",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:57:12",
        "Option1" : "12z exp 2 + 54y",
        "Option2" : "12z exp 2 + 54y ",
        "Option3" : "21z exp 2 + 46y",
        "Option4" : "21z exp 2 - 54y",
        "Question" : "The solution of 12z  <sup>2</sup> + 50y + 9z  <sup>2</sup> – 4y is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG25IwSWMa7tA2J4xzv" : {
        "Answer" : "16k exp 2 + 56k",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 10:59:22",
        "Option1" : "16k exp 2 - 56k",
        "Option2" : "16k exp 2 + 65k",
        "Option3" : "61k exp 2 + 56k",
        "Option4" : "16k exp 2 + 56k",
        "Question" : "8k (2k + 7) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG26Xdm1ibNulvvS4qo" : {
        "Answer" : "c exp 2 - c - 6",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:4:44",
        "Option1" : "c exp 2 - 5c - 1",
        "Option2" : "c exp 2 - 5c - 6",
        "Option3" : "c exp 2 - c - 6",
        "Option4" : "c exp 2 - 5c - 5",
        "Question" : "The solution of (c + 2)(c - 3) is: ",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG27pVgI3jM5BDk6aE9" : {
        "Answer" : "(h - 3)(h - 5)",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:10:23",
        "Option1" : "(h - 3)(h - 5)",
        "Option2" : "(h - 6)(h - 8)",
        "Option3" : "(h - 3)(h + 5)",
        "Option4" : "(h - 1)(h - 15)",
        "Question" : "The factorization of  h  <sup>2</sup> – 8h + 15 is:",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG29iSUh7AzEMUJSDtR" : {
        "Answer" : "f exp 2 + 3f + 3",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:18:39",
        "Option1" : "f exp 2 - 3f - 3",
        "Option2" : "f exp 2 + 6f - 3",
        "Option3" : "f exp 2 - 6f - 3",
        "Option4" : "f exp 2 + 3f + 3",
        "Question" : "(f + 1)(f + 2) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2DZ1lyHKyedKbcLSb" : {
        "Answer" : "36d  <sup>2</sup> - 8d",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 13:17:10",
        "Option1" : "20d  <sup>2</sup> - 9d",
        "Option2" : "36d  <sup>2</sup> - 8d",
        "Option3" : "36d  <sup>2</sup> - 6d",
        "Option4" : "13d  <sup>2</sup> - 30d",
        "Question" : "4d (9d - 2) = ?",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG2DnDb4NPiMWNhm1r7" : {
        "Answer" : "-14c",
        "Date" : "2020-8-31 11:36:27",
        "Option1" : "-14c",
        "Option2" : "-114c",
        "Option3" : "+14c",
        "Option4" : "114c",
        "Question" : "2 x (-7c) = ?",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Science" : {
      "-MG7U03L3XS0KHHw7bfY" : {
        "Answer" : "a cell",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:5:24",
        "Option1" : "a cell",
        "Option2" : "an organ",
        "Option3" : "a tissue",
        "Option4" : "a muscle",
        "Question" : "A ..... is the basic unit of life and the smallest unit of a living thing.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7UR3u8TOlYOTDTbBd" : {
        "Answer" : "unicellular",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:7:15",
        "Option1" : "multicellular",
        "Option2" : "unicellular",
        "Option3" : "organ",
        "Option4" : "muscle",
        "Question" : "An organism or living thing that is made up of only one cell is called...........",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7UkNkBo1bzRu1YLOh" : {
        "Answer" : "one cell",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:8:38",
        "Option1" : "three cells",
        "Option2" : "one cell",
        "Option3" : "four cells",
        "Option4" : "million cells",
        "Question" : "A unicellular organism such as  the Paramecium is made up of only ..........",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7V4CrTPmyqPXe1CtO" : {
        "Answer" : "nucleus",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:10:3",
        "Option1" : "cytoplasm",
        "Option2" : "chloroplast",
        "Option3" : "cell wall",
        "Option4" : "nucleus",
        "Question" : "It controls all the activities of the cell, including cell repair.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7aS3ESuo3dqHgy8Is" : {
        "Answer" : "cell wall",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:37:54",
        "Option1" : "cell wall",
        "Option2" : "vacuole",
        "Option3" : "cytoplasm",
        "Option4" : "nucleus",
        "Question" : "It is a strong and stiff structure made of cellulose.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7b6WgeDPfi3g3lslW" : {
        "Answer" : "chloroplast",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:40:48",
        "Option1" : "chloroplast",
        "Option2" : "cytoplasm",
        "Option3" : "cell wall",
        "Option4" : "vacuole",
        "Question" : "These are disk-like structures which contain a green pigment called ......",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7bR4lF0LgFxnxSUJ6" : {
        "Answer" : "cytoplasm",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:42:12",
        "Option1" : "cell membrane",
        "Option2" : "cell wall",
        "Option3" : "vacuole",
        "Option4" : "cytoplasm",
        "Question" : "It is jelly-like and contains other celll parts such as the nucleus ans chloroplast.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7buep6IyasOVo-ysB" : {
        "Answer" : "dermal tissues",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:44:17",
        "Option1" : "vascular tissues",
        "Option2" : "dermal tissues",
        "Option3" : "ground tissues",
        "Option4" : "nerve tissues",
        "Question" : "The epidermal cells of a plant are organized into ..........",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7cVrn5lmqOMQd8aeH" : {
        "Answer" : "ground tissues",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:46:53",
        "Option1" : "nerve tissues",
        "Option2" : "dermal tissues",
        "Option3" : "vascular tissues",
        "Option4" : "ground tissues",
        "Question" : ".......... from the bulk of tissue of a plant and their functions include photosynthesis physical support and food storage.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG7cnooZf0jVIFIgYVe" : {
        "Answer" : "lungs",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 12:48:11",
        "Option1" : "lungs",
        "Option2" : "brain",
        "Option3" : "heart",
        "Option4" : "kidney",
        "Question" : "Enable gaseous exchange to take place.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8I9UFy2Mvqc1uQ_XK" : {
        "Answer" : "cell membrane",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 3:53:15",
        "Option1" : "cell wall",
        "Option2" : "vacuole",
        "Option3" : "nucleus",
        "Option4" : "cell membrane",
        "Question" : "The ....... is a partially permeable layer that controls the movement of materials into and out of the cell.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8Ij1Zt5XrKrpCt0qI" : {
        "Answer" : "division",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 3:55:44",
        "Option1" : "division",
        "Option2" : "multiplication",
        "Option3" : "subtraction",
        "Option4" : "addition",
        "Question" : "The splitting of a cell to produce two new cells is called cell .......",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8JALBMQw8IuUaKiA9" : {
        "Answer" : "vacuole",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 3:57:40",
        "Option1" : "nucleus",
        "Option2" : "vacuole",
        "Option3" : "cell wall",
        "Option4" : "DNA",
        "Question" : "The ....... almost fills the entire plant cell.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8L93JwK14-meae2v4" : {
        "Answer" : "1839",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:6:19",
        "Option1" : "1837",
        "Option2" : "1849",
        "Option3" : "1839",
        "Option4" : "1893",
        "Question" : "In ....... , two scientists,Sehwan and Scheiden, proposed the cell theory.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8LkO-T_0UcqZp1rM-" : {
        "Answer" : "300",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:8:56",
        "Option1" : "300",
        "Option2" : "400",
        "Option3" : "500",
        "Option4" : "600",
        "Question" : "More than ....... years ago, a scientist, Robert Hooke, used a microscope to observe thin slices of cork.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8QlotURl-aM8rbhkZ" : {
        "Answer" : "objective lense",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:30:52",
        "Option1" : "base",
        "Option2" : "focus knobs",
        "Option3" : "stage clips",
        "Option4" : "objective lense",
        "Question" : "....... magnifies the specimen.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8RDaOxrF3ykrwT0gF" : {
        "Answer" : "arm",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:32:50",
        "Option1" : "eye piece",
        "Option2" : "arm",
        "Option3" : "stage",
        "Option4" : "light source",
        "Question" : "...... should be held when moving a microscope.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8RmBuRDaxNYDySgiz" : {
        "Answer" : "focus knobs",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:35:16",
        "Option1" : "power switch",
        "Option2" : "focus knobs",
        "Option3" : "base",
        "Option4" : "stage",
        "Question" : "...... are turned to get a sharp and clear image.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8SazxmOrAzuWEd8Fx" : {
        "Answer" : "nerve cell",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:38:52",
        "Option1" : "red blood cell",
        "Option2" : "nerve cell",
        "Option3" : "white blood cell",
        "Option4" : "plaisade",
        "Question" : "A ....... has many branched endings to receive messages in the form of electrical signals.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8SxADGFVOm9jSnmMV" : {
        "Answer" : "24",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:40:23",
        "Option1" : "23",
        "Option2" : "22",
        "Option3" : "25",
        "Option4" : "24",
        "Question" : "Our cheek cells divide once every ...... hour.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8THcUYYftDgq9z_AB" : {
        "Answer" : "xylem",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:41:51",
        "Option1" : "xylem",
        "Option2" : "phloem",
        "Option3" : "vascular",
        "Option4" : "ground tissues",
        "Question" : "...... transports water and minerals.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8TocXnD_gsp0ijMFx" : {
        "Answer" : "specialized and connective tissue",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:44:10",
        "Option1" : "nerve tissue",
        "Option2" : "muscle tissue",
        "Option3" : "connective tissue",
        "Option4" : "specialized and connective tissue",
        "Question" : "Organs are made up of.........",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8U8w24jPZ9VCCopjB" : {
        "Answer" : "sperm cell",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:45:37",
        "Option1" : "sperm cell",
        "Option2" : "palisade cell",
        "Option3" : "groud cell",
        "Option4" : "nerve cell",
        "Question" : "A ....... has a long tail which enables it to swim towards an egg to fertilize.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MG8UZR37YznjZG8TxGH" : {
        "Answer" : "red blood cell",
        "Date" : "2020-9-1 4:47:26",
        "Option1" : "nerve cell",
        "Option2" : "white cell",
        "Option3" : "red blood cell",
        "Option4" : "gaurd cell",
        "Question" : "A .......... contains a red pigment called hemoglobin which enables it to transport oxygen.",
        "author" : "sirfaisalky786@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCDhV1-X_6OmTEfOL0" : {
        "Answer" : "Genes ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:12:14",
        "Option1" : "Genes ",
        "Option2" : "Chromosome ",
        "Option3" : "Nucleus ",
        "Option4" : "DNA",
        "Question" : "..... determine many charateristics or traits such as height and the colour of eyes, skin and hair.",
        "author" : "mohib2156@gmail.com"
      }
    },
    "Urdu" : {
      "-MFnb0wZypjN_O4AYIRa" : {
        "Answer" : "امریکہ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:48:24",
        "Option1" : "پاکستان",
        "Option2" : "برطانیہ",
        "Option3" : "امریکہ",
        "Option4" : "جاپان",
        "Question" : "س۔15واشنگٹن جس ملک کا شہر ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbU-99slHKAzaYGIV" : {
        "Answer" : "تضادات",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:50:22",
        "Option1" : "تضادات",
        "Option2" : "تض",
        "Option3" : "تضادوں",
        "Option4" : "تضادے",
        "Question" : "س16۔تضاد کا جمع ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnbyw0QsjlFbHrfyat" : {
        "Answer" : "رجحانات",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:52:33",
        "Option1" : "رحجانوں",
        "Option2" : "رجحانات",
        "Option3" : "رجھان",
        "Option4" : "راجحانات",
        "Question" : "س17۔رحجان کا جمع ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncPIqjnbl0MRxLIsw" : {
        "Answer" : "رفت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:54:25",
        "Option1" : "آنا",
        "Option2" : "رفت",
        "Option3" : "استقبال",
        "Option4" : "پیشکش",
        "Question" : "س18۔آمد کا متضاد ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFncnKEKzv-pRhF7MjJ" : {
        "Answer" : "پستی",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:56:8",
        "Option1" : "اونچائی",
        "Option2" : "برتری",
        "Option3" : "بڑائی",
        "Option4" : "پستی",
        "Question" : "س19۔بلندی کا متضاد ہے۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFndZ3UjQ7CB5ULr6E5" : {
        "Answer" : "حرارت",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 10:59:28",
        "Option1" : "سردی",
        "Option2" : "حرارت",
        "Option3" : "گرمی",
        "Option4" : "ٹھنڈ",
        "Question" : "س20۔تپش کا مترادف ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFne0bJtJmGD3RTEWPw" : {
        "Answer" : "لفظ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:1:28",
        "Option1" : "کلمہ",
        "Option2" : "اسم",
        "Option3" : "لفظ",
        "Option4" : "جملہ",
        "Question" : "س21۔حروف کے مجموعے کو کہتے ہیں۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFneHm-mv51LXqUiKpV" : {
        "Answer" : "2",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:2:39",
        "Option1" : "2",
        "Option2" : "3",
        "Option3" : "4",
        "Option4" : "5",
        "Question" : "س22۔لفظ کی اقسام ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnekKSi8pwUm9vVItq" : {
        "Answer" : "مہمل",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:4:40",
        "Option1" : "اسم",
        "Option2" : "فعل",
        "Option3" : "کلمہ",
        "Option4" : "مہمل",
        "Question" : "س23۔بے معنی کو کہتے  ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnf56BoyigjBpmzKks" : {
        "Answer" : "کلمہ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:6:9",
        "Option1" : "کلمہ",
        "Option2" : "مہمل",
        "Option3" : "اسم",
        "Option4" : "فعل",
        "Question" : "س24۔الفاظ کے مجموعے کو کہتے ہیں۔",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MFnfPYg4AxtgfxKPfRy" : {
        "Answer" : "کلمہ",
        "Date" : "2020-8-28 11:7:33",
        "Option1" : "کلمہ",
        "Option2" : "مہمل",
        "Option3" : "اسم",
        "Option4" : "فعل",
        "Question" : "س25۔ہر با معنی لفظ کہلاتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCKp7dkjomCNtc5p0i" : {
        "Answer" : "اللہ کی تعریف",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:43:22",
        "Option1" : "اللہ کی تعریف",
        "Option2" : "حضرت محمد صلی اللہ علیہ وسلم کی تعریف",
        "Option3" : "بادشاہ کی تعریف",
        "Option4" : "سردار کی تعریف",
        "Question" : "حمد کا مطلب ہے ",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCLYy7CErHSyyvb-_c" : {
        "Answer" : "حفیظ الرحمان غازی",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:46:34",
        "Option1" : "حفیظ جالندھری",
        "Option2" : "حفیظ تائب",
        "Option3" : "حفیظ الرحمان غازی",
        "Option4" : "صوفی تبسم",
        "Question" : "نظم حمد کے شاعر ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCLvj_gEUh4YBwLD4_" : {
        "Answer" : "گلشن",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:48:11",
        "Option1" : "گلشن",
        "Option2" : "چمن",
        "Option3" : "جنگل",
        "Option4" : "نشیمن",
        "Question" : "یہ ۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔۔ میں پھولوں کی رنگین قطاریں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCMvODbbd4VG2ivNn9" : {
        "Answer" : "اتحاد،ایمان،نظم و ضبط",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:52:32",
        "Option1" : "اتحاد،نظم و ضبط،ایمان",
        "Option2" : "نظم و ضبط،اتحاد،ایمان",
        "Option3" : "اتحاد،ایمان،نظم و ضبط",
        "Option4" : "ایمان،اتحاد،نظم و ضبط",
        "Question" : "قائداعظم کے فرمان کی درست ترتیب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCNoo6_qnu9_ne-7Z8" : {
        "Answer" : "دل",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:56:27",
        "Option1" : "پاوں",
        "Option2" : "ہاتھ",
        "Option3" : "ٹانگیں",
        "Option4" : "دل",
        "Question" : "صفیں ٹیڑھی بنانے سے اللہ تعالی ٹیڑھے کر دیتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCOH8VJdAZt_-5tWz2" : {
        "Answer" : "عربی",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 10:58:27",
        "Option1" : "عربی",
        "Option2" : "فارسی",
        "Option3" : "انگریزی",
        "Option4" : "جاپانی",
        "Question" : "نظم اور ضبط جس زبان کے الفاظ ہیں",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCOtQ_KDwHWTguSQcV" : {
        "Answer" : "شکست",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:1:8",
        "Option1" : "کامیابی",
        "Option2" : "شکست",
        "Option3" : "عداوت",
        "Option4" : "شاباش",
        "Question" : "نظم و ضبط سے محروم ٹیم کے مقدر میں لکھ دی جاتی ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCP_ek2MerQ8kFJY4t" : {
        "Answer" : "گیارہ سال",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:4:9",
        "Option1" : "آٹھ سال",
        "Option2" : "نو سا ل",
        "Option3" : "گیارہ سال",
        "Option4" : "پندرہ سال",
        "Question" : "آرول کی عمر سات سال جبکہ ولبر تھا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUNw_1cPR1fem6VbZ" : {
        "Answer" : " 1903،17 دسمبر",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:25:8",
        "Option1" : " 1903،17 دسمبر",
        "Option2" : " 1904،5 دسمبر",
        "Option3" : "1906،16 دسمبر",
        "Option4" : "1908،25 دسمبر",
        "Question" : "شمالی کیرولینا کے مقام کٹی ہاک پر کی گئی پہلی پرواز",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCUhz_v7Uq4L2QctH3" : {
        "Answer" : "59سیکنڈ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:26:34",
        "Option1" : "55سیکنڈ",
        "Option2" : "56سیکنڈ",
        "Option3" : "57سیکنڈ",
        "Option4" : "59سیکنڈ",
        "Question" : "ولبر فضا میں رہا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCVKH7cs4lS48Ihh9P" : {
        "Answer" : "چھاپا خانہ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:29:15",
        "Option1" : "دوا خانہ",
        "Option2" : "مردہ خانہ",
        "Option3" : "چھاپا خانہ",
        "Option4" : "شفا خانہ",
        "Question" : "پرنٹنگ پریس ہوتا ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWLhd-z2R8jrG4KcH" : {
        "Answer" : "1900-1902",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:33:43",
        "Option1" : "1800-1900 ",
        "Option2" : "1880-1906",
        "Option3" : "1900-1902",
        "Option4" : "1906-1908",
        "Question" : "دنوں بھائی جہاز کے سلسلے میں مسلسل تجربات کرتے رہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCWgWazCbuvFHLjC0l" : {
        "Answer" : "ٹائفائیڈ",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:35:12",
        "Option1" : "ہیضہ",
        "Option2" : "ملیریا",
        "Option3" : "ٹائفائیڈ",
        "Option4" : "تپ دق ",
        "Question" : "ولبر جس مرض میں مبتلا ہوا",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      },
      "-MGCXAOzfjhRzU9Mx543" : {
        "Answer" : "بکھر جانا",
        "Date" : "2020-9-2 11:37:19",
        "Option1" : "اکھٹا ہونا",
        "Option2" : "بکھر جانا",
        "Option3" : "ضائع ہو نا",
        "Option4" : "ظاہر ہو نا",
        "Question" : "انتشار کا مطلب ہے",
        "author" : "rizwanatameem@gmail.com"
      }
    }
  }
}
